Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
Tendou!
Stop it!
Hand over the belt!
Do not touch me.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Stop it!
You guys are no match for him!
What an interesting thing to say.
So he is Kabuto after all?
According to Misaki, you're his friend, right?
Be good and follow orders.
That won't work.
He...
That's right.
We're not friends.
But...
If you want it that badly, I'll give you it.
Stop it!
That's a good attitude.
So this is the scheme you
were talking about earlier?
Go to Tokyo Tower for me will you?
You did a good job.
I appreciate your cooperation, boy.
Are you Kabuto?
What a silly question.
Do you face the sun and say "Are you the sun?"
Why do you have a Rider Belt?
Another foolish question.
Do you face the sun and ask "Why do you shine?"
Someone I know was suspected of
being Kabuto and has been captured.
What's going on?!
That's for headquarters to decide.
But he's not Kabuto!
He's not involved.
That's for headquarters to decide as well.
Tadokoro, do you consent to Misaki
being placed on a different team?
Of course.
I wonder what's happened to Tendou?
If he resists ZECT...
...there's a chance he might be eliminated.
But hang on a sec...
This might be a chance for Tendou to join ZECT.
That'd probably be best for him.
Go to Tokyo Tower for me will you?
Tokyo Tower!
Umm...
Waiting for someone?
She took a rest, but said she's alright.
So we didn't take her to a hospital.
Hiyori.
Oh, it's Kagami.
Mister.
Thank you.
Right.
Hey, hold on.
Where is he?
You mean Tendou?
Did something happen?
Yeah...
But nothing terribly serious to him.
Where is he?
Don't know...
It was all a lie!
I bet he just didn't want to go with me.
No!
He's strange, but he wouldn't lie.
Whatever.
The one who lied...
...is me.
Bro, you're way too late!
Hiyori?
He's not here?
Say something.
Misaki.
Pick up the phone.
What was that?!
It's time for a phone call.
Stop screwing around!
You're the prisoner here!
My dear little sister is waiting for my return.
Do you want to make her worry more?
Put it to my ear.
I'll cut it off the moment you
say anything superfluous.
Just a second.
Hello?
Juka, It's me.
Big Brother?
Where and what are you doing?
I'm trying to help a friend with their problems...
...but he's being a real tough case.
Hiyori is here.
Good timing.
Can you put her on?
It's Tendou.
Hello?
Hiyori, I have a favor to ask.
Can you make pancakes for Juka?
That's what she has on Sundays.
Stop screwing around!
I waited for you!
Among those hateful crowds...
All that time!
With that much spirit...
you won't lose to the crowds.
I am by your side.
And...
I will give a one-of-a-kind tulip to you alone.
Forget it!
I hate liars!
Satisfied?
Not yet.
Aren't you supposed to provide pork
with rice during interrogations.
Make sure it tastes good.
Hey.
I don't think Tendou is a liar.
Do you want to eat?
Pancakes...
Okay!
Where is he hidden?
That Tendou... I hope he's not suffering...
Hey.
How many ZECT teams are there?
Why do you want to know?
Do they tell you the important details?
Do you know if headquarters
give the instructions?
I'm the one that's doing the interrogation.
Now cut it out.
Delicious!
Absolutely fantastic!
Tadokoro, you know where Misaki is, right?!
What'll you do if I told you?
I've got to stop Misaki.
You cannot defy headquarters.
Headquarters! Headquarters!
I'm talking about Misaki!
What Misaki is doing is wrong!
Real comrades correct each other
when they are wrong, don't they?
I don't want to be a liar!
Tell me, please!
But still, he...
He didn't come home last night?
But it's Tendou, so I'm not worried.
He promised you, right?
Yup!
He said he'd never let me be afraid again.
And...
He said he'd always be by my side.
Always by your side?
Yup!
Resist and I'll shoot.
Misaki.
I'm disappointed in you.
You can go back now.
What do you mean?!
As long as we have the Belt...
...he cannot become Kabuto.
Stop this tepid interrogation...
...and begin interrogating with more force.
Tendou's up there?
New weapons?
Where's the prisoner?
You.
What's your name?
It's Katou.
Mackerel?
Talk!
Mackerel or pork?!
Which do you like?!
It's me.
Get in!
What the hell happened?!
Looks like the Worms are
after ZECT's headquarters.
Headquarters?
But no one knows where headquarters is located.
No, there's a way...
...if you mimic a ZECT member.
Misaki is in danger.
We've got to get the Belt to headquarters
before the Worms attack again.
Misaki.
Please hurry and contact headquarters.
Okay.
Yes?
It's Kagami.
Stay calm and listen.
The two you're with are Worms.
Get the Belt out.
If you get it out, there's
someone who can do something.
Sorry, but we...
...have a higher sense of hearing than humans.
You!
Time to pay you back...
...for the pork and rice.
I'm entrusting this belt to you.
Hiyori.
Come again.
I think he's a liar after all.
Juka... he's been gone so long...
No...
He's here.
My grandmother once said...
"When not close by, one is even closer".
So... you are Kabuto after all.
Time for you to feel the heat of the sun.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
So are you going to report to headquarters?
Of course.
But this is what I'm going to say...
"The man I was after....
...wasn't Kabuto"
Misaki.
When not close by, one is even closer...
But...
...no one is by my side.
'Heaven'
A one-of-a-kind tulip...
That guy...
We've lost Kabuto.
Seems like he's a rather tough opponent.
So then...
He is an elephant.
They are the most affectionate among animals.
But...
Even an elephant...
Those that are not on my side are discarded.
And...
To protect me...
...he will be eliminated.
Right?
Do not worry.
We've already started our next plan.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
The most important thing
in battle is... "Perfect Harmony".
It's a cooking contest? And you're using my kitchen?
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.
Defeating Kabuto... is my mission.