Mom...
Protect me.
Hiyori...
You...!
Hiyori is a Worm...
That can't be!
Put on!
PUT ON
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Hiyori!
Where are you?!
Let's go. She's not here anymore.
I... still don't believe it.
Hiyori is a Worm...
What... will you do with Hiyori?
I told you before.
When dealing with a Worm, I show them no mercy...
Before I defeat them.
Don't say that!
We're talking about Hiyori!
Don't you feel sorry for her?!
How naive.
Go home and take a nap.
I will take care of Hiyori.
It's a new Worm.
This woman...
Mamiya Reina's actions of late have us worried.
Get her before she does.
No matter who the enemy is...
...I will protect you!
I'm...
Come with me.
Come on!
You're so good with women, Kageyama Shun.
You!
Hand that woman over.
What?
I was told nothing of the sort.
I was told nothing as well.
Stop!
I won't let you do what you want with Hiyori!
She's a Worm.
Are you going to cover for a Worm?
This is some kind of mistake. Hiyori isn't a Worm!
A hot head as always.
Eliminate those that
defy the organization. Fire!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
My friend. Kagamin!
Tsurugi!
Now is the time I repay for
your noble friendship.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Kabuto!
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
You can't be...!
RIDER KICK
Stop it!
Hang in there... Hiyori.
Tendou.
Are you feeling well?
But... just now I...
That was just an act.
HYPER CLOCK UP
HYPER CLOCK OVER
But for what reason did you do that?
To make them think you're dead, Hiyori.
Now, you won't be chased anymore.
But why do this for someone like me?
I'm one of those monsters that you call a Worm.
You are my little sister.
Don't joke.
That can't be possible.
Come to think about it...
Why do you have a photo of my parents?
Hey, Souji!
One more picture!
Souji! One more! Another photo!
Souji, wait!
Hey, wait! Souji!
My parents... were mimicked by the Worm...
...and killed.
At the time...
...in my mother...
...was a baby.
If it were a girl...
...she was going to be named Hiyori.
Tendou... comes from my
grandmother who took me in.
My name used to be... Kusakabe Souji.
It can't be...
The Worm that killed your parents were...
Seven years ago, on that day...
I saw my parents that should have been dead.
No...
The Worms who had killed
and mimicked my parents.
I couldn't forgive those two.
I planned to someday take revenge on them.
Please! Don't kill!
But...
When I saw you... I...
Please!
I will be by your side.
Those words...
They still remain in my heart.
So that was you.
You are my little sister.
Killed before being born... my only little sister.
If I can't save you, then who can I save?
But...
I was born a Worm.
Don't worry.
You may not be able to
return to the restaurant, but...
Grandmother will take you in.
Wait just a moment.
I'll be right back.
Come with me.
Since you know that Hiyori is alive...
...I have no choice but to kill you.
Hold on a second.
Why?!
My grandmother once said...
"Even in a world full only with enemies,
there will always be someone you must protect"
World full of enemies...
If it's to protect Hiyori,
I will defeat all Worms and humans!
That's all.
Calm down! I'm not your enemy!
I want to help Hiyori too!
Tell me.
After your grandmother takes her in,
what will happen to Hiyori?
Hiyori will continue living as Hiyori.
Hiyori will...
...live as Hiyori?
I will defeat all Worms except Hiyori.
Then there will be no problem.
Are you... serious?
To do that...
I have prepared for seven years.
What's your decision?!
Will you do as I say?!
Or will you be killed by me right here?!
It's okay.
I'm by your side.
Speaking of which...
He's always by my side.
Don't be decieved.
Tendou Souji's words are
nothing but a fabrication.
I...
...want to believe in him.
But...
He's the one who invited me here.
He...
...attacked you.
It's only natural.
You are a Worm.
If he covers for a Worm...
...he will become the enemy of humans.
Stop it!
Please stop it!
To humans, the Worm are their enemies.
You are humanity's enemy.
You can't live in human society.
Who's that?
Is it calling for me?
Mother...
Please tell me.
Where is Hiyori?
Who is it?
Is it calling for me?
Stay away!
This place is off limits!
Stop!
We'll fire if you continue!
It's a Worm!
Fire!
This is...
Hiyori is inside.
Who is it that calls for me?
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Clock Up!
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Where is Hiyori?
She's in here.
Go if you want.
I won't stop you.
Hiyori!
That's...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I, Takatori Renge, will work hard as
Mr. Tendou's second-in-command.
Tendou is trying to gather all the Zecters.
I am the only Rider needed.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.