Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Rider Kick!
A Worm?!
Just what is this place?
Seems like some kind of
experiment was being conducted here.
Experiment?
For what?
Well...
For example...
...the Masked Rider Project?
That can't be!
Masked Rider Project...
1971.
That's...
Thirty-five years ago.
Why would the Masked Rider
Project exist so long ago?
You guys... what were you just talking about?
Don't worry about it.
Weird guys talking about weird fairy tales.
This is...!
What is it?
The god of battle, Gatack's chosen one.
Kagami Arata.
My name...
...why is it in a file from thirty-five years ago?
Hiyori, stay here.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
There's new movement in the factory.
What is this place?
Follow them!
Stop!
You won't get away!
Mishima.
What's that file?
And what was that room?
None of your business.
The roots are even deeper than I thought.
The organization called ZECT,
as well as the Masked Rider Project.
Summer break sure is nice!
Let's eat!
Being able to eat without having
to worry about school is the best!
And this too.
That really is the best.
But why?
Could it be you're going to work?
Being a salaryman wouldn't be bad. I'm going.
Come back by this afternoon.
You promised to take me to the pool.
Yeah.
To the criminals. You are
completely surrounded. Come out!
You're the one in charge here?
Who are you?
Let's enter in one minute.
Put the money in the bag!
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
My grandmother once said...
"In this world, there are no bad
restaurants or evil-doers who prosper."
That wasn't possible!
Let me go!
The guys at the central
station really do things differently.
It's no big deal.
Yo!
You're investigating the
upper ranks of the police?
But... why the cops?
If I approach ZECT, they would have a strong front.
...but the police might have an opening I can use.
I see.
The police superiors are definitely
connected to ZECT, right?
Wait a minute.
Speaking of the police... my father is also...
But that...
I will act my own way.
Here are your next orders.
She's a Worm. Eliminate her.
I've heard the Worms have
been acting differently recently.
What's going on?
There are somethings that
you don't need to know.
Yes.
I understand.
What is it?
Why are you in the rain?
I...
...haven't made any progress from before.
Even though I went to Shibuya...
I didn't figure anything out.
Well, I was able to confirm something at least.
But in life there is much that you don't know.
You're always dodging the issue like that.
I'm suffering because of you.
Was the boy with the belt you?
How long do you plan to keep dodging me?
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Hiyori.
Run!
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Thanks for waiting.
This is roast beef with petite vegetables.
Take your time to enjoy it.
Welcome.
Has Tendou been here?
Seems he's pretty busy.
I see. He has a little sister, right?
What's her name?
Juka, you mean?
I see. Juka, right?
Misaki?
Yes.
Headquarters has contacted Tadokoro.
Now's the time for carrying out that plan.
Misaki?!
What about Juka?
What are you talking about?
Come here right away.
Okay.
Tendou, welcome home!
Juka's preparations are all okay!
You're Tendou's little sister, right?
Section chief.
He's the one who handled the bank robbery.
You're the one?
Here.
Seeing your rumpled uniform,
I can tell you've been working all night.
You...
The incident was solved because
such a section chief was hard at work.
Put this in your tea, and relieve your fatigue.
We've arrived at the designated location.
Tadokoro.
We're switching cars. From this
point on it's just Mr. Tadokoro.
No.
Misaki is my capable subordinate.
Misaki. Come with me.
Okay, Tadokoro.
Wow. Misaki, you're great!
Jump in, Juka!
Okay! Juka is going!
I am the man who stands at the top of diving!
You are... Kamishiro Tsurugi.
You are?
I see. So such a great cop is from headquarters?
He has very sharp senses.
I see.
You are?
Chief. Pleased to meet you.
He's the one.
I see.
Not only are you keen,
you also act promptly.
Please get out.
Switching cars again?
How many times must we
switch before you're satisfied?
We've arrived at headquarters.
However, keep the blindfold on.
This is..!
You aren't Tadokoro, are you?
We're putting you under arrest.
TRANSFORM
Transform.
Are you the one searching for me?
Let's engrave this onto your grave...
"Kageyama Shun. Also known as TheBee."
You!
Sneaking around right in front of me!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Get away. You'll get hurt.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Stop!
We'll fire!
Fire!
Don't get in the way!
You're...
What's this?
I was wondering who it was.
That's what you deserve.
I know.
The wind blows to everyone...
...no matter how despicable they are.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
That's...
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Cast Off!
CLOCK UP
Police Headquarters
Juka.
Start talking!
Tell me everything about
the Masked Rider Project!
Return to Masked Form!
Don't give me orders!
Put on!
PUT ON
Commissioner.
It has been a while.
Hey, you! You're standing before the commissioner!
It's okay.
He's a friend of my son.
Are you well?
I wouldn't have guessed you
were the police commissioner.
Then there's something I want to ask you.
Were you the one who wrote the names
for the invitation list thirty-five years ago?
What invitation list could you be talking about?
Masquerade.
A masked party.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I will lure you to hell with my beautiful requiem.
Just remember this...
No matter who the enemy is... I will protect you!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.