ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER SHOOTING
Um vento caprichoso está soprando?
Vento caprichoso? Está errado.
Você se lembra da nossa última batalha?
I am here just to pay you back!
I'm surprised by how petty you are.
Drake?
Show me what you've got!
Ei.
Am I your opponent or what?
Isso mesmo.
Te derrotar é a minha missão!
Por que não? Ele era apenas um aprendiz.
Você não tem o direito de liderar pessoas.
O quê?!
Se não tivessemos sido interrompidos....
Parece que meu débito aumentou.
Eu não vou com a cara dele.... Tendou Souji.
O que está errado?
Dói?
Você poderia ao menos me responder.
Acho que ele está em choque
por ser usado pelo Kageyama.
Que patético...
Primeiro de tudo, foi culpa sua ser usado.
Como você pode se sentir mal,
se sua vida foi salva?
Kagami!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Que cheiro bom!
Sim.
Está pronto.
Parece delicioso!
Vamos comer!
Onii-san, mais uma vez a
comida de hoje está ótima!
My stomach feels all happy inside!
Hey, hey. If you cram like that you'll choke.
See.
Just like I said. Here.
Thank goodness. I thought I was going to die.
But this is so delicious!
Yeah, Whole fried new potatoes.
The important thing is the potatoes you buy.
The outside has to be crisp, the inside fluffy.
While enjoying the fragrant smell, you eat it.
But everything you make is good.
What's your secret?
You have to make it when your happy.
In the oil, even an enemy's tear wouldn't congeal.
What a truly interesting fellow.
How utterly unbelievable.
Kagami was used by Shadow...
...by Kageyama as bait!
This cannot be acceptable!
Shadow acts according to ZECT.
We're just members.
As a result... are you saying what
happens to us doesn't matter?
Misaki... Our lives are in the
hands of ZECT, the organization.
And... that is what we signed up for.
O Soba
Welcome!
Fried oyster soba.
Got it.
What'll you have? I'll treat you today.
Here you go.
Mister, give him tempura soba.
Right!
Here.
Hey there!
How long are you going to be depressed!
Are you a man?
It's not funny!
I almost died!
And...
And what?!
Kageyama used me as a lure...
He must have thought it'd be okay if I died.
Like I was worthless.
Kagami Arata!
Y-yes.
What?
Eat! Your noodles will grow stale.
Oden
Pounded fish cake.
Okay.
Here you go.
Here.
Delicious!
Boss!
Ghost.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Hello?
Sensei, this is the emergency room!
We need you to do a emergency operation.
Righty o.
Boss.
I'm going.
Okay. Come again!
Sincerity South General Hospital
Wakabayashi, are you okay?!
Please give me the usual.
Okay.
Alright.
Scalpel.
Okay.
The sponge next.
Pliers.
Okay.
Amazing.
Of course.
He's usually just an old man, but when he holds
a scalpel he's the world's greatest surgeon.
Looks like the bleeding's stopped.
We'll be finished in thirty minutes.
Please take your time.
How rare it is for you to call me.
Was it a bother?
No, not so.
Rather, I'm quite pleased.
Eating together like this...
...it really has been a long time.
As the Superintendent General of the police...
...I don't have very much time.
What is it? You want to talk about something, right?
No, nothing in particular.
I don't know what happened....
...but you should have confidence.
You can do it if you try.
I know best as I've watched
you since you were little.
You are my pride.
Now...
...and in the future.
Thank you.
Father.
Well...
Let's eat.
But... if he knew your secret identity....
He would be quite shocked.
It doesn't matter.
We'll deal with that when the time comes.
Iron...
...becomes stronger only through forging.
Wait, Kagami!
Wait!
What is the meaning of this?
Absence Notice
Like it says, I'm taking a break from work.
Please give that to Tadokoro.
You're free to take a break from work, but...
Why do you need to take a computer with you?
Give it back.
Hey...
Yo.
Don't shout in public.
It's a nuisance.
You want to solve a case without
relying on the organization?
So that's how it is?
Yeah.
I want to prove myself.
I want to show that I can do it if I try.
It's too dangerous! Facing a Worm alone.
So... what kind of case is this?
This is a graphic created from
the testimony of witnesses.
There's a good chance the
Worm is mimicking this man.
All the victim's bodies were changed
into a dry wood like substance.
A human couldn't have done it.
Anyway I'm going to try.
Also to stop the increase of victims.
Wait! Kagami!
I've got it. Why don't you
support him from the shadows?
I don't have the free time for such a guy.
You...
What? Come to exchange blows again?
My, my. Why are you always
trying to pick a fight like that?
There's no talking to you.
I just like the coffee here.
Life has granted me enough wandering.
Can you talk a little more normally?
Yes! Good change.
I was smitten by your beauty when we last met.
You are truly beauty's...
Beauty's....
Umm...
....personification.
Yes yes.
That that.
I'm asking can you please talk more normally?
Please become a make up model.
I can get you into the most
famous global magazines.
Okay... but I have a condition.
Any condition is no condition to me.
Just a moment.
I know it's sudden, but I want to check.
What are they doing in the shop?
Perfect.
It's true, your make up is first rate.
But you should also change
the hair style in this case.
Honestly. What are they doing in the shop?
Perfect.
Well? This suits her better now.
No.
She was better before.
Now.
Before.
Sincerity South General Hospital
Most of the incidents occurred around here.
So that means...
There's a good chance this man will appear again.
Could it be the condition is to support that guy?
Yeah. Just be quiet and do as I say.
Okay.
That guy!
Lucky! He already found the target.
That's...
This is...
Looks like more is going on than it appears.
How strange....
It's been two days.
And nothing suspicious yet.
How long do you plan to follow him?
Hey!
Two identical humans means
one has to be a Worm.
The Worm will definitely
try to kill the real one.
When those two come in contact...
One will show himself as a Worm.
Welcome.
They've met at last.
Listen. You're up when one turns into a Worm.
Pounded fish cake.
Okay.
Cheers.
Delicious!
Looks like they're getting along.
Boss.
Yes.
Ghost.
Looks like they just did a skit.
What's going on?!
What's going on?! The one I was
following wasn't a Worm?!
That can't be! There were so many witnesses!
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Get back!
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE DRAGONFLY
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
What?!
Fire!
Kageyama, change into TheBee and attack up front.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
First platoon from the left. Second platoon
cut off it's path of retreat from the right.
Right!
Roger!
My grandmother once said...
Cast Off.
"Fighting is something done from the stomach."
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Put your gut into it!
No way....
It can't be...
Tendou...
Why are you...?
What's going on?!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Riders that don't join ZECT must be eliminated.
That's the captain's orders!
But why doesn't the Worm try to kill the real one?
Allow me to demonstrate... how to truly fight.
Transform!
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.