In 1999, a meteorite landed in Shibuya.
From it an alien life form, the Worms, were born.
They have the ability to mimic.
They are a cruel and sly life form.
Stop!
To counter this unprecedented
crisis, we created ZECT.
And so, it is time for a new system.
Do not worry.
Lately the Worm numbers
have really gone down.
At this rate, our victory is almost certain.
No.
The battle has just begun.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Hello? It's a Worm!
I'm dead.
Hello. It's a Worm.
And so...
After the Worms are completely annihilated,
all Masked Rider System equipment will be collected.
But if that happens ZECT will...
Of course... we will disband.
This is embarrassing, but...
I think that's the first step to true peace.
By the way, what is this?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I wanted to hurry, so I started behind your back.
Speaking simply, it's a Worm detection device.
When near a Worm, it turns red. Thus notifying you.
This is incredible.
But...
Why now?
Well, if we had completed it sooner...
No. We Native don't have enough power.
But...
I am deeply grateful.
'City Hall'
Wait, everyone!
Please give me one!
One each!
We'll soon run out again.
If we give this to everyone,
people won't be in danger from the Worms.
Man, it's pretty popular.
But... the stock in our areas
are already running out.
Oh no...
Gotta increase the production.
I'm still counting on you.
Okay.
Please get in order.
That's dangerous!
There's still some left!
Get in order!
One each!
I can't give you that much!
Kageyama! It's one each!
Don't be stingy! How many
Worms have I defeated?!
Even this isn't enough to repay me!
Hey!
I want one too.
No. I won't forgive you if you do.
Everyone in school has one. And it's free.
Expensive items don't come free.
Juka, I'll get you a present
that suits you better.
Really?! Lucky!
Hiyori. You're late.
This is... the recipe I wrote before.
Let's make that Chef Hiyori's debut menu.
Now... let's make it right away.
Don't decide that on your own.
Hiyori! Try it! You're finally back after all.
Alright. The debut is in one week.
Okay!
I'm also cheering for you! Good luck, okay?
Now, do it.
Good job, Tendou.
Like I said, don't decide that on your own.
Carrots, and...
Hey! Wait!
Stay away!
Kagami!
Are you okay?
That necklace is working perfectly.
This is thanks to the Natives' cooperation.
Yes?
What?!
What happened?!
I was transporting the necklaces
when I was suddenly attacked.
By whom?
I didn't see.
Didn't see?
Before I realized it, the truck was like this.
Help!
An enemy capable with Clock Up?
Clock Up...
Better and better.
But this isn't good enough. It doesn't surpass me.
Maybe I don't have any skills in cooking.
Minha vó uma vez disse... "Truly delicious food
will change the life of the one who eats it."
I'm sure you will change many people's lives.
You always talk so big.
I'm a big man, it can't be helped.
Now...
Don't give up. Do it again.
Let me do the rest myself.
If I don't... it won't be my cooking.
Properly cook it.
Then... in return... you will be my first customer.
Will a Worm appear?
It happened just three times last night.
I'm sure they'll attack again.
Kagami, are you ready?
Yes.
Now come, Worm!
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Tendou! Why are you...?!
CLOCK OVER
Kagami! Where's the culprit?
Kagami!
The white night?
We know who attacked
the transport. It's Kabuto.
Why Kabuto?!
Seems that's how it is.
Really... I'm stunned.
With this, Kabuto is an enemy to
society, no... an enemy to peace.
Then... he must be executed.
Man... that really is a pity.
By the way...
I received info that the
necklaces are being investigated.
So... do you not trust us?
Of course not. The government forced us to.
I deeply apologize.
No. That's okay, Mr. Kagami.
Mr. Kagami.
I'm sorry.
You have a terrible fever.
It's no big deal. More importantly...
I got one for you too, Bro.
I don't need it.
Bro! Please don't abandon me.
Don't be stupid.
Look.
There is light that we can
grasp too. Come with me.
We seek the sun in the depths of night.
The world of the white night.
Kabuto... has been targeted, to be killed.
Kagami...
Can you do it?
Despite everything, you can't
give Kagami those orders!
I understand.
Your opponent is Tendou!
Can you really do that?
He must be thinking something.
I'm the only one who can get him to speak.
'Nationwide Search For Suspect'
'Attempted murder and
possession of illegal weapons
Tendou... so that's why he didn't come home.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Kagami.
Has Tendou contacted you?
No.
I see. Thanks.
Hey.
What's happened to him?
I don't know about this either.
But I'm sure Tendou has an idea.
I'll show that.
So if Tendou contacts you, let me know.
Okay.
It's Tendou Souji!
He's wanted by the police!
Run!
It's Tendou!
It sure is tough to be popular.
So you're still loitering in this world?
T-there's no need for two of me.
Minha vó uma vez disse... "The sun is wonderful.
It can even make the dirt shine."
The one who will turn to dirt...
...is you!
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Kabuto's appeared.
Master...
Kagami... you're up.
Okay.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Are you okay?
I'm sure everything with Tendou
is just some misunderstanding.
I also think so.
CLOCK OVER
CLOCK UP
Before Clock Over occurs,
I'll pretend to start a Rider Kick.
Then I'll rapidly fire the KunaiGun.
In that time I'll do Put On,
then smash him into the ground.
It's a self sacrifice attack, but I'll have
the advantage in Masked Form.
...is what he's thinking.
That's why I'll let him think I'll fall for it.
ONE TWO THREE
ONE
TWO
PUT ON
Hyper Clock Up!
HYPER CLOCK UP
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
Naive.
What?!
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
Looks like you are not me.
Hey, that's cruel!
Stop it! What are you doing?!
Tendou!
Why are you doing this?!
Because I don't like it.
Tendou!
What?!
That's your only reason?!
For me to see heaven's path...
...don't butt in.
CLOCK UP
A wonderful present just for me.
Right now only I can hear! Tell me!
You have a real reason, right?
I told you. I just don't like them.
I can't accept such a reason!
But that's good enough for me.
CLOCK OVER
Renge!
Tendou, you idiot!
Renge, are you okay?
Tendou!
Master...
Do you know what you've done?!
Tendou!
Say something!
Master...
Renge...
Renge.
Renge!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I want to create a truly peaceful world.
Justice is on our side.
Kabuto... I will defeat you.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.