ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Can I have a moment?
Is your activity approved by headquarters?
The plan to capture Kabuto
is already in progress.
I would you like you to help me with it.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Why are there two of me?!
Fire!
Finish it before it can Clock Up!
Please cancel the attack.
What?
What is the meaning of this?
These are the headquarters' orders.
Please stand down.
That voice... Misaki?
Why are you there?
I'm terribly sorry.
I am working for a different group
so that we can capture Kabuto.
Yo.
Playing hide and seek?
Please do something about Kagami.
He's avoiding work again?
I'm fed up with him.
He's annoying when he's overly zealous,
but he's even more annoying when he's depressed.
Wait! Guest number two!
I'm counting on you.
Wait.
I'll do it, but...
...I have my own favor to ask.
'Japanese Diner'
Sloppy handwriting as always.
Father...
You were a total failure at housework...
...so I can't believe you'd be
working in a restaurant like this.
Are you eating properly?
I am.
If you don't want anything then go away.
I don't know if this is about your freedom...
...but how long do you plan to waste time?
Now that Ryou is gone...
...you, as the eldest brother,
have to take responsibility.
I'm responsible.
What about you Father?
When Ryou disappeared,
you didn't even do anything.
It wasn't that I didn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything.
I know.
You were busy, right?
Or maybe...
If people found out your son had run away
from home, your fine career would be damaged?
Pot-au-feu?
One of Juka's favorites.
Could you go away?
No.
This time I'm stealing the secret of your flavor.
Hiyori.
Could this be a picture of
the Shibuya's meteorite?
I'm sorry for looking without permission.
I just happened to see it since
it was sticking out of the bag.
It doesn't matter.
I was in Shibuya then too.
But Bro saved me.
That time, Big Brother said
"I won't ever let you be scared again."
Are you the same?
You can't forget it either?
I've forgotten it.
It's been seven years after all.
Help me!
I'm down here!
Dad!
Mom!
I sure was stupid.
By then, my parents...
...were already dead.
That's not true.
I'm sure they heard your voice, Hiyori.
Someone please help me!
Are we supposed to just watch?!
Got a problem with it?
Let's wait.
Our prey will fall for it.
A flowers of the world exhibit?
Seems like Hiyori wants to go.
You should take her.
But...
She won't go outside if not for chances like these.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
Let's go together.
Why suddenly ask me?
Come on, let's go!
I'm fine.
You want to go, right?
I want to go, but...
I can't go.
Why's that?!
'Instances of Unknown Serial Murders'
The victim was found with no body fluids
in this series of baffling murders.
The time of crime, method and clues
regarding the culprit are all mysteries.
'No Witnesses'
'Case Leaves Police Baffled'
Worm...
How stupid of me to count on him.
You know the Worm is doing this!
So why are you ignoring it?!
It's headquarters' decision.
I have no choice but to obey.
Tadokoro, are you really okay with that?!
Orders from headquarters are absolute.
Kagami, that guy. I came here to cheer him up too...
He's not even here.
He dashed out after reading that.
What are you drawing?
Nothing.
A one-of-a-kind tulip.
You like tulips?
I wanted to go and draw a picture.
That's all.
Why don't you go?
You sure are annoying.
Flowers don't suit me.
My grandmother once said...
"Flowers can make any girl glow."
I agree.
I hate crowds...
Then why don't I go with you?
I'll be waiting for you under
Tokyo Tower at four o'clock.
If it's not possible then it's not possible.
It'll be okay.
I am...
...by your side.
Man!
What are those bastards
at headquarters thinking?
Ignore the Worm? Bullshit!
I'll never acknowledge it!
Misaki.
Don't act on your own.
What about you, Misaki? Why are you here?
A different team?
Misaki, what's the meaning of this?
Who are they?
It doesn't matter, just go home.
What? You're playing hide and seek too?
Tendou, listen.
Hiyori.
Isn't it almost time?
We'll be fine here.
Go already.
This is the last day of the exhibit.
Right?
But...
That "walking the path of heaven"
guy should be able to keep you safe, Hiyori.
I see.
Seems like ZECT headquarters as an
organization is ignoring the Worm.
Organization?
Don't you think it's odd for Worm incidents to be
appearing in the newspapers in the first place?
Who cares if it's weird or not?!
Can you just stand by as the victims increase?
No.
Better to not interfere.
So you're going to ignore the Worm too?
Because it's obvious they're up to something.
I get it.
I was an idiot to ask you advice.
What a let down.
That guy doesn't get it.
Man...
I can't... after all...
It'll be okay.
I am...
...by your side.
Wh-what?!
What's going on?!
The victims will increase!
It can't be helped!
Cancel the operation!
You have no patience at all.
Something is nearing!
Run!
Kagami!
Him again?!
I think he has some connection with Kabuto.
That might be useful for capturing Kabuto.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Find Kabuto's location!
Okay.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
The Clock Up Rider Form can move at
speeds far greater than any human.
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
Hurry up and come.
Please come...
Tendou!
So you aren't by my side...
Tendou...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Stop this tepid interrogation...
and begin interrogating with more force.
We've already started our next plan.
Looks like the Worm are after ZECT's main body.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.