Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
CHANGE SCORPION
Looks like the match is over.
This is the horn that signals the end of battle.
Jiiya.
You have lost this duel, Young Master.
What?
That's correct.
Look more carefully.
Put On.
PUT ON
Impossible!
No...
My sword was faster.
I'm sure of it.
More importantly... I cannot
forgive you for opposing me.
You are fired!
No! I merely wish for your growth, Young Master!
I am already on top. There is no more growing for me.
Never appear before me again.
P-please! Please! Forgive me!
You don't comprehend his true intentions.
Be quiet! I will settle things with you.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Where are you planning on going?
Leave me alone please.
Don't tell me...
You plan to enter the ruins of Shibuya?
If I go there... things might become clear for me.
Like who the boy who wore that belt was?
No.
I can't let you go to such a dangerous place.
Don't get in my way.
Cool your head!
First of all, Shibuya is closely guarded.
How do you plan to get past?
You... don't understand how I feel.
Hiyori! You're being targeted!
You should hide somewhere safe!
Okay?!
No.
You must not enter Shibuya.
I know!
I know lately Worms have been attacking
people with the Shibuya meteorite.
The key to everything is
in Shibuya. Just what is ZECT—
Enough!
I see.
I've also been removed from
this Worm investigation by Tadokoro.
Why?!
As you say. They're hiding some secret in Shibuya.
But... it's not like you to back off like that.
Shouldn't an idiot act like an idiot?
If I think I'm right, then I should
dash straight forward, right?
I understand.
It's my treat today.
Thanks for the meal!
Sir, this isn't enough!
Unbelievable!
High Class Ramen
Tsurugi
Everyone, look at this wonder!
Here we have a French, Chinese,
Italian, and other famous chefs...
They use caviar and other expensive
items to make super high quaity ramen.
And the price is 300 yen. You just have to try it!
I knew it was you.
You're the owner, aren't you?
Of course.
A statement please.
All I'll say is that I am the man who
will replace the gods with a slash of my sword.
Delicious food must be delicate.
You must use the best
ingredients in a dazzling fashion.
This match...
...accept it.
Okay.
This man has no etiquette.
How amazing. This other ramen
establishment has taken on a tough duel.
Excuse me. Can I get a word?
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"Delicious cooking is alive..."
"...You must be nonchalant about it."
Must be.
Who will win? Is this really a fair duel?
Let's ask a person on the street.
Hello.
Which ramen do you think will win?
Buckwheat soba.
Your son... has become interested in Area X it seems.
Do you know what happens
when there are too many rats?
Huh?
They will...
...throw themselves in the river...
...to stop from dying.
When that happens, the rats are embracing hope.
...as they plunge in.
Even though there...
...is nothing but hell waiting for them.
Ummm... what about your son?
There is a light shining in the future.
If you're going to hell either way...
...you should embrace all your hope.
That is what I wish for.
I apologize deeply for the
trouble Young Master is causing.
Please stop. Here's the money from today's sales.
I'm so sorry.
At Young Master's restaurant, the more
customers that come, the more he goes into debt!
Why does a person like you...?
Let's settle things tomorrow.
Please forgive me.
What?
I'm going to Shibuya after this.
The Worms and the Masked Rider Project...
I think the answer to everything is in Shibuya.
You can't. You must never go there.
You're saying that too? Why?!
So it seems...
...you really did kill Hiyori's parents?
Don't kill!
Alright!
You killed my parents!
I'll say it one more time.
Don't go to Shibuya...
...If you care for Hiyori.
No.
She's suffering because she can't clearly
remember what happened seven years ago.
She can't be happy unless she
knows the truth and gets past it.
If you insist on going...
...then I will have no choice but to take you down.
What?!
Do you think you can defeat me that easily?
If you want Hiyori to be happy...
Do as I say!
How meddling can this guy be?
Hiyori.
You here?
She... couldn't have gone to Shibuya?!
This is Hiyori?
So, that means these people are...
This stone...
It's the stone Hiyori has.
But, why is this stone here
before the Shibuya meteorite fell?
And now, bring the newly created La Men.
Okay!
Thank you for waiting!
No good. Next.
Bon appetit.
Please try this.
No good!
Next.
Here you go.
Terrible!
Next.
Please enjoy your meal.
What is this thin looking La Men?
Delicious!
The flavors move so easily.
Such a noble flavor.
Why...?!
You... made this?
No.
This man did.
Jiiya.
I couldn't create such flavor.
Do you know why?
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"No matter what condiment,
no matter what ingredient..."
"...there is something greater."
"And that's the love of the
person creating the food"
I suppose...
Jiiya's cooking truly is the best.
Y-Young Master.
Wait.
I have... lost this duel.
So you acknowledge your defeat?
I did not lose the duel.
I lost to your noblesse oblige.
Right, Jiiya?
Well said.
Young Master!
Hey, Miss.
You shouldn't go in there.
If you go, you won't return alive.
Hiyori, wait!
Please leave me alone.
This problem is mine alone.
You don't know what's up ahead!
You don't know if it will benefit you, Hiyori.
Do you still want to go?
I understand.
Then I'm going too.
I'm going alone.
You're not alone.
I'm by your side.
It's okay.
Wait.
You cannot go any further. Orders from above.
What's up ahead?
I wouldn't know.
I have no reason to know!
HENSHIN
Hide over there!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
You bastard!
Stop it!
Stop!
Be good!
Hiyori!
Stop it!
That's...
That guy...
Let's go.
Hey!
You...
Tendou. Why are you...?
I hope you're satisfied by coming here.
No matter what is in here.
Hide.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
There's no end to them.
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Rider Kick!
CLOCK OVER
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
You bastards will go no further!
Jiiya once said...
"A noble deed must be nobly returned."
That is my...
Noblesse oblige.
STANDBY
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Don't get in my way!
Leave him to be. You all go!
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
This is...
Why in a place like this...
...is there a door?
Let's open it and see.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Experiment? For what?
For example... the Masked Rider Project?
Start talking!
Tell me everything about
the Masked Rider Project!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.
The original Rider's enemy were
Shocker, Gel Shocker and Destron.
And this is King Dark, who was fought by X Rider.
I guess Riders are destined
to fight an organization.
If you fight ZECT...
...than we will show no mercy.
Neo-ZECT, revolting and
disassociating from ZECT...
I will definitely crush them.
Well said, Yamato.
ZECT'S demon.
My ZECT...