Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
A one-of-a-kind tulip...
Everyone...
Watch out from every direction.
Get back!
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Who are they?
Headquarters' personal elite team, Shadow.
And that's the new Rider, TheBee.
TheBee...
Platoon A, use explosive bullets
and take them head-on.
Platoons B and C, surround them
and build a path to retreat.
They're molting.
Flash bomb!
That was amazing...
Yaguruma!
So, it's you?
Long time no see.
Tadokoro.
You're the most elite in Shadow.
I thought you'd be the most suitable for TheBee.
A word of warning.
I acknowledge your courage
for facing the Worms alone...
...but no more grandstanding, okay?
But that time...
The most important thing in battle...
...is something called "Perfect Harmony".
Perfect Harmony...?
Grandstanding disturbs the harmony of the team.
If victory for the team is lost...
...then it's not a real victory.
Okay!
Goodbye.
Wait...
I want to defeat more of the Worms.
What should I do?
You bastard!
Don't talk so casually to him!
There has to be some pattern to the Worm's actions.
If you know that, you can
predict the Worm's actions.
Okay!
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Okay.
That was delicious!
As always... good!
What would you like for dinner?
Well...
Boiled tofu!
Sounds like the cravings of an old man.
The most important thing
is to have delicious tofu.
Really?
Well, at least we should have cold tofu.
Now that makes you sound like an old man.
But... I'll look forward to it!
Okay. I'm off!
Have a good day.
For TheBee to enter so early...
...is there a change in the Masked Rider Project?
There is no change in our plan.
Then...
What is TheBee's goal?
As you know...
I do not take questions.
But TheBee... has an important mission.
Silk strained tofu.
Sorry! But I only have one left.
I want to treat my precious subordinates.
My cute little sister is looking forward to it.
Since it's for important people in both our lives...
We should split it evenly.
My grandmother once said...
"Chase two birds, and you catch two birds."
What an interesting thing to say!
Who are you?
He who walks the path of heaven...
...will rule over everything.
Do you have a container large
enough to be talking about heaven?
I have a container.
And compared to yours...
...it's bigger.
Bigger!
If you're going to take it that far, then it's a duel.
So...
It's a cooking contest?
And you're using my kitchen?
I apologize for the intrusion.
The theme is tofu cooking.
And the judge is Hiyori.
Why me?
Of course you.
We're using your tofu after all.
That was bought by some guy,
so that I can train to become a chef.
Impressive, Hiyori. Such quality tofu.
Please, look forward to it.
Then...
Shall we begin?
You may now kiss the bride.
I wonder if I can get one of them to work here?
If you do that...
Kagami would be fired, right?
There sure has been a lot
of incidents in Area B4 lately.
Wash away the past cases...
We've got to figure out which
crimes are committed by the Worm.
If we can figure out the Worm's
pattern of action as Yaguruma says...
We can get there before the
Worm commits the crime.
Maybe if I get some advice from Tendou...
Now that TheBee has been found,
we should keep him out of this now.
What's wrong?
You should go.
It's time for your part-time job.
Okay.
Chinese style cold tofu.
Mine is mabou tofu.
Hiyori, what do you think?
The most important thing in cooking...
...is Perfect Harmony.
A perfect connection.
Let me see.
Perfect Harmony?
I see.
Is that why you didn't bring out
the individual flavors of the vegetables?
Being a sore loser?
Good morning!
I've won the match.
As I said earlier...
Let's split it up evenly.
I already said...
The one who chases after
two birds, gets both birds.
Do not forget what that means.
If you're going to go that far...
...then I'm taking it.
Wait a minute!
Yaguruma!
As you said Yaguruma, we're
investigating the Worm's pattern of activity.
I see.
The work of my action team
depends on your investigation.
Please do your best.
Okay!
Yes, Kagami here.
We know the Worms' pattern of
conduct that Yaguruma mentioned.
I'll be right there.
That's right.
We have Yaguruma.
A Worm?
Tendou.
I have to talk to you.
Tendou's is delicious.
I...
...like hot things....
That's why you chose the mabou tofu?
Because...
...hot...
The second rider?
TheBee?
Yeah.
ZECT has finally found a qualified Rider.
I look forward to that.
Tendou...
You should avoid the Worms from now on.
We have TheBee, it's okay now.
You have Juka also...
There's no reason for a civilian like
you to endanger yourself in battle.
And who's the man who chose this TheBee?
That's the ZECT Secret Committee.
Is it that neutrality and harmony guy?
Cut that out...
The one they picked this time is a man I respect.
Anyway, you should just stay away.
Understand?
An interesting fellow as always.
Why did I get stuck with you?
Well, what can I do?
We know the Worms are targeting Area B4.
So, we have to act as bait.
You two are a good match for each other.
Tendou.
Why are you here?
But...
Would the Worms really pinpoint an area like this?
What do you mean?
Leave the rest to me.
Give my regards to that guy.
What are you talking about?! Wait!
That guy?
This is Yaguruma. The Worms
have appeared. Get over here!
Okay. I'll come right away.
Yaguruma!
That was close.
It's okay, so please calm down.
It's okay.
It's okay now. It's okay.
So, the Worms are targeting
only brides and grooms...
...is wrong.
The pattern has to be more simple...
It's okay...
Please relax.
I see.
The Worms are targeting white clothes!
I knew it.
You only target those that wear white clothes.
What twisted tastes you have.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
What's going on?
Hurry and guard people wearing white!
I'll search for the fleeing Worm.
No.
Shadow is already on the way.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Platoon B, Platoon C, provide
back up from a distance.
Platoon A, use blades for close combat.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Kabuto, Clock up and move the Worms.
Very well.
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
We fight the Worms for peace, on humanity's behalf.
We want you to work with us.
Is that the "Perfect Harmony" you speak of?
I told you before.
I walk the path of heaven.
So, it is you.
Kabuto's true identity.
More importantly, one of them got away.
Defeating him is the priority.
That trick won't work.
If you plan to defy the organization...
...we have but one choice.
What are you trying to do?
Defeating Kabuto...
...is my mission.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
With Yaguruma here, you're no longer needed.
Looks like the case isn't over yet.
Seemed... really bad.
Must we do this?
There is no need for two Riders.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.