You...
So it's you?
Very well.
STANDBY
I'll save you, so hurry and run.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
CHANGE SCORPION
All Worms are my prey!
Do not interfere! There is no place for you!
You're...
A member of ZECT?
No!
I act of my own will!
Cool your head.
My grandmother once said...
"Men must be cool. Boiling water is but vapor."
Jiiya once said...
"All men are fiery."
"If a spark isn't lit early,
they'll never rise to be a firework."
At any rate, don't get in my way.
I will destroy all the Worms.
That is my duty.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
We did it, Misaki!
'The Phantom Thief Shadow strikes again!
This time it was a national museum.'
I'll also do my best...
...as a member of the Phantom Thief Shadow.
So, you finally got employed too?
In the Phantom Thief Shadow?
What? What are you talking about?
It's okay.
He's one of us.
One of us?
We asked Tendou if he could be our bodyguard.
It's only natural.
That... is understandable...
Young Master.
Hey, Jiiya.
What's today's schedule?
Oh, yes.
Today in the afternoon, there is a history lecture,
archery training, and a piano lesson.
Hey, Jiiya, you're picking the best tutors, right?
Only those truly who are capable
are worthy of teaching me.
Well... if such people exist, of course.
I will keep that in mind.
Please.
Jiiya.
What's this?
It's rose tea.
Did you forget?
I...
...hate roses.
Sis! Where are you going?
Mika!
Mika...
I will avenge you...
I swear to it!
Someone!
I'm glad you came Kagami.
I already know.
Seems that the Worm has reappeared.
This is the sixth victim.
Yeah.
It's all very strange.
The victims are all thugs.
It only targets those that
are headed for prison.
But... my questions for you have
nothing to do with the Worms.
It's about Misaki.
Misaki... what about her?
I've received information that
she is the Phantom Thief Shadow.
Do you know anything about that?
Misaki would never do such a thing.
This would usually be police business....
But if there's a criminal in ZECT,
then I cannot ignore it.
Worst of all...
...I will not forgive anyone
who uses the name Shadow.
Don't you think so?
Of course! It's unforgivable.
How could they use the name Shadow...
Okay then.
I'll know the truth eventually.
That's far enough, Phantom Thief Shadow!
Hurry!
This way.
Where is he?!
Follow him!
Go!
I thought I was dead.
Looks like it doesn't suit you.
Do you know of the Phantom Thief Shadow?
They're becoming quite the talk of the town.
This is secret....
I have received information
that the thief is one of ours.
Quite a surprise.
While keeping it secret from ZECT...
...they get around the police.
If this information is true...
Then they are deserving of some scolding.
Earthy desires...
...I guess?
Looks like the lion has shown it's true nature.
But what a surprise.
Young Master... isn't it archery training time?
No.
That coach isn't worthy of teaching me.
I had him go home.
I understand.
Next time we'll have a more talented person.
So I, Jiiya, will go shopping now.
Hey, Jiiya. I'll go today.
It'll help me kill some time.
Preposterous!
Young Master, you're a descendant of the famous
English family Descabil, I cannot let you go shopping!
I will not allow it!
It's okay. You're such a worrywart, Jiiya.
I was able to go shopping when I was born.
I will stand at the top of shopping too.
Three of them.
H-hey you!
Get in line!
I am the man who will
stand at the top of everything.
I would never take orders from people like you.
Hey.
Give me the best meat in this shop.
All my meat is good.
Then I'll take all of it.
Since it's an inconvenience, deliver it for me.
All of it?!
Yes.
Hey!
Please.
Please forgive him.
Hey, Hiroko.
Big brother!
Want a ride?
Yeah.
Juka, we can give you a ride too.
Really?!
Yeah.
Alright. Lucky!
Hey you!
You!
Stop, you!
Stop!
What?
I'm home.
Hold it right there, Juka!
Come here!
Where did that wound come from?
Oh, this?
I kind of got hurt. But I'm fine, so no need to worry!
Juka.
Tell me the details.
Hey, because of you a big accident occurred.
Do you understand that?
I will walk where I want.
The car should have just gone on ahead.
Hey, you!
I am the one who will replace the
gods with a slash of my sword.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Please.
Please! Forgive him!
Please forgive him.
Young Master!
Hey, Jiiya.
I'm sorry.
Looks like I caused some trouble.
Please do not worry about it.
Okay, please go ahead.
By the way, after you went
out shopping, this arrived for you.
I'm coming for the "Praying
Mother and Child" statue
-Phantom Thief Shadow
It's the Phantom Thief Shadow's advance notice.
Shadow?
The guy that's been appearing lately?
Yes.
It was delivered to the police.
You!
What do you want?!
Young Master!
What are you doing?!
Only natural that you receive your retribution.
Because of the accident you created...
...my little sister was hurt!
You...
...have a sibling?
I see...
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Please tell that to your little sister.
As long as you understand.
Then that's good enough.
You're a friend of Tendou Souji, right?
I never would have imagined
you as a member of ZECT.
You know about ZECT?
There is nothing I do not know.
But... isn't it the police's job to
catch the Phantom Thief Shadow?
This is a special mission.
You can go home at any time.
I sent all the cops home too.
I will catch the Phantom Thief
Shadow with my own hands.
I can't allow that.
My job is my life.
So...
Where's the artwork mentioned
in the advance notice?
A heirloom passed down in my family.
What a conspicuous location!
There's no need to hide it.
I'm protecting it after all.
Misaki, Misaki!
The item is on the lounge table.
Roger.
Just a minute.
What?
I cannot allow you to face this opponent alone.
I'll help too.
Young Master. A new piano teacher has come,
on such a day, shall I send him away?
It doesn't matter.
Let him in.
You're a piano teacher?
I'll teach you.
You should be grateful.
Excuse me.
Can I have a cup of tea?
Yes, right away.
Misaki?! I knew it!
Why are you doing this?
No! This is...
...a plan to lure him out!
This Worm only targets criminals.
That's why we put up this act.
As the Phantom Thief Shadow!
Hurry up and transform!
Fight him!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
You sure gave us a lot of trouble.
This time you're not getting away.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
STANDBY
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Rider Slash!
RIDER SLASH
Clock Up!
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
I told you before.
Do not meddle with the Worms.
They are all my prey.
I don't remember saying I would do what you said.
Then... die!
What's wrong?
I can feel it...
It's his power...
He's here...
He is...
Where?!
Where is he?
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
An experiment for becoming the new Rider... Gatack.
Now come... Gatack Zecter!
It's a promise!
There's someone waiting for me to save him.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.