HYPER STING
Can I put this up here?
Do you know who she is?!
She's a Worm!
Worm?
Hiyori!
You're...
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Hiyori!
ONE
TWO
THREE
RIDER KICK
Tendou!
What is it? What exactly happened?
I saw Hiyori.
What?
Hiyori...
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
I... I...
Reina... Please pull yourself together.
Reina!
Hey... Tell me.
What is a Worm?
Am I like that monster just now?
You are not a Worm.
You are... you.
Kamen Rider Drake. Kazama Daisuke?
I envy you.
Make up artist. How fashionable.
Who are you guys?
But what a surprise.
I can't believe Mamiya Reina
returned to being human.
That makes her easy to kill.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
CHANGE PUNCH HOPPER
Underhanded scum.
TRANSFORM
You guys have no right to approach Reina!
Were you laughing too?
Laughing like you ate poisonous mushrooms?
Reina!
Stop it.
Please.
This woman...
I see darkness in her eyes.
Did she see the same hell as me?
Bro!
What is it?!
Hurry up and run, Daisuke!
Nice, Gon!
Now. Here's our chance.
Are you hurt, Reina?
Let go.
Why didn't you finish her off?
Don't tell me... you have a
crush on Mamiya Reina?
It can't be.
We live in the darkness, right?
Yeah.
I know.
What is the meaning of this? Why?
A mimic version of me is with Hiyori.
There is too much that I do not know.
I guess you're worried about Hiyori.
If only there was a good way...
More importantly.
Aren't you troubled by something?
It's written on your face.
Of course not.
We're going out!
No... Mine isn't that important.
Congratulations!
Kagamin! Misakinu!
You!
What... What's with that outfit?!
I'm a Cupid of love.
I'm sorry for causing problems the other day.
But...
Kagamin and Misakinu are both important to me.
I give you both a blessing from my heart.
I'm cheering for you.
You two are going out?!
I had no idea! You're a good fit!
Hey! How rude! Why compare me with Kagami?!
What is it?!
Don't tell me you've fought?
No no no! We're super love love.
Right?
Right!
There's something on you.
Good.
Umm... I'm sorry.
I don't remember anything.
Could it be... that I hurt you, Kazama?
No... it's not your fault.
You're lying!
It's my fault, right?
I am hurt, Kazama.
Please sing your song.
I want to hear it.
Your song.
I can't. Not right now.
Then at least let me hear...
...why you want to be a singer?
When I was a child...
When you were a child?
I was always afraid of people.
I wasn't able to talk to others.
I wanted to cure myself of that.
But... when I began singing I met so many people.
At last, I thought people were okay.
That's when I first had my dream.
I wanted to express my feeling in song.
The next time I lose myself...
...tell the other me...
"Open your ears to the voice in your heart."
If so, I'm sure...
...that she would hear my song.
You can do it, Hiyori.
Hiyori?
Food.
You can do it, Hiyori.
I... wasn't able to always be by your side.
I'm sorry.
Well done, Reina.
Perfected in such a short period of time.
You're singing in tomorrow's performance.
Okay! Thank you!
I'll work hard.
I'm counting on you.
Never interfere with that woman again?
You came all this way to tell me that?
Yeah.
I'm serious.
Do you have a crush on her?
What a foolish man. You're dealing with a Worm.
Someone important to me is a Worm.
That's all.
How can you understand how I feel?!
I understand.
I also know.
Ah. Kazama.
Then you're appearing in
the upcoming performance?
Yeah. Definitely come.
Yes. I absolutely will.
You're...?
Those ruled by a human heart must be executed.
Please run. I will protect you.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
'Red Group's New Member Performance'
'Red Group Mamiya Reina'
Kamura.
Stop it! What are you doing?!
I can't forgive you!
Why were you chosen?
I also did my best to practice!
Unforgivable!
Why?!
Stop it!
Run! You can't be near me! Hurry!
Hurry up and run!
Reina!
Stay away!
I...
You are... the Worm?
Why?
How could something as
trivial as a human heart revive?
Reina said...
"You should open the ears of your heart."
If you do that, you will hear a song.
One that would make you think people are great.
Reina's song.
What rubbish. Humans care about
nothing but their petty greed.
An existence that's all about taking.
Get lost.
I will protect this person.
You can do it, Reina! You mustn't lose!
I'm by your side!
I'll always be by your side!
Welcome back, Bro.
Good to be back.
Make Up.
With this make up, you'll shine even on stage.
Thank you.
But...
I'm sure I won't make it.
I know.
I will lose myself very soon.
I'll never come back.
No...
Make a promise to me, Kazama.
When that happens... it will be by your hands...
...that I...
What are you saying?!
I can't make such a promise!
Reina!
Reina...
If your heart is disappearing...
Then I will give you a full heart.
Softly... softly...
Think of Reina! Give Reina back!
Bit by bit...
It's no use.
That woman's mind is completely sealed away.
No!
The flower of tomorrow blooms.
Then why did you continue singing?
Even though you reverted to
a Worm halfway through?!
Don't do anything barbaric.
You have no place in this.
TRANSFORM
Please... come back.
Reina!
I said it's no use!
Fight, Kazama Daisuke!
Daisuke!
Gon!
TRANSFORM
Run, Gon!
Rider Shooting.
RIDER SHOOTING
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
SASWORD POWER
HYPER SLASH
Time does not wait.
It move forward.
Sad times do not stop.
Rider Shooting.
RIDER SHOOTING
If you are to make a mark in the passing days...
Then smile...
And feel joy.
I will protect you.
How strange...
Why?
Am I?
This world...
It continues on eternally...
Reina.
Happiness...
I love you. I really do.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
ZECT members. This time you've created
a lousy Anti-Mimic Bomb, it seems?
Humanity made a deal with the Natives.
So even the Riders belong to the Natives?
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.