To all citizens.
The Worms will soon be eradicated.
Please cooperate by wearing the necklaces.
Humans that don't wear necklaces might be Worms.
Stop. You're not wearing a necklace.
If you see anyone like that, please contact ZECT.
Sir, here.
"If anything happens to me, give this to Kagami."
'Heaven'
Tendou...
"Their goal is to turn humans into Natives."
"But they can't wait for the necklaces to transform all of humanity."
"The necklaces are nothing more than antennae."
"If a shock is applied to those antennae..."
"...all of humanity will simultaneously
be turned into Natives."
"They must have a transmission
site for such a purpose."
Transmission site?
...will broadcast to the whole world.
That's it?!
Father... I'm going.
Renge, take care of my father.
I can't let you through here.
There are orders to arrest you and your father.
I am going to stop Negishi's plan.
And you have a reason for having to go?
Yes.
So you're saying that you'll
run straight forward?
Yes.
Okay then.
You guys!
Try laying a finger on my subordinate.
...because you won't be getting away with it.
Kagami, go!
Okay!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
How are preparations going?
Right on schedule.
The necklaces will have been distributed to the
whole world by 3:00 this afternoon, right?
And then the humans will simultaneously be
transformed into Natives, and true peace will come.
Today is truly a blessed day.
Hiyori, at last...
Here! A present from me.
Thank you so much!
I'll do my best!
Five minutes until the transmission commences.
These foolish human's history will end.
We will forge a new history.
Stop!
So you weren't going to help me?
I won't let you have your way with this world!
Move!
I've always hated you.
Straight forward guys like you!
Everyone, did you forget that you're human?!
Please remember when you fought with me!
Please open your eyes!
Remember! Please open your eyes!
Move!
The God of Battle...
...should die in battle!
Not yet...
I won't stand losing!
It's time.
Commence the broadcast.
To all humans, I am truly sorry.
We have foreseen the fight
between humans and Natives.
It's true that the Worms are invaders, however...
Humans had no intention
with coexisting with them.
Humans are destined to battle.
Humans continue to fight even when
it consumes countries and people.
They cannot coexist with us Native.
That's why we... will turn all
of humanity into Natives.
That is true peace.
Foolish humans are no longer needed.
Shut up...
Humans...
...have amazing guys like Tendou...
Humans won't lose to the Natives...
He always said this to me...
Even if the world became his enemies...
...he, all alone... didn't give up even in the end.
Stubborn fool.
Tendou no longer exists.
My grandmother once said...
"In this world there is only
one name that you must know".
My grandmother once said... "There is only one
name in this world that you must remember."
He who walks the path of heaven...
...will rule over everything.
Tendou... Souji.
I am the world.
As long as the world exists...
...so will I!
A single flower for a man that destroys dreams.
You should rise to heaven with that flower.
You foolish humans cannot change yourselves!
That's where you're wrong.
Humans can change!
So humans belong to the Natives?
All life in this world...
All life is lovely.
You changed humans into your servants.
You don't change the world for your own sake.
If you change yourself... the world will change!
That is the path of heaven!
First of all...
Humans and... Natives...
...a world where we live together...
...a world without conflict...
...we will grab a hold of
that with our own hands.
But that world is not needed.
Because humans are not needed!
That was your limitation to begin with.
Get him!
What is it?! He told you to get him!
You... you've lost your Native heart?!
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Kabuto!
Follow him!
Stop!
Tendou...
Tendou!
TRANSFORM
Hang on!
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
Victory is mine!
Go!
All right!
Rider Kick!
Hey!
Wake up!
Tendou, it's going to blow! Let's run!
Hey!
Kabuto!
Take care of this world!
Our world!
We did it.
I'll only tell you this once.
Those walking the same path
don't merely pass as comrades.
But those who walk different paths,
and arrive together at the end are...
...friends.
Are those your grandmother's words?
No.
They're my words.
Kagami!
Master!
Hey!
Renge!
It looks delicious!
Then I'm going to put this out
'Hiyorimi Lunch - Now Available'
It's thanks to you that this was completed.
One Year Later
Okay.
Hey!
Tadokoro!
Hey. Running a soba shop sure is hard.
Hey, what's with that getup?
Hey, Tadokoro. Ms. Misaki
has become a president.
President?
Yes.
Discabil Corporation?
What kind of business is this?
A restaurant line. The concept uses
Tsurugi's will and Jiiya's flavor.
To revive the Discabil family,
everyone please come eat there.
I'm going!
Hello.
Oh, long time no see!
Lovely!
Hello!
Oh, hello!
Beautiful as always...
Still?
Like a...
Umm...
...like Yuriko.
"Yes yes, that that"...
I would say, but isn't that your real name?
Well I know what my real name is now.
Right right.
It sure is peaceful. Peace is good.
Alright, I'm going to make soba!
When not by your side, they're even closer.
Right, Sis?
Hiyori.
There's an order for a Hiyorimi lunch.
Alright.
Thanks for waiting.
Thanks for waiting!
Here you go.
Eat it up.
Is it good?
It's good.
We're waiting, Kagami!
It's Mr. Kagami.
Kagami!
Bye bye!
Bye bye.
Be careful, okay?
Hey, where did that "Walking
the path of heaven" guy go?
Right now he's gone to buy tofu.
Oh, if I'm not mistaken, you are...?
My grandmother once said...
I walk the path of heaven.
I am the man who will rule over everything.
I am Tendou Souji.