Please die.
If I don't kill you... Gon will be in danger!
So that's how it is.
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Shooting.
RIDER SHOOTING
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Damn!
Gon...
"Gon"? You mean the girl
that's always with Kazama Daisuke?
You're saying that girl was kidnapped by ZECT?
Yes, I'm almost certain.
What do you mean?!
Gon was kidnapped?!
Is that true?
Yeah.
No...
It's my fault...
I...
No!
It had nothing to do with you.
Don't kill! Don't kill!
Where is Gon?!
We've got to hurry and save her.
Yeah, I know.
Gon is the same... as me....
Daisuke. Please hurry and save me.
I don't like this place.
Yeah, I know.
I'll definitely save you.
I'm sorry, Daisuke.
I'm always so selfish...
I keep getting in your way.
I lost my memory, so I didn't know what to do.
Then you bought me a strawberry milk.
The only person to help me
in that time was you, Daisuke.
I'll buy you all the strawberry milk you want.
Because to me you are my only...
Only...
...partner?
Yes yes. That that.
That's enough.
Time's up.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
It looks delicious!
I'm so glad that I was born in Japan.
This miso soup is great!
Yeah. But it seems in this world
there are even better miso soups.
As unbelievable as that is.
I've had more delicious miso soup before, I think...
That was so good.
My tummy's so full!
Yo. It's you?
I understand your desire
to kill me for Gon's sake....
It seems like your a better man than I thought.
But...
...you're not very smart.
What?!
If you want to save Gon... there are other ways.
Shut up!
This will all end if I kill you.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Henshin.
What's the meaning of this?
The agreement was that I'd kill
Kabuto, then you'd let Gon free.
I don't remember making any agreement like that.
As long as Drake chooses you...
...you will have to work for ZECT.
You bastard!
Stop it, Daisuke!
That's enough. It's enough.
Gon...
It's my fault. It's all... my fault.
No!
It's my fault!
Because...
Because I let go of your hand!
Let me say, as one with medical training...
Someday, she might remember her whole past...
But...
Instead she might forget everything
she's done since she lost her memory.
No way!
I will never, ever forget you. Daisuke.
There's someone in ZECT who kidnapped a girl.
What's going on? Tadokoro.
No matter what ZECT does....
I'm sure there's a hidden meaning behind it.
That's all I can say.
So you accept that?!
Can I ask one thing?
If that's true... where do
you think the girl is right now?
Tadokoro!
You guys seem tired.
You should take a break.
ZECT should have a good rest home in Izu.
I heard the view is good too.
A rest home in Izu?
Let's go, Kagami.
To take a break?
Idiot...
Thank you very much, Tadokoro.
Hey.
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry.
What's wrong Kazama?
You seem down today.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
I don't know what happened, but...
Here, drink.
Cheer up. Here, cheers.
I'm a failure...
I couldn't protect a single girl.
I really am scum.
Me too.
I'm scum.
I couldn't protect the most important thing to me...
Hey, you two.
Don't you think you guys have had too much to drink?
Here. It'll wake you up.
Miso soup.
Gon.
You!
You're alive?!
Quit it.
We're going to save her...
Save Gon.
I'm also... going.
Oh, excuse me.
It's almost afternoon, we've got to hurry.
Wait a moment.
What?
I'm not fond of a plan where
we put sleeping drugs in food.
Why?
Food must be cherished.
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"During meals an angel descends..."
"...for it is a sacred time."
What are you babbling about?!
Saving Gon is the priority!
I understand though...
So, what'll we do?
Alright.
Leave it to me.
Hiyori, please help.
Today's lunch is the best so far.
And free refills.
Hey! Seconds on the mackerel miso.
Hurry hurry.
Okay!
Here too please.
Okay.
Look.
Everyone's forgotten their work.
Here's your chance to save Gon.
I'm going too.
Daisuke!
Gon!
Thank you very much.
Thanks to you all, I was saved.
That's not so...
We're just glad you're back.
Right?
I'm sorry that you had to go through that.
But...
I don't understand... why were they after Gon?
Will they attack Gon again?
That's possible.
But no matter who they are, they'll leave
her alone if she returns to her normal life.
So she has to retrieve her whole memory.
Please drink these.
What is this?
Gon said she has tasted
better miso soup than mine.
That might be the key to
retrieving Gon's memories.
Nope.
This isn't it.
Completely off.
Not this one either.
No good...
I'm sorry.
The one I remember had a more refreshing flavor.
Come to think about it...
The miso soup I drank yesterday
had a refreshing flavor like the wind.
Where is this miso soup?! Tell me!
This is...
This is it, this is the flavor.
I see.
They used a tomato.
How did you learn about this miso soup?
A customer that always comes taught it to me.
You know. The magazine writer
that you were with last night.
Could it be...
The one most important to me...
...I couldn't protect her...
It can't be...
My... mom?
Yeah. I found out.
It seems your mother has been
looking for you all this time.
My... mother...
She'll be here soon.
No! I don't want to go!
I want to always be by your side, Daisuke!
Yuriko!
Yuriko...
Time to go.
Come on.
No, no! I want to stay by Daisuke!
Yuriko!
HENSHIN
Hurry and get out of here!
Damn traitor.
I'll eliminate you!
HENSHIN
It's okay. Mom is with you.
I'll never let go again.
Don't kill. Don't kill. Don't kill.
It's okay. Mom is with you.
Mom...
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE DRAGONFLY
Rider Shooting.
RIDER SHOOTING
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"Children are treasures."
"The greatest sin in this world..."
"...is to damage those treasures."
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Kabuto!
RIDER SHOOTING
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Mom!
Man... Yuriko, you bought both of them.
Well, it was cute.
But you know, both of them look good on you.
So... that pink one piece
suits you, shall we buy that?
Maybe we should get a water colored one.
Gon.
Gon...
Mom... who is that person?
Yuriko...
That person is...
I'm sorry, Miss.
You were so cute...
...I called out to you without thinking.
Your cuteness is...
Truly a...
A...
Ummm...
Nevermind...
Excuse me.
You've remembered everything haven't you, Gon?
And so I guess... that means you've forgotten me.
I'm happy for you.
This is... for the best.
Yuriko.
Goodbye, Gon.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
My name is Kamishiro Tsurugi.
Just as that name states, I am the man who
will replace the gods with a slash of my sword.
The man who will stand at the top of everything.
Henshin!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.