Perfect.
Good morning, Young Master.
Morning.
The main course is red tonguesole.
It's a full course.
Excellent work, Jiiya.
Thank you very much.
Young Master, remember your ancestors
started England's famous Discabil family.
So that you do not forget that brilliance,
we must be more extravagant.
Yes, I understand.
I plan to stand at the summit in all fields so
that I do not disgrace my noble family.
No... I'm already on top.
Let's eat!
Delicious!
This kind of breakfast goes down so smoothly.
This is so good!
You'll be late.
Oh no!
I'm off!
Later.
I'll go get you a new fork.
Good, but throw that one away.
Throw away?
This fork has been passed down from
the pure blood of the Discabil family.
Meaningless.
I cannot forgive a lowly fork for leaving my hand.
Discard it.
Yes. As you command.
Excuse me, sir.
Hello?
This is Kamishiro's...
Yes.
Young Master.
Pardon me for bothering
you while you are eating...
But you're needed elsewhere.
Hey, you in the car! Stop!
Stop!
You were speeding. Your license?
And you.
Even if it's a short drive, you should
always wear your seat belt.
Do you know who you are addressing?
My name is Kamishiro Tsurugi.
Just as that name states, I am the man who
will replace the gods with a slash of my sword.
The man who will stand at the top of everything.
What are you talking about?
Do you not understand?
There isn't a single law that affects me.
Worm.
I am grateful.
My job will be done much quicker.
STANDBY
Henshin!
HENSHIN
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Excellent work.
Young Master.
Misaki, do you ever have feelings of
doubt or rebellion against ZECT?
Well, it's not that I haven't, but...
...it's okay as it is.
ZECT isn't my whole life after all.
What do you mean it isn't everything?
You have some kind of daily life?
Yeah, I suppose.
That's a secret.
When I think about it,
you sure are mysterious, Misaki.
There are times when I have
no idea what you're thinking.
I can't imagine what your
private life is like either.
Yes.
I'm a mysterious woman after all.
'3,600,000 yen'
Good work.
The agreed payment for the three Worms.
This is correct.
Thank you very much.
Jiiya.
If the business is done, then let's go.
Wait.
Your next job.
There are Riders who will not ally with ZECT.
Eliminate them.
Watch your tone.
I am not your subordinate.
I am paid to eliminate Worms.
That was our deal.
Do not ask anything more of me.
In return... I will defeat all the Worms.
I will definitely do it.
Join a soccer match?!
Yeah. Seems the town soccer
team has some open spots.
They're looking for someone.
But soccer...?
I don't have any confidence in that...
How about you, Tendou?
Okay.
I'm always obliged to you, Ms. Yumiko.
But I have a condition.
Condition?
Yes.
Let me do the match by myself.
What are you talking about?
Soccer teams are made of eleven people. Eleven!
You didn't know that?
I'll be more than fine by myself.
I don't need anyone else getting in my way.
'Grand Soccer Tournament'
Will he really be okay by himself?
Don't know.
What is this?
Where is the rest of your team?
Don't worry about it.
Shall we begin?
You're serious?
You'll see when we start.
I'm plenty by myself.
Interesting.
You guys, go back.
Then I'll do it by myself too.
You're serious?
Yeah.
You'll see when we start.
You'll see my power.
Those two are pretty alike.
So those two are the "high and mighty" type?
How tiring.
Wow...
So the match is over?
Zero to Zero. A tie.
I am the man who will stand at the top of everything.
I cannot let this end in a tie.
That's my line.
Let's finish this.
No mercy, eh?
Hey... how about giving it a rest?
Just leave it as a tie for today.
It's night already.
It can't be helped.
Okay.
Will you tell me your name?
Tendou Souji.
The man who walks the path of heaven,
and will rule over everything.
You?
Kamishiro Tsurugi.
The man who will replace the
gods with a slash of my sword.
One more game...
...you in?
Okay.
'Crystal Jewelries'
Don't move.
That's far enough, Phantom Thief Shadow!
Listen.
Now just convert it into a graph.
Oh, I see. You're so smart, Big Brother.
By the way, Big Bro, you know
about the Phantom Thief Shadow?
They took a lot of valuables today didn't they?
It seems they grabbed a lot of jewels.
Before they steal they always
send an advanced note.
That's kind of cool.
Even if it's cool, they're just a thief.
Didn't our grandmother once say?
"People who steal things,
lose something even more precious."
Don't be interested in such things,
and focus on your homework.
Okay!
Mika...
Mika!
Young Master!
Master!
Jii..
Jiiya...
Was it that dream again?
Here.
Hey, Jiiya.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Can you... stay by my side, till I fall asleep?
Stop!
Young Master.
What are you doing, Kagami?
Doing checks for Worms.
You know.
Lately a strange Worm has been appearing.
I thought there'd be something on
the city crime prevention videos.
I see. Then I'll help too.
Ummm...
What happened to that hand?
I just fell.
That's...
The Phantom Thief Shadow.
Misaki.
What?
No, nothing! It's really nothing!
Jiiya.
What's the plan for today?
Oh. Right.
This afternoon you have fencing training.
And then, ummm, a lecture on
how to be a good emperor.
Umm... then...
Hey, Jiiya. All my tutors tell me.
That I've already surpassed their level.
That is true.
What?
Misaki is the Phantom Thief Shadow?
You're speaking too loudly!
It's true.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I don't know what to do.
Go to a hospital.
What? Misaki is the Phantom Thief Shadow?
Yes.
I know you don't believe me.
But...
It's true.
Kagami...
There's something I must tell you.
Stop!
This way!
It worked, Misaki.
Yeah.
But... I never would have thought you'd join us.
I was sure you'd be against it.
What are you talking about?
I'm not an "all work" kinda guy after all.
I don't just follow ZECT's orders.
Kagami.
Seems like the three of us did it.
Wait.
Your opponent is me.
You...
So it's you?
Very well.
I'll save you, so hurry and run.
STANDBY
Henshin!
HENSHIN
I see.
But I do not need you to save me.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
You're...!
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
What are you trying to do?
I will defeat him!
Don't get in the way!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE SCORPION
A burglary occurred nearby.
Sorry, but I'll need to see your license.
You work for ZECT!
Excuse me!
Good work.
All Worm are my prey!
Do not interfere.
There is no place for you!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Jiiya once said... "All men are fiery."
"If a spark isn't lit early,
they'll never rise to be a firework."
Mika... I will avenge you...
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.