As long as men of influence have existed,
they have all tried to make good chefs join them.
The cooks were supposed
to be used by powerful men...
But eventually men appeared who would use
the power of cooking to control powerful men.
The man that stood at the top of the
world of dark chefs passed down a single knife.
Its name is the Dark Knife.
What's wrong?!
Hey!
Pull yourself together!
Give this... to the proper successor.
Hey...
Hey!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
But who was that Rider?
Well, doesn't matter who he is...
I hope this one has his act together.
There haven't been any
decent Riders so far, right?
Exactly.
I'm the only decent one!
You're the weirdest one of them all!
You lose.
Hey! Today's recipe: tuna bowl.
Let's eat.
Thanks for the meal.
What the...?
Someone put it in my care.
Seems it's no ordinary knife.
I can't pull it out either.
Seems that knife has a rightful
successor as it's owner.
This is the best! It's just as
good as Tendou's cooking!
Aminchi's cooking is so personalized!
But lately we've had no customers.
Why?
Even though the food is so good?
It's because a neighboring
restaurant took all our customers.
As ordered, I've gathered famous chefs
from around the world. Please eat.
Fickle Sea Captain's Cheerful Seafood Pasta.
Duck meat terrine with caviar garnish.
~An afternoon garden of escargot~
Good part of the pig, cooked whole.
General tuna cooked well scolded.
10 points. 20 points.
15 points. 25 points.
The flavor isn't interesting at all!
All right.
I cannot entrust an important party to them.
Let's eat!
To protect from summer heat...
I used carbonara with a lot of egg
to make fried soba and salad.
It's so lively~!
Hey, girls shouldn't talk while eating.
Ah! Oh right, Tendou...
I'd like to ask a favor.
Really? I'll listen to any request you have, Juka.
Well...
My friend is in trouble.
Find a chef?
What is the meaning of this?
Soon ZECT will host a party to bring
in important government officials.
A Worm like you should have
sharper senses than humans.
I want you to use that sense of taste.
More importantly...
Why was the recovery of the
Drake Rider System a failure?
Do you know why?
The Worm you used was too weak.
Wrong.
Human beings have a mysterious power.
That's why.
What do you think of humans?
Humans are...
...the same as machines.
Jiiya. Here.
My first paycheck.
This is...
73 yen?
Yeah.
It's because I got a lot of penalties.
Seems I am the man that stands
at the top of earning penalties.
At any rate, that money is yours, Jiiya.
Please use it as you like.
What's wrong?
I'm so happy.
Anyway... it would be a waste to use this.
I've got an idea. Let's frame it!
Alright!
I'm going to work!
I have to please you more, Jiiya!
That restaurant?
Because of this restaurant,
Aminchi is having a hard time.
But... I wonder what happened...
The lines are gone.
A tuna so delicious that it's eyes would
pop out. Tuna with vegetables.
Me too!
Terrible.
It's terrible.
Terrible...
Juka!
What's with this cooking?!
It's so bad that it brings sadness to people!
It is not fit to serve customers!
That's fine.
What?
I can use cooking to manipulate
people's emotions.
All human emotions.
Hey, please stop it!
You! Weren't you going
to save my restaurant?!
I don't remember saying that.
I just chose this restaurant as
the grounds for my experiment.
That's all.
You are wrong.
Cooking should only exist to make people happy.
Seems you don't know the
profoundness of cooking...
...or its magic.
That's you.
You are not qualified to be a chef.
My grandmother once said...
"A knife in hand can only make people
happy... through cooking."
I need a favor.
I need your skills as a chef.
I have no intention of being your lackey.
Wait.
I will rule this world my way.
Using the power of cooking.
Cunning fellow.
Boss!
Hey!
What's with this soba!
What?
The soba's fragrance is dead, and...
The tsuyu stinks of rawness,
and the materials are lousy...
It was put out with the temperature too high.
If you want to complain about my soba...
Then how about facing
me as you say it, customer?
I was so surprised! Seems Tadokoro
is a famous soba connoisseur.
Don't bring your face so close, you're spitting.
You... what are you here for?
I heard this restaurant was famous.
I came to check its flavor.
Who is the person who cooked
this Chinese fried rice?
Me.
This cooking is pig food!
When you made this, you shook the wok, didn't you?
By shaking the wok, the rice
dances and mixes the flavor!
Making the moisture fly is only
allowed by the most skilled!
You only shake the wok to create
flavor in the fried rice!
As proof...
The fried rice sprinkles don't
have enough individual flavor!
You didn't shake the wok...
The rice was on that wok surface the whole time!
So of course the moisture would evaporate!
You are nothing but an amateur!
Stop it.
You don't have the right to
talk about Hiyori's cooking.
This is...!
The legendary Black Knife.
Why do you have this?
As a favor for someone.
They asked me to give it to the proper successor.
Then this is mine.
The only one who can master the Black Knife...
...is me!
I feel it.
I feel it!
The souls of past chefs are attaching to me!
I am...
...a god.
Your principles of cooking are wrong!
Duel me.
Very well.
I challenge you in your specialty cooking!
Master! Master! Master!
You guys...
Then...
I'll start with Tendou's.
Well made, delicious.
Just as I'd expect from Tendou.
Then...
Next...
What's wrong?
Is it so bad it brings you to tears?
Sooooo good!
Eating such a delicious thing...
It makes me so happy!
It can't be!
I told you.
I can use cooking to control emotions.
There are many excellent skills you lack.
For example.
When you cut the tofu you used a knife.
But it's better to break the toku by hand.
This preserves the precious good flavor.
When you use a knife, not only do you cut
the tofu, you also cut away the good flavor.
That's far enough!
Ikesu Ichirou!
Aren't you the guys I beat?
We will be avenged by our Master!
Master!
You...
Are you okay with accepting that duel?
I don't think it's necessary for you to appear.
It cannot be helped.
It's for my beloved students.
Speaking of students...
I'm also one of your students.
Twenty years ago, the one book you wrote...
I always...
...keep it on me.
I always carry it.
Knowledge of Cooking
Well...
How embarrassing.
Good luck in your cooking match.
Mishima.
Will this be okay?
This upcoming chef?
To insure this...
I'm having you judge this cooking match.
Please decide for yourself.
How fun.
Please order again!
STANDBY
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Now we begin a cooking match
according to the Dark Kitchen Rules.
The loser will be stripped of
his value and honor as a cook.
The daily dish will be the seasonal fish.
Hamo.
Start!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Please enjoy your meal.
Wonderful.
This magnificent hamo harmony!
It's a flavor orchestra.
Next... mine.
HYPER CLOCK UP
What was that just now?
Hey!
What's wrong?
How... surprising!
Who am I?
Where am I?
Yes!
It's heaven!
Right now I'm in heaven!
In comparison, your cooking...
Yes!
Is pig food!
I-I can't believe it!
Are you okay?!
I...
...have won.
No way...
It can't be...!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I will be the unchallenged chef of the world.
I will protect Misakinu!
I swear to protect her... with these hands.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.