Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
And you're just going to giving up TheBee?!
I...
I have something...
I have something more important to me.
Miss.
You know her?
No.
Then leave her be.
That is the law of life in the ruins of Shibuya!
"Don't concern yourself with strangers."
I told you not to come here.
What am I going to do with you?
But...
Poor thing.
What kind of life has she lived?
Women are flowers.
Bloom like a flower, even if it's just for a while.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
It's a bunch of bamboo shoots!
It's a shirako from Kyoto, They're delicious.
Brother, today's is also good!
It's the best!
As always, I want Juka to eat
the most delicious things.
Oh right. Why not have Hiyori
and Kagami have some too?
It's the first produce of the season.
Hiyori yes, but why Kagami?
There's a limit to how unsuited he is.
Welcome.
Tendou!
Yo!
Say "Welcome".
I'm a customer.
Actually, there's something I want to say to you.
I quit... being TheBee.
So what?
Where's my "Welcome"?
Welcome.
Good.
At work, you have to do your job properly.
Hiyori.
These are for you and Yumiko to enjoy.
A thanks for all the recipes you've treated me too.
It's the best takenoko.
It looks good, but...
There's too many.
Tendou.
What?
I'm fed up with you.
What's with that passionate look?
I felt it that time.
When I was fighting you...
You and I were connected...!
Cut it out.
There's no reason to be embarrassed!
We're friends, right?!
Don't misunderstand me.
Listen.
In the past, present, future, all ages there is always
a single person more perfect than others.
A man like me...
Do you think I can befriend a commoner like you?
Didn't you hear?
Let me see your ear. Your ear!
Clean out your ears!
I'll say it one more time.
In the past, present, future, all ages...
I gave up TheBee for that guy?
I don't know what happened, but...
I believe he's thinking about
you in his own way, Kagami.
Like the takenoko, there's
enough for three people.
Really?
I suppose this is too much for two people.
I'll just take one back.
Kagami.
You are forgetting something important.
Stop screwing around!
That's my line!
Don't forget you're just human!
Tendou Souji.
Hey, Gon.
What?
I've been thinking...
How long are you going to hang on to me?
What's that mean? Are you saying I'm in the way?
Are you going to abandon this poor, lonely girl?
Or rather...
You'd be fine without me, right?
First of all, there's no reward
in hanging out with a kid.
What are you saying?
A sloppy guy like you needs
a level headed person like me.
Understand?
Ow!
Hey, that hurt.
Move!
Don't you care about what'll happen to this guy?!
Daisuke, big trouble!
It's a robbery! He has a hostage!
A woman?!
A man!
Whatever.
Hey! You!
Stay away from me!
Hey!
Oh, the hostage changed.
It's a woman now.
What?!
Listen to us!
Shut up!
Hey! Get in!
Don't follow us!
What is this?!
Wh-what?
Fly away!
What is this?
The facial is about to begin.
This might hurt a bit.
Now...
Please don't cry anymore.
What your tears have damaged, I will fix.
Now...
Please.
What a lovely face.
Right now you are...
...ummm...
Right now you...
...shine more than a diamond.
Yeah, yeah. That's it.
You sound friendly enough...
So, that means you are trying
to turn me into a member of ZECT?
Yes.
If you do that everything will be official.
I refuse.
I will not join ZECT or any
organization in this world.
So, that means...
You want to stay a lone wolf?
That's not it. My individuality is too great.
I would not fit in any organization.
What a shock.
Kagami says that you have quite the ego.
But I wanted to see for myself.
You may want to be careful.
Or else you'll fall in love with me.
Cut it out!
Just how inflated can that head get?
Is something wrong?
Who are you?!
You must not anger women.
You must treat them like flowers.
Hello.
Always gently.
Yes. Understood.
It's none of your business.
He'll be right there
That's no good.
Protecting all woman...
...is my job.
Then protecting all life on Earth is my job!
From humans to even amoebas!
Well...
Aren't you a peculiar one?
You're the peculiar one.
Daisuke.
It's work.
Let's go.
Hurry.
I'm sorry, Daisuke. I suddenly had to go to a party.
I do not mind.
No matter wherever or whenever, you can call me.
And I will appear.
Gon.
Face lotion #2.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Pencil #7.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Make Up!
Just what I'd expect from Daisuke.
It's lovely.
Ma'am, for such a perfect
woman to exist in the world...
...you're truly one of a kind.
A single...
...miracle.
Yeah, yeah. That, that...
Gon.
Want to catch a breeze?
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm cleaning.
Actually...
I was thinking I may have said too much earlier.
If you're going to clean
make sure it's done perfectly!
You have no place here.
Come on...
Big Bro, welcome back.
Good to be back.
Really?
Looks like I don't have a choice.
Bye.
What is it?
Actually...
Today I have a group date to go to.
Good.
In your situation, getting a
girlfriend might shape you up.
But my friend said he had sudden
business and would be late.
My only choice is to cancel it.
I see.
So, without a friend you can't do anything?
How could I go by myself?
I've got it!
Why not just take Tendou?
You were listening?!
Let me tell you this.
Our partners will be learning a new language.
New language?
The language of the sun and the snapping turtle.
What's wrong?!
Kagami?!
It's nothing...
Look like your friend didn't make it.
You're here, it'll work out.
Yeah, yeah. The two of you should be plenty.
You're a couple of handsome guys.
Hey, sit.
What should we talk about?
Hurry, hurry.
Sit, sit.
Here.
They're awesome.
Wait.
Don't lump me with this guy.
What an ego!
Good!
Cheers.
Cheers...
What is it?
This tempura has no flavor.
My grandmother once said...
"Each meal only happens once in your life..."
"...so make each one important."
Just a moment.
He said his grandmother.
I bet he's a rich son.
My! He's rich?!
A rich son?!
Sometimes you get a good find!
Wow!
That's amazing.
Want to try?
Delicious!
Hey, that...
That shrimp...
Wow! It's delicious!
Delicious!
Kagami, did you eat it?
It's delicious.
It melts your heart.
It's all melty melty!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kazama Daisuke.
You...
Your friend?
I don't know him, he's a total stranger.
Just passing by.
But... I have a principle to
participate in all dating parties.
You really are strange.
You ladies are beautiful flowers.
But...
With my power...
I can make you more beautiful.
Kazama style ultimate technique.
Ultimate.
Make Up.
Pretty!
Wow!
Do me too!
So pretty.
You lost.
Hey, Daisuke, big trouble.
Don't get in the way. I'm at work.
What is it?
This is...
A Worm?
Tendou...
There's a good chance someone on
this ship is a Worm in mimic mode.
Please remember.
Everything you saw.
Oh right. There were grey pants.
So, it's one of those two.
What an extremely unusual flower.
Your make up is unusually bad.
Hey Kazama or whatever your name is.
That's not human.
What are you saying?
How rude...
Run!
This way! Hurry!
Tendou!
Tendou.
I'm not saving you.
I told you before.
You have forgotten something important.
So, what is that supposed to mean?!
My perfect make up...
So, all of them were Worms.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Daisuke.
Him again?
No choice...
Transform.
TRANSFORM
He's..!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Looks like I win.
Please join ZECT.
Are you planning to eliminate them all?!
For what reason did you join ZECT?
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.