[POST CREDITS]
A work in commemoration of Kamen Rider's 35th anniversary.
7 Years Earlier - 1999
Dad...
Mom...
Hiyori is here.
Save me.
Seven years ago on that day...
...the meteorite that fell on
Earth dried up the oceans.
From the meteorite an alien
species, the Worms, were born.
The secret organization ZECT
developed the Masked Rider System.
They joined to be warriors that fight the Worms.
However, Riders calling themselves Neo-ZECT have
appeared who want to revolt against the organization.
7 Years Later - The Present
'Worm Menace'
Please don't push!
Hurry hurry!
I said wait!
Hey!
You!
Hold it right there.
It's dangerous up ahead.
ZECT and Neo-ZECT's dispute is still continuing.
Understand that?
The path I walk... is for me to decide.
What?
Yes?
I said I can't see behind us!
Let's go back!
No good! There are too many!
Well I have a lot too! We can't run any further!
Oda!
There's nowhere left to run.
You're the only remnants of Neo-ZECT.
Yamato!
If it's to win our freedom,
then we'll fight to the last man!
ZECT doesn't allow traitors.
We'll follow you to the very edge
of the land and eliminate you.
You guys are just scared of freedom, aren't you?
The wind is fickle.
It just flows wherever it wishes to.
Is that all you want to say?
Prepare to fire!
Please just wait a second!
Our goal is to defeat the Worms!
Not for Riders to fight each other!
Kagami.
You're right.
Mr. Yamato!
This is the first time I've begged on my knees.
Return to ZECT.
I will endure any humiliation
if it accomplishes that.
Fine!
What we Neo-ZECT hate the most
is being ordered around like that!
Then by my hands...
...I will smash your rotten guts.
That's what you should have
said in the first place, ZECT dog.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
CHANGE BEETLE
Transform.
TRANSFORM
CHANGE BEETLE
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Cast Off.
Who are you?
My grandmother once said...
"I am, the man who walks the path of heaven..."
"...the man who will rule over everything"
Tendou... Souji.
Transform...
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
An unpleasant note that
disrupts Perfect Harmony!
How unlikeable!
Who wants to pay for my strength?
I come at a high cost.
I, the sun, shines!
Oda.
Are you really joining with that Tendou guy?
Isn't that guy interesting?
How so? Isn't he just arrogant?
But that strength is real.
And...
There is a darkness in his
eyes that draws me to him...
Although I don't know what that darkness is.
Kagami Arata, pull yourself together!
You've been going out with her for a year, right?
That... hey!
If you don't do it, she won't
stay with you. Go on! Come on!
What is it?!
Here I go...
Hiyori.
What is it?
I... I... want to always join in battery.
Is the battery in your bike broken?
No!
By battery I mean a pitcher and catcher.
Ah, so anyway...
With me... will you m...
M- M- M- Ma-
Thanks for the meal!
Wow!
Real mackerel!
I want to eat that.
No one would give you mackerel to eat!
M- M-
M-
Hey!
You...
Please make your mackerel miso.
Why me?
Who are you?
My grandmother once said...
Come with me. We have to talk.
Hey, are you joining with Oda?
Yeah.
He has a surprisingly good price.
Neo-ZECT say it's for freedom, but...
...they're just thugs doing whatever they want.
My grandmother once said...
"The strong are saved, the weak crumble."
Only the strong need to survive.
Arata.
I don't like fighting.
Do you really think that?
That only the strong should survive?
It's the law of evolution.
Then... I'm out, I guess.
Hiyori!
I'm fine.
I'm just a bit tired.
Let me tell you.
I'm joining with Oda to
destroy Neo-ZECT from the inside.
To do that I need your cooperation.
So you told him about the
Ladder to Heaven project?
Yes.
Can we trust this Tendou man?
No.
But it's not like we can hide this info.
At least this way we can use him.
Use him?
We feed Neo-ZECT information to control them.
Okay.
But you can't just decide that...
Well done, Kagami.
I'm going to recommend you as the one to
carry out the Ladder to Heaven project.
Okay.
The Ladder to Heaven project
will decide humanity's fate.
We must not let it be interrupted.
Do not worry.
I have another ace up my sleeve.
I'll leave it to you.
Ladder to Heaven project?
Yeah.
If that succeeds, humanity will
be able to regain its oceans.
How can we regain our oceans?
The orbital elevator connecting the
land to space is already complete.
From there they create a
phase in space somehow.
And draw a comet to Earth.
A comet?
Yeah.
Comets are masses of ice.
If successful, we will obtain
a great deal of water.
That's great.
If that happens, ZECT will gain even more power.
Hey.
Why doesn't Neo-ZECT take over that project?
Unfortunately...
Our offensive capability is
like a whirlwind facing a storm.
Better to remain as a fickle wind.
I'm fed up with a life of just running!
If you're serious about being free...
...then we have to stand on top of ZECT.
I'll go obtain data on ZECT's
offensive capabilities.
They say "those who control
the water, control the world".
You changed the phrase.
Interesting!
If it's you, then you can do it.
Okay then.
It's decided, isn't it?
What is it?
Do you know?
The story that ZECT has a pet gold Rider?
Yeah.
It seems those who fight
him lose before they start.
Already lost?
That's all that can be said.
When we find them, all that's left are
the corpses of his opponents and rose petals.
Why ask that?
If he's the strongest one, then I want to duel him.
You're an interesting guy.
What a beautiful place.
This is the only place where
I have memories of my mom.
I see.
If the oceans are restored,
I'm sure life will be peaceful, like in the past.
When that happens...
I want you with me, Hiyori.
By my side.
Oh right.
It's getting cold.
Hiyori, I bet you're cold too.
I'll get your coat.
Mom...
This is okay, right?
I'm actually really happy about how Arata feels.
But...
Arata...
Arata!
Run! Hurry!
But...
Hurry!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Hiyori?
Hiyori!
Hiyori...
Hang on!
Why... me?
Take her to a hospital!
Go call them!
Doctor...
You've got to be mistaken.
Hiyori doesn't have much time left?
It's unfortunate. It's the result of the
meteorite from seven years ago.
I told Hiyori, but...
Then... Hiyori knew all along?!
Doctor! That's much too tragic!
Please heal her!
She... lost her parents because of that meteorite!
Now she will lose her life too!
Please...
...heal her.
Hiyori is... here.
Save me.
Save me...
Oda has taken the information you gave me.
They're planning to take over
the Ladder to Heaven project.
That...
...doesn't matter.
If I lose Hiyori...
What should I do?
Pathetic man.
Can you protect Hiyori like that?!
I will crush Neo-ZECT.
You guys make the Ladder
to Heaven project succeed.
This is to protect Hiyori as well.
I heard how they're going
to make the phase dimension.
Good job.
It's a giant Clock Up machine.
To use that they have to send a Rider up
the orbital elevator to the space station.
Don't believe that man.
He's in communication with ZECT.
I saw him with Kagami.
He's just a source of information.
Didn't look like that to me.
You're pretending to be with us so
you can crush us with the organization, right?
What do I get if I do that?
I'll beat all the excuses out
of your body that I'll need.
Hiyori...
Could it be because you're sick...
...that you turned down my proposal?
I don't care about that.
Let's overcome your sickness together.
Thank you.
But... that's really enough.
My feelings for you are greater than all others.
From now on please let me protect you, Hiyori.
No...
I will protect you, Hiyori.
Later...
...how many days will I live?
Take it day by day.
We'll cherish each of them...
...together.
As a family.
Wake up!
I'm getting sleepy. Put more vigor into it.
What are you planning?
What about you?
What are you afraid of?
Why you!
He might be plotting something like you say.
But it's surely something really big.
Is it possible to be bigger than trying to
overtake the Ladder to Heaven project?
I want to see that.
You sure about it?
I might betray you.
When that happens...
...I will deal with you.
The Ladder to Heaven project will
be implemented in a few days.
If we're to get under ZECT, we have to act now.
Interesting!
Daisuke!
Gather the troops!
What?
Understood.
What is it?
Neo-ZECT is making their move.
Notify headquarters.
Right.
You sure you want to have
your wedding in my place?
Yeah.
It's because I love this place.
Right?
I also thought this place would be great.
Really?!
Yes?
You've been chosen as the one to carry
out the Ladder to Heaven project.
Me?
Yes.
The project will be implemented now.
But there are still arrangements.
Tendou has betrayed you.
He's sped up the timing for the attack.
Come right away.
Tendou, that guy...
What is it?
I'm sorry. I have to go right now.
But I'll be right back.
Till then... please wait.
Have a safe trip.
Today...
We will... bring down the ZECT dogs!
We're taking over the Ladder to Heaven project.
And!
We will stand at the top of humanity!
We will be the best!
And for the first time obtain true freedom!
We're nothing more than a diversion.
We're to draw off as much of the
enemy's main force as possible.
Women are flowers.
If it were up to me, I would not
bring a flower to the battlefield.
When this project is over,
can you do my make up?
Be glad too.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
I'm going on ahead.
It's begun.
We're going too.
The two are on board.
Alright. Activate it.
No one's here. Why?
What are you trying to do?
If women are flowers,
then betrayal is a sweet nectar.
Remember that.
Wind boy.
I just...
...wanted to... be the wind.
That's all.
Was our plan leaked?!
Shuda! You're a traitor?!
You betrayed ZECT,
what do you think you're saying?
Drake has already been executed.
You have no chance of winning.
This is absolute victory.
A perfect mission.
Tendou! You head for the Ladder to Heaven!
What about you?
I'll beat all of them.
I control the land. You control heaven.
Interesting!
Your opponent is me!
Fire!
TRANSFORM
Your opponent is me.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Come.
Mom...
I'm able to have a new family.
Mom.
It's done.
Try it on.
Hiyori!
Something is approaching.
It's Kabuto!
What is he trying to do?
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Open.
Yo. You're late.
Tendou...
You bastard.
What have you come for?
There's always a hidden side to ZECT's actions.
I have come to crush that.
Kagami... you go on ahead.
I'll get rid of this maggot.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Computer. The first floor is locked.
Preparing to create a hole.
Okay, I've got it.
Clock Up!
CLOCK UP
Why not call the gold Rider?
So that's what you're after?
Clock Up Machine power on.
What is that?!
Emergency. Emergency.
The Ladder to Heaven
project is proceeding well.
What are you trying to do?!
If you want to live, then don't let go!
I don't need your pity!
The flame of my passion won't lose to this heat!
RIDER BEAT
How can perfect death befall me?
We still have... Yamato.
Really?
My soul is with ZECT!
You lost your last ray of hope.
I will protect ZECT!
Fine.
But I will crush ZECT!
A rose?
Are you the gold Rider?!
But I hadn't... done anything yet.
Tendou...
As long... as you're there...
I've been waiting for this.
How dare you deceive me.
You let yourself be deceived.
Didn't you see that meteorite?
Shut up!
Why don't you punch back?
I don't want to sadden Hiyori.
It can't be...
You also have feelings for Hiyori...
She's...
...my little sister.
Hey! What do you mean little sister?!
Yes?
Kagami...
Please hurry back.
Hiyori is...!
A meteorite is currently
headed towards Earth. If it hits...
...the Earth will be completely destroyed.
Mr. Tadokoro.
However, do not worry.
The space station has antimatter
missiles that we plan to fire...
...to destroy the meteorite.
It can't be that this was
the plan from the beginning?
The organization wouldn't do that.
The plan moves into its second stage.
We pretended to bring a comet.
And we brought the meteorite.
Furthermore we pretend
to destroy the meteorite.
We hit it with missiles.
Do you believe in an afterlife?
If we're going to be destroyed either way...
...then humanity can only live on in the Worms.
Right?
Jacob received a ladder to heaven.
Perhaps that ladder, is all we have left.
Seems we have a rat listening.
A present to celebrate your marriage from me.
This... is my mother's...
It's also a memento of my mother.
Then...
If I had a brother, I'd want him
to try my cooking, just once.
And then... I'd want him to say it tastes good.
Then... hurry and get better.
Then make me a feast.
However... it better not taste bad.
Shall we begin?
As long as you two are together...
Through rich times. Through poor times.
You stay close. Living to
help and support each other.
Do you swear to this?
I swear it.
I'm sorry...
We...
...were deceived by ZECT.
ZECT... has joined with the Worms.
I...
...can only...
...rely on you now...
You going?
You don't need to come.
Your fight...
...is my fight.
The launch jetplane is about to start.
Flight mode on
Thermobatteries activated
Twenty
Nineteen
Eighteen
Seventeen
The launch Vehicle is waiting.
Sixteen
Fifteen
Fourteen
Thirteen
Twelve
All systems are clear.
Eleven
Ten
Nine
Eight
Engine ignition.
Seven
Six
Five
Four
Press out the air. Ignition.
Three
Two
One
And...
Ignition and lift off!
Lift off.
Add to the color of my rose.
The red blood of a traitor
and your tears of humiliation.
Transform.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
CHANGE BEETLE
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
HYPER CLOCK UP
HYPER CLOCK OVER
He's faster than normal Clock Up.
Gravity device? How boring.
HYPER CLOCK UP
Gravity cannot beat my Hyper Clock Up.
Your goal from the beginning
was this Hyper Zecter, right?
To make me appear you made
the Riders wipe each other out.
Then you just waited for me to appear.
However, it's no use. The cradle
carrying the Worm eggs is already here.
Worm eggs?!
The meteorite... is a cradle
for carrying dormant Worms?
The missile exists to awaken them?!
Like the kiss from a prince?
Right.
Right now, an overwhelming number of
Worms are ready to destroy humanity.
And you're okay with that?!
Letting the Worms take Earth?
Whether it's the Worms or
the humans, it doesn't matter.
The one who finds the rose is the
strongest and most beautiful.
I fight just for that.
A rose means "love".
Scatter with my love.
Rider... Kick!
MAXIMUM RIDER POWER
I'm glad...
I was able...
...to meet you.
Now!
It's thanks to you...
Hiyori...
What are you doing?
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
You alone I cannot forgive!
HYPER CLOCK UP
!evigrof tonnac I enola uoY
You alone I cannot forgive!
It can't be!
Did you go back in time?
Tendou...
MAXIMUM RIDER POWER
Hyper Kick!
RIDER KICK
Where are you going?
I walk the path of heaven,
I will save my little sister.
My grandmother once said...
"Turn the tea bag inside out
when the food is extremely bad."
I'm going back seven years to turn it around.
Kabuto... is headed for the
meteorite carrying the Worms.
But what can Kabuto do now?
It's okay.
He...
...walks the path of heaven.
He's the man who will rule over everything.
Come for a drive with me.
I'll let you meet with your
friends from seven years ago.
Hyper Clock Up!
HYPER CLOCK UP
Take this. It's my gift to you.
This is...
Was our decision a mistake?
The end of the world...
It's so beautiful.
Tendou...
I will see Hiyori again, right?
Hiyori is here.
Save me.
Put the belt on.
Take care of Hiyori.
It's okay.
I'm by your side.
A Different 7 Years Later
It's okay. I'm by your side.
I'm by your side.
Alright.
It's okay. I'm by your side.
I am by your side.
My boots are worn from all this walking
I'm on the brink of despair
When I close my eyes, I see a faint glimmer of your smile
We used to run on the beach
With our arms wrapped around each other,
as we faced the setting sun
Such calm, ordinary days are what make me happy
Storms may come, the wind may hurl me about, and I may be hurt
Even then, I wish to keep this love of mine
It's gonna be alright, I'll always be by your side
No matter how far apart we are, we both share this One World
Even if I turn my back to destiny,
over great distances, going to a distant time
There is a place I want to come home to
I'll never leave this place for anything in the entire universe
Though we may be tiny, we both reside in this One World
Hey, you...!
You too!