MAXIMUM HYPER CYCLONE
HENSHIN
CAST OFF
I will destroy...
...this world.
Maybe even everything!
Right now you're close to being our comrade.
Because you hate everything.
Come with us.
Their defeat is near.
If we keep attacking indiscriminately,
the humans will end up being destroyed.
HENSHIN
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
HENSHIN
You are the same as a newborn child.
Someday you will need our power.
Hiyori!
Hiyori? Hey! Hiyori!
Hiyori.
Don't worry.
It's okay now.
Please tell me.
Just what happened?
Hiyori?
Nothing.
It's my fault.
Because... I'm weak.
Because I'm selfish.
It's all my fault.
Hiyori...
Tsurugi...
I see...
I was able to protect you, wasn't I?
Hey. If there's anything I can do, just say so.
It's fine.
Please go.
I'm fine.
I'm sure you have more
important places to be than here.
Even I know that.
Hurry.
Please go.
Tsurugi...
I will protect Misaki.
Speaking of which... how old are you?
Twenty.
Why do you ask?
No... nothing.
So he is younger.
So... just what am I thinking?
Jovem Mestre! Jovem Mestre!
What a terrible sight!
How terrible!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Mr. Negishi.
Oh, I'm sorry. I arrived early.
Am I causing a problem?
Of course not! Please have a seat.
No! Don't be so cautious.
More importantly, the rumored Mr. Tendou?
If you mean me, I'm here.
You wretch!
Know your place!
My! An interesting person, as rumored.
Let me introduce you. This is my friend, Negishi.
Please to meet you.
Lately the Worms have been acting strangely.
Of course, we Native need your cooperation.
I was wondering what you wanted. That's it?
Don't worry. If I'm here, everything will go well.
There is no one who can beat the rising sun.
Man... that's good.
Just what I'd expect from Mr. Tendou.
Is it okay if I become your fan?
Do whatever you want.
Worms have appeared in Area E2. Tendou, hurry!
Henshin.
Area B1, Area D8, Worms have appeared!
It can't be!
One after another!
There's no end to them!
What are you going to do?
What? I'm going to help.
Like you did before, Bro.
I was a fool.
Look.
I've made it so that I will
never act like a fool again.
So that I can take in even
more darkness than before.
That's amazing! Bro, you're way too amazing!
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas.
Jiiya. It's almost Christmas, isn't it?
Yes. What present would you like this year?
Jiiya will ask Santa for you.
Do you remember?
Last year's Christmas? Just the three of us.
Cheers!
That sure was fun.
I hope the weather is good
on this year's Christmas.
How are you, Tsurugi?
M-Misakinu. You came...
Well... it seems he doesn't have much appetite.
That's no good. You have to
eat properly or you won't heal.
Here. Open.
Mi-Misakinu, it's great!
This is the best.
Jiiya.
I'm leaving the hospital.
I have completely recovered.
Then that makes things faster for me.
Tendou!
I want you to join ZECT and fight with me.
We don't have enough people.
Go ahead, Tendou.
I cooked something special for Christmas.
Chestnut and trout. KurisuMasu?
You got it!
Who cares about that?!
Why did you have Tsurugi join ZECT?!
Is there a problem?
Right now we need his help.
There are a lot of problems! He's a...
What?
If there's something you want
to say, then spit it out.
At any rate, I won't be
responsible for what happens.
From today I will lead you.
I'm Kamishiro Tsurugi.
Listen. Our mission is to defeat all Worms.
And... to protect Misakinu.
What? What's he talking about?
Today... right here...
I declare this organization
will be for protecting Misakinu.
You guys!
Are you okay, Misakinu?
Tsurugi.
What's this?
A video I borrowed.
If I don't return it, I'll have late fees.
Leave it to me.
Stop the rental video store
in Area H3 from closing.
Hey.
Who are you guys?
Video returned. Mission complete.
Okay.
Hey! Tsurugi! Just what are you doing?!
We are an organization for protecting Misakinu.
Rejoice, Misakinu. Now your safety is insured.
No! Can't read the enemy movement at all.
Everyone in formation A. Protect Misakinu!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Make some room!
Mission complete.
You're not hurt are you, Misakinu?
Tsurugi!
Hey! You joined ZECT to defeat the Worms.
Do you understand that?
What are you doing?
Everyone enter the river and find Misakinu's shoe.
I said that's not it.
Yo. You guys should help too.
We don't have enough
hands for fighting the Worms.
No one's voice can reach the darkness.
We're going.
Really?
Yeah.
I was a fool for thinking even
for a second that they'd help.
Fall back. Fall back.
Where are you guys going?
I'm sorry. We can't follow you anymore.
Do what you want then!
Tsurugi!
Cut it out!
With this, it's like you haven't
changed at all from before.
Man... what a stupid man.
But... that's not all bad somehow.
Found it! Found it, Misakinu!
Thank you!
I have a request!
What?
Christmas is coming up really soon.
Please go on a date with me.
Okay!
Really?
Jovem Mestre... what's that?
Misakinu's Christmas present. A scarf.
So that Misakinu doesn't catch a cold.
Jovem Mestre.
A date with Kamishiro Tsurugi?
Are you serious?
Don't know. Who knows?
I'm definitely against it.
Of all things...
I've been meaning to ask, why does
mentioning Tsurugi always provoke you?
No...
I just don't think you
should be dating in this situation.
I know that. But...
But?
What?
It's a secret.
Jovem Mestre... I am also delighted.
Please let Jovem Mestre's
happiness continue forever and ever.
Then... this please. With wrapping for Christmas.
What the heck? A present for Tsurugi?
Don't tell me Misaki is serious.
No... Misaki and him...
But...
When did it get finished?
I'm really the man that stands
at the top of knitting scarfs.
Oh no! I'm going to be late for my date!
Jiiya! Jiiya, get the car out. Jiiya!
Enough, Jiiya. I'm running from here.
Just wait, Misakinu. Very soon my
sparkling love will reach you.
You seem well despite all
those wounds I gave you.
You scum!
Today I'm not losing. Because
today is the most important day.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
You scumbag... you're alive?
I'm immortal!
Then...
I'll defeat you as many times as need be.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
CAST OFF
He's...
It can't be...
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
KABUTO POWER
THEBEE POWER
DRAKE POWER
SASWORD POWER
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
Tsurugi!
Misakinu...
You...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
What is a Worm?
What is a human?
I... will stand on the top of all that is Worm.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.