Stop it!
Tendou!
Stop it, Tendou!
Stop it!
Kagami... what are you trying to do?
Are you... serious?
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Please step back, Tendou!
Why? Give me a reason.
Well...
I see.
He...
Tsurugi! Where are you?!
Tsurugi...
Tsurugi!
What have I been doing?
Do not worry. Young Master doesn't
have to worry about anything.
I see...
Increase the security.
Make sure they do not become aware.
By "they"...
...do you mean us?
You... when did you?
Looks like it's finally complete... Hyper Zecter.
What are you talking about?
Playing dumb is no use.
But... how pathetic.
If Hyper Kabuto has already appeared...
Then that means eventually the
Hyper Zecter will be taken by Kabuto.
If you know that, then stop it!
Say please!
Fine.
First...
I will use that woman.
Mom...
I...
I want to try trusting him again.
The usual.
Try helping out sometime.
If you're that good, then instead of just cooking,
why not get your own customers?
Yumiko also says that. What do you think?
You have to do it.
I see... I've always refused... but maybe I'll try it.
Here.
Oh well... Guess I'll think of
Chef Hiyori's debut menu.
Come over after you're off work.
Gramps, the usual.
Not Gramps.
I am the man that stands at
the top of the soba world.
What are you doing?
I created this because I thought
it would make you happy, Misakinu.
I have put in my affection,
which is greater than any seasoning.
Please eat it.
The pressure of your affection is a bother for me.
Also, I only eat kakesoba.
I'm sorry... can I have a moment?
Ummm... it's hard for me to say this...
But I saw it.
Saw what?
Tsurugi becoming a Worm.
That's not possible. As you know...
Young Master has a grudge against Worms.
But I really saw it!
Furthermore, the Worm that is the target
of his sister's revenge is himself!
Sometimes, God forces you
to make a difficult decision.
There is no one to continue the famous
Discabil family other than Young Master.
No matter what his true identity really is.
It can't be...
You knew all along?
It's for Chef Hiyori's important debut.
I'll have to think of a surprising recipe.
All right!
A little work first?
You sure treat people roughly.
At last, I found the ultimate
soba that will please Misakinu!
Nobly white like me.
Elegant thickness.
It's perfect!
Delicious!
What? You came to eat kakesoba too?
That's udon.
What?! U-don?!
What kind of cooking is that?
Is it from U-ganda? Su-dan?
Anyway...
I have to talk to you.
About kakesoba?
I see.
Your little brother was also killed by a Worm.
Actually... my sister was murdered.
We are... kind of similar.
Maybe.
But... don't worry.
I will defeat all Worms.
I will also avenge your little brother.
Before you said "Where is the scorpion Worm?"
Do you remember what happened
before being attacked by that Worm?
There is no way I could forget.
I fought to try to protect my sister.
But...
Mika...
Why do you ask that?
Well...
Actually, the target of your revenge...
Yes?
I'll be right there.
A Worm?
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Hurry, Kagami!
Roger!
Zectroopers, put some distance between you!
Focus on one!
I will defeat all Worms.
Don't get in the way!
They're molting.
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Walking the path of heaven,
the beautiful girl of forests and flowers.
Tendou Juka!
Who... is this?
Coming.
What?
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE SCORPION
Tendou should be back soon. Please take it easy.
Now Juka is off to her classes!
Have a good time.
Bye.
Why... are my parents...?
Rider Slash!
RIDER SLASH
Your noblesse oblige...
your noble deed has touched me.
Huh?
Will you let me call you friend?
Is that not a pleasing word?
Jiiya once said...
"There is no greater wealth than friendship."
Let's make it our treasure.
Hey! I'm still not done talking.
My best friend. I am the man that
stands at the top of friendship.
Kabuto is still fighting.
Head over there.
Right, right. Right...
Let me live! Please!
Please!
Don't kill me!
ONE TWO THREE
I'm sorry! Let me go!
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Can I ask you something?
Kusakabe Hiyori.
Let me, check your body again.
Why?!
Because you are a Worm.
Worm? What's that?!
You should know that better than anyone else.
Why don't I awaken you fully?
What if...
I'm saying hypothetically...
What if someone you knew was a Worm?
So what?
No... well...
Do you ever hesitate before killing a Worm?
The Worm hold the memories
of the humans they mimic.
If I hesitate, I will be the one that dies.
But don't you feel sorry for them?
What if...
It doesn't matter!
When dealing with a Worm...
I show them no mercy... before I defeat them.
I don't think I'll be able to
ask him about Tsurugi after all.
I don't have time for this pointless discussion.
I have to go home and cook with Hiyori.
Hiyori?
So you saw this photo?
They look similar to your parents, don't they?
But don't worry about it.
It is merely a coincidence.
There's something weird about my body.
A woman said to me just now...
...that I'm a Worm.
Don't be silly. There's no way you're a Worm.
No.
You are one of us.
So you're the one feeding this rubbish to Hiyori?
If you want to know the truth, then come to me.
To know the truth, is only for
he who walks heaven's path.
Go away, weakling.
Come along now.
I'll sing a lullaby for you.
Hiyori, run. Hurry!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Tendou!
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Do you... call that living?
So hatred has...
...caused you to forget how to talk?
Poor guy.
The key to our victory, the Hyper Zecter...
...be proud that you have
donated your body for that!
Mom... protect me.
Hiyori!
Mom...
Hiyori...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
My grandmother once said...
"Even if the world were full of enemies,
there is someone you must protect".
I will take care of Hiyori.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.