Were you the one who wrote the names
for the invitation list thirty-five years ago?
What invitation list could you be talking about?
Masquerade.
A masked party.
That sounds fun.
Be sure to invite me too.
Don't play dumb.
On a list from thirty-five years ago,
is the name of your unborn son.
Why is that?
You are the one playing dumb. The reason for that...
...is probably best known by you.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Is this the limit to the Riders' powers?
What?!
My name is Mamiya Reina.
When you want to die, be sure to call that name.
I will lure you to hell with my beautiful requiem.
What do you mean that I know?
It was truly an unfortunate incident...
...with your parents.
Sounds like you know my parents.
Please continue to get along with my son.
That's right...
Is your little sister well?
You have to take care of your only blood relative.
What does that mean?!
The man who walks the path of heaven,
and will rule over everything?
I see.
It couldn't be... he...
...knows about my little sister too?
Talk! Why did I become Gatack?
There is no reason for you to know.
Then...
I'll find out myself.
What's so funny?
It can't be... this place is...!
Did you think we'd lead you
to headquarters that easily?
You!
You tricked me?!
Those who defy the
organization... must be punished!
Just try it!
Stop it!
Tadokoro.
Enough! Kagami!
Misaki!
We're leaving.
Okay.
Hello.
Tendou! Juka is... in trouble!
Looks like you've mimicked Misaki.
Juka! Are you hurt? Juka.
Oh, Tendou.
Go home and stay there.
I'll say this...
No one gets away with
messing with my little sister.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Sis!
What? It's just you?
Just now... you called me Sis?
Resignation
Tadokoro... what's this?
Don't say anything.
Why?
Could it be you're taking
responsibility for what we did?
No.
It has nothing to do with you.
Then why?!
For me, orders from the
organization are absolute.
I was able to suffer humiliation because
I thought what they were doing was right.
But, I can't do that anymore.
I no longer have the right to
be a part of this organization.
Then I'm the same way!
If you're quitting, then I am too.
No way! You too?!
You... You guys should follow your beliefs.
And what about your beliefs, Tadokoro?
Didn't you join ZECT to defeat the
Worms and protect humanity?!
I'll defeat the Worms and get
higher in the organization.
If I do that... someday I will understand
the mystery of the Masked Rider Project.
Tadokoro! Misaki! Please help me.
Please!
That dress suits you well.
Could this be your sister's dress?
For now, think of me as your sister.
Really?
Mika.
My always caring sister...
Weren't you going to use
that girl to lure Kabuto to hell?
Who are you?!
I see... so you changed your target to him?
What are you talking about?
I will sing my requiem.
Kamishiro Tsurugi...
...also known as Sasword.
A Worm?
STANDBY
Transform.
TRANSFORM
You're a...
You can do what you want.
Give it back.
I've been looking for you.
What about Juka?
She's fine. She's been home since then.
Of course she's done nothing but complain.
I see. That's good.
Actually... you're also in danger.
The Misaki doppelganger you saw...
...means the enemy is targeting those close to me.
I'm fine.
No!
Don't leave my side.
Can I trust you?!
Hiyori!
Seems my follower has
developed a peculiar mentality.
Because she took on those human memories...
Humans sure are mysterious.
Allow me to investigate who you are.
Tendou Souji.
I will give you the most beautiful...
...and cruel death.
Hiyori, run!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
It's true the young man with the belt
you saw seven years ago was me.
But I can't tell you what happened there.
Why?!
If I can't say then I can't!
Seems it's more complicated than I thought...
There are still many secrets right now...
But...
Just remember this...
No matter who the enemy is...
...I will protect you!
Forever.
If you want to investigate me, then do it.
But...
Can't you stop with Tendou?!
Hiyori...
That tepid emotion...
Humans are...
...foolish.
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Stop!
You've come to hear my requiem?
Sending the result of the analysis.
Roger!
Tendou! I need your power. Can you fight?
Of course.
Take care of Hiyori!
Understood.
Are you okay?
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to deceive you.
Were you trying to get close to me just to kill me?
It's true, I was at first...
But... I couldn't.
Then I'll forget about it.
Really? To someone like me?
It's a memento of my sister.
I want you to receive it.
I will not forgive the Worms!
I never will!
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
You did it, Kagami.
No. It's thanks to Tadokoro's guidance.
Kagami.
Tadokoro.
Let's try trusting him again.
Hiyori.
Let's go home.
Rather than doubt... I'd rather trust...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
No! I'm not going back till I see Daisuke.
Challenge me!
You must know how I work by now.
I will use everyone that I can use.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.