ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick!
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Kazama style ascension technique.
Ultimate Make Up.
Make me really pretty, okay?
Yes, of course.
You are the ultimate material.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Just what is going on?
What will I do?
Gon... please tell me.
Hey?
Gon.
Juka?
Juka!
Welcome home, Tendo—!
Oh, thank you.
Thanks to you, I'm much better.
That's good.
But...
Why does a little girl like you need to work?
There's someone I have to see.
So you need money for that?
I see.
I hope you see that person.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Could it be... Daisuke?
Daisuke?
Gon! You remember me?
Yeah! I remember it all.
Hey... I want to see you.
Daisuke.
Where are you right now?
Yeah... I want to see you too.
But...
Kazama Daisuke, open up!
Kazama Daisuke! We know you're in there!
Open up!
Goodbye, Gon.
Wait! Don't hang up!
Don't hang up, Daisuke!
Daisuke!
What?
Yeah. Right now, ZECT headquarters just called.
Kazama Daisuke.
I've never heard of that guy.
Just come here!
I'm going to check it right now.
He's not totally unrelated to you.
Kazama Daisuke is...
Kazama Daisuke...
Kazama...
Daisuke is...
It can't be!
He's really...?
Kazama Daisuke is...
ZECT has confirmed his death.
Unfortuantely...
...there's no doubt about it.
The culprit is a Worm.
And the Worm is mimicking Kazama Daisuke.
The police will let us know about people
spotting the wanted Kazama Daisuke.
Yeah.
The living Kazama Daisuke is a Worm.
This is unforgivable!
Absuloutely!
Leave it to me. I will defeat all Worms.
Well done.
Pretending to be dead is easy for us.
The scenario is going as we thought.
Daisuke!
Where are you?! Daisuke!
Where are you?!
Daisuke!
You guys!
That's far enough!
We won't let you kill anymore!
Die, Worm!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
I'm the real one! I'm not a Worm!
Just what is going on?!
That's enough!
I'm fed up with your tricks!
TRANSFORM
Look!
I'm the real one.
A Worm copies everything!
It's no surprise that you can transform!
Why is this happening?!
Fire!
Daisuke!
Please leave the rest to ZECT.
We'll confirm his death...
...and recover the Drake Grip.
I wonder if we have avenged him?
Kazama Daisuke?
What's wrong?
I see. I understand.
Everything went well.
All that's left is to recover the Drake Grip...
...and you will be Drake's chosen one.
As promised...
...you will use that power for ZECT.
Okay?
However...
I will decide who Drake kills.
Don't forget that promise.
Yeah.
I understand.
Daisuke...
Gon.
We... finally meet.
I'm so happy... Gon.
Fool. Why are you being so frank? It's gross.
But... just why is this happening to you, Daisuke?
I don't know either.
You've done enough.
Please go.
No! I only just found you!
I'm glad to see you.
Being near me...
...is not good.
No! I want to be by your side, Daisuke!
I don't want to leave!
He's working?! Young Master?
How terrible.
No... I can't stay here. I can't stay here.
You should sleep more.
Now. Eat this.
It's turtle porridge. It's full of nutrients.
I'm sure it'll make you better soon.
No, no. I'm really okay.
No, please don't resist so much.
No, no, I'm really okay. I'm really okay.
Please.
Then I'll take this.
Gon...
Okay? As my part time work fee.
Shopkeeper
Now delivers
But...
I can't believe it.
That Kazama Daisuke is...
Does Gon know this?
It's done.
Eat.
You!
To restore the fortunes of the world's
number one famous family, Discabil...
...please leave your money.
I'll take it as your donation.
But you don't have to Misakinu...
It's my treat.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I will today.
I don't have any appetite.
Misakinu!
What's wrong?
Do you feel uneasy?
If there's anything I can do, just tell me.
Another Rider, just like you, is dead.
Don't you... feel anything?
I hate insensitive people.
It's true...
...that I think a lot about myself.
My sister also said it often.
"You are insensitive..."
Young Master.
Good?
Yeah.
It's full of nutrients,
you'll get better right away.
I see.
So that's how it is.
You!
Stay away!
Seems we fell into a trap.
If Gon acknowledges you...
...then I want to believe.
Didn't I say so?! I said I was the real one!
Just what were you trying to do?!
Going all out on me!
But I wasn't a hundred percent
sure you were real.
What are you saying?
Daisuke is Daisuke. He's the real one.
Seems the Worm wasn't alone in this incident.
I have no doubt ZECT is also involved.
ZECT is?
Their goal is probably...
...to collect the Masked Rider System.
Where's the Drake Grip?
In the river.
Thanks to you guys knocking me out cold.
If you're real...
...then you will pretend to be an imposter.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I've calmed down. It's from suddenly moving.
I'm more worried about Young Master.
How pitiful.
I understand...
Young Master can see his deceased
older sister in that woman.
Deceased...? Could she have
been killed... by a Worm?
That...
...is the same... as me.
Yes?
Tendou?
What is this?
Just what is going to happen?
Be quiet and watch.
The truth will be exposed soon.
Take it. From now on you are
Drake, and will work for ZECT.
Wait!
No way!
Two Daisukes?!
What the hell?
He's an imposter.
No. He's the real one!
What are you saying? You are the imposter.
No. The real one!
Fool! I'll show my proof right now!
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Don't worry.
From now on I will always live on as you.
How dare you decieve me?!
Just to steal that—!
My grandmother once said...
"Fancy food does not taste good..."
"No matter what truth you
try to hide, you cannot hide it."
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Damn!
Move!
Like I'll let you!
Gon! The Grip!
I'm the real one! Give it to me!
Here, Daisuke!
How did you know?!
You can't decieve my eyes! I can tell!
Good job, Gon. No matter
what happens, we are eternal...
Eternal...
Ummm... well...
Partners.
Yes, yes. That, that.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Rider Shooting!
RIDER SHOOTING
Clock Up!
CLOCK UP
You cannot be me!
The only one who can live as me...
...is me!
CLOCK OVER
Daisuke!
Gon.
Here. I earned this.
Money.
What is this?
Well. You are busy...
So to see you, I thought I'd have to be
one of your make up customers.
So... I got a part time job.
Silly.
I'll do it for free any time, your make up.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
The only one who can master the Black Knife...
...is me!
Now we begin a cooking match
according to the Dark Kitchen Rules.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.