Your grand plan will probably
be completed by our sons.
Do not worry.
Kusakabe.
HYPER CLOCK UP
MAXIMUM RIDER POWER
ONE TWO THREE
Hyper Kick!
RIDER KICK
HYPER CLOCK OVER
One, two.
A complete solar eclipse...
...search for it.
An eclipse...
Hiyori is...
...there.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Good morning!
I'm a caterpillar.
Hey. Camp is next week, right?
You have tension over that already?
Because I was sick and missed
the elementary camp, right?
That's why this is my first camp,
and I'm really looking forward to it!
I see.
Then get your nutrients so
that you don't get sick this time.
I love pork broth!
It's delicious!
Oh right. Tendou, did you know?
Members from our baseball team have vanished.
Vanished?
It's definitely because of the cursed mirror.
You mean the one on the school stairs?
What kind of mirror is it?
You want to know?
Well...
Orders to investigate from Tendou?
He's so bossy.
So. What are we investigating?
At Juka's middle school, every member of
their baseball team has disappeared.
That's a pretty big case.
So what happened?
It's strange.
Strange?
At first, orders to search for
them all were given, but...
...they were immediately cancelled.
That is weird...
I'll take these.
Hey. I'm not done eating yet.
Oh yeah, these are also orders
from Commander Tendou.
Kagami is to take care of Renge.
Me?!
I don't like that.
Don't say that! I don't like it either.
This is good. You've finally got someone under you.
I don't think I'm lower than him.
There it is.
What are you saying?!
Kagami.
Anyway, what is Tendou doing?!
He's already doing an internal investigation.
'Seika Academy Middle School Division'
Good morning.
Good morning! Good morning!
'Yakisoba Bread'
So why a bread store?
This way I won't miss even the smallest thing.
This is also for the success of Juka's first camp.
Camp?!
We're here for that reason?
Although it's for the baseball team incident.
That disgraceful team...
...it's good they disappeared.
Disgraceful team?
Seems they haven't won in many years.
In the end they made a wish on the cursed mirror.
They're awful.
Cursed mirror?
Then. I have class.
The cursed mirror? Juka also knew that story.
This is the cursed mirror?
If you make a wish on this mirror,
it will make your wish come true.
That's good.
I hope I can succeed before Tendou.
But when your wish comes true...
you disappear mysteriously.
Say that sooner!
I lied.
Please! I'm sorry.
Today, I have a new friend to introduce to you all.
Come in.
I am the man who will replace the gods with
a slash of my sword, Kamishiro Tsurugi.
You should be proud to be learning with me.
So happy you have nothing
to say? What cute fellows.
I remember! The strange elementary
school student from before!
You are... the commoner who gave me takoyaki?!
You know each other?
Then you can sit next to Juka.
Nice smell.
I'm honored by your compliment.
Hey! Please leave.
Excuse me?
What? Who are you guys?
What are you doing... hey!
R-Ruffians!
Let go! Let me go! Let me go!
Let go!
Ruffians!
'Autumn Quarter National Mock Exam Grades'
'Tendou Juka'
That's amazing, Juka. You're number one again.
It's because my talented brother is my tutor.
'Kobayashi Keiko'
So next week is the camp! Let's go!
I love camp!
How is this charm meant
to make you smarter?!
This thing...!
That's me.
I have been broken into many little pieces.
What are you talking about?
Humans don't break that easily.
I won't rely on that charm anymore.
I'll just work harder tomorrow.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
CHANGE PUNCH HOPPER
Run.
That girl being attacked...
It might mean something is
occurring near Juka's school.
In this case, I'll have you guys
do undercover investigating too.
Bro.
Partner.
You... shouldn't think of that as a good thing
If you think losers like us can grab
onto even the slightest bit of light...
...you'll get hurt.
Hey! Everyone inside! Push it!
Okay! Push it!
Breaking through the middle!
Damn! Damn!
Why is Misaki a teacher
while I'm a rugby coach?!
That makes the investigating easier.
Get along with the team members
and ask them a lot of questions.
Then why don't you get along
with the members as their manager?
I... hate the stink of sweat.
What was that?!
I was newly appointed to
this school. I'm Misakihara.
Misakinu!
Why are you here?
After having first rate tutors...
I learned how to be a good emperor, but...
By becoming the top of a common
middle school, such a noble heart is...
Noblesse oblige.
Well said, Young Master.
Ruffians!
Let go!
Won't you let go?!
Hey! Let go! Ruffians!
Should you be studying here
even though it's class time?
I must do better on the next exam.
I don't have time to go to class.
How troublesome.
By the way, what is that?
Yakisoba bread that I made.
Is it good?
Its deliciousness is on a different level.
You sure are confident.
Well. If I feel like it, I'll buy one from you.
So, who knows the answer to this problem?
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Okay then...
Kamishiro.
Okay.
Ladies and gentleman, I give you this honor.
Is there anyone who will
take my place and solve it?
Yes!
Well then. Jiiya.
A servant's answer is the
same as the master's answer.
Right, Misakinu?
What manner of reward is this?
Did you get any new information?
Nothing in particular. What about you?
Just heard a different rumor.
What kind?
Some years ago... there was a Choral
team that won the nationals, but...
But they disappeared suddenly.
What happened afterward?
Even now you can hear their singing it seems.
When you hear that song...
the devil's door is opened... and the dead are revived!
Is that story real?
D-don't scare us.
First a cursed mirror, then a missing choir club.
Interesting.
Anyway, I need you guys to help.
What is this uproar?
They say this yakisoba bread is really good.
Yakisoba?
Is that related to kakesoba?
Settle down!
There's still plenty left.
Ah. Big Brother!
He's your brother?!
Yeah. Tendou!
Juka! Do you want one too?
Renge, change.
Putting in 100 yen.
Tendou, that guy. Why is he doing this?!
I'm sure the master has some sort of idea.
My friend Kagamin!
Tsurugi!
Why are you...?!
'Sold out for today'
Working too hard is bad for your body.
Here.
I left it for you.
Thank you.
It's really delicious!
This is...?
Don't tell me it's the song of the missing choir?
One two.
So they're back?
The rumors are true.
The devil's door opened?
Then...
The dead have revived?
How can such rubbish be true?!
I'm gonna go check it out!
What are you doing?! Hurry up and come!
You can handle them if they're ghosts.
Agreed.
That's not the case!
Let's go.
When did they...?
Be careful. They're here.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
CAST OFF
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Rider Kick.
Not gonna lose!
Hyper Cast Off.
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
Hyper Kabuto.
Will you tell me about the
type of Worm called Native?
Doesn't ZECT know them best?
What do you mean?
First defeat it without using Hyper Clock Up.
You people underestimate my power.
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"My evolution is faster than the speed of the light"
"Nothing in this universe can
keep up with my evolution."
That's...
I want to be number one in the next exam.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
The truth lies in the rumors.
Tendou Juka's wish has already
been conveyed to the Worm.
I'm going ghost-hunting. Take care of everyone.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.