ONE TWO THREE
Rider...
...Kick
RIDER KICK
The Worm?!
Did Kabuto defeat him?!
Looks like it.
Where's the Rider Bike?
It...
...was taken by Kabuto.
But you were the one who
took it without permission!
I'm sorry!
How do you plan to take responsibility for this?!
I'll pay it back with the
money I earn working part time...
Stop screwing around.
You're not fit to be a member of ZECT.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Overtake him!
Retreat!
What?!
Where is it?!
Hey! What's wrong?! Are you okay?!
What's going on?!
Hey! Let go!
Wait!
No!
It wasn't me!
Capture her!
The culprit is that... thing, not me!
I'm not fit to work for ZECT?
Did I get fired?!
Mackerel miso.
You wanted to try it, right?
But why?
No reason. If you don't want it...
Please, let me try it! Let me try it!
This is great.
I finally get to eat it too!
Hiyori!
That miso is the best present you can give me.
Waiting for the trout to bite would fit you best.
Tendou...
The golden mackerel is first class.
Offer me a gift as well.
Why me?
Hiyori!
Another mackerel miso.
Why should I?
I want to eat the world's best mackerel miso again.
You sure are persistent.
Tendou...
Do you know how much I've suffered because of you?
You want to talk about ZECT here?
Please don't make that sound again,
another will be ready soon.
You should be happy.
I'm going t help you, as your comrade.
Really?!
In return, I want you to tell me a few things.
No good.
We're out of mackerel.
Seven years ago...
A meteorite suddenly
fell in Shibuya, destroying it.
But that was only the start of humanity's crisis.
"It was more than a meteorite
that fell from space" right?
Yeah.
It brought over the Worms.
They've killed countless people... and they're
able to perfectly mimic their victims.
What are they after?
What's their criteria for picking victims?
We haven't a clue.
They're smart... and they're destroying
humanity as we know it.
So right now you could be a Worm...
Please stop!
Someday, I will defeat every last Worm.
I will defeat them.
That's why I joined ZECT.
So you have a grudge against the Worm?
Not exactly...
What kind of organization is ZECT?
It's as I told you before.
All I know is that it's a secret
organization for exterminating the Worm.
But the police, who are helpless
against the Worm, secretly help ZECT.
I see.
I've learned quite a bit.
Hey!
Wait!
Take me to your comrades.
Sorry, can't.
What?
You said you'd cooperate.
I've done plenty of cooperation for you already.
I already defeated a whole swarm of Worms.
You tricked me!
Then I'm going to report you to the organization!
You can't do that.
Yes?
Kagami, where are you?
There's been an incident.
Okay.
I'll consider it my final chance and do my best!
Tamai Yuki, twenty years old.
She's currently under
arrest for killing an officer.
However, someone fled the
scene who looked exactly like her.
One of them is a Worm.
Can we let the imprisoned one go?
We can't use the organization's
powers that easily.
That'll make our secret plans harder.
I see.
Misaki.
Yes.
You check out the imprisoned one.
Okay.
You search for the one that fled.
Kagami.
Considering what happened previously...
I've decided to give you this.
If you'd please.
Hey! I'm not the culprit! The real culprit is me!
But that me is not me!
A weird monster has my face!
Be quiet!
Cool your head!
Hey, I have an important date today.
It's my chance to be an IT Service apprentice.
Please! Let me out!
Why...
Why me?
Why won't you believe me?
I believe you.
So will you tell me?
What happened to you?
I've located her in the Chita area.
Beginning pursuit.
Wow!
Rose, lemon grass blend tea. Folded fruit tart.
Let's eat!
It's so yummy!
Good!
Hey, Big Bro!
You seem so happy lately.
Has the thing you've been
waiting for finally arrived?
Correct, now I'm waiting for something different.
Something different?
Could it be... a girlfriend?
The one that waits gets the okay.
The okay?
It's the best mackerel.
Sound good?
I want to try that too!
Leave it to me.
Umm... Miss Tama Yuki?
Wait!
Ryou...
Where'd she go?!
So this one must be the Worm.
You!
Have you got more mackerel yet?
Granting my little sister's meager wish...
is yours and all of humanity's duty!
Forget that, I'm in big trouble.
Hey, wait!
What are you doing, Tendou!
Misaki is on watch here.
There's no need for two lookouts.
If we bring them together, one of them
will try to eliminate the other.
That's how we identify the Worm.
That's too dangerous!
But hold on a sec...
That could actually work.
Hey!
This is obviously a bad idea.
I should talk to my superiors.
There's no time for that.
And do you want to report
your mistake to your superiors?
It was my chance to be an IT apprentice.
I finally got an interview...
There's no way you're the Worm right?
Worm...?
No...
It's nothing.
Where are you two going?
Is the detention cell in there?
Yeah...
Hold it right there!
Open up!
This is too reckless!
Who are you?!
Stop!
Push it in!
Help me!
Okay!
Please hurry! I can't hold it forever!
Is your name Yuki?
What are you doing?
Setting her free.
Come with me.
Who are you?!
The man who will rule over everything.
Open up!
Damn it!
Stand down!
Why you!
Don't move!
Let that woman go!
If you don't...
I'm sorry!
This is a misunderstanding!
Please let them go!
Your organization's true power...
ZECT's power, you will show it to me.
What?!
Wait!
Don't worry about the rest.
Do what you want.
Tendou!
That was fast.
That wasn't fast at all!
It's all a mess thanks to you.
Where's the woman?
What are you doing?! Hurry up!
Looks like I don't have a choice.
This is so I can let my
little sister eat your mackerel.
Uemura, thanks for waiting.
What are you?
What are you?!
What are you guys?
Are you girls twins?
No! I'm Yuki!
It's me! I'm the real one!
Get lost!
Wait!
It's dangerous, get away.
So you're the Worm after all.
It's over for you.
Well.
So it was the imprisoned one.
Why you...!
Just as I thought.
This is the most thorough way to identify a Worm.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
It's using Clock Up!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Huh?! Where am I?!
C-cracks!
Why?!
CLOCK UP
Clock Up, again?!
ONE TWO THREE
Rider...
...Kick
RIDER KICK
Tell them you defeated the Worm.
Why?
It was your last chance to redeem yourself, right?
Are you feeling sorry for me?!
No.
You are an important source of information.
It would inconvenience me
if you got fired from ZECT.
I see...
You really like making
everything revolve around you.
No.
I am the center of the world.
My grandmother once said...
"Make the world revolve around you."
"It's more fun to think that way."
Ryou!
It sure is hard being popular.
I don't even have time to eat.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Kagami's little brother has returned.
Go investigate using your powers at ZECT.
This is the restaurant Salle, right?
So you're saying that man is Kabuto?
Yes. I think we should further investigate him.
Do you know anything
about Kagami's little brother?
It seems he disappeared... two years ago.
Are you really Ryou?
You're Ryou, right?
Why aren't you fighting back?
What'll you do?
You decide.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.