KABUTO POWER
THEBEE POWER
DRAKE POWER
SASWORD POWER
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
Since then I've done
Hyper Clock Up many times, but...
...I still haven't reached that place.
What is going on?
And...
The man who was with Hiyori...
Just who...
You!
Finished with your after-meal coffee?
It will be your final coffee.
I was going to let you take
your time to drink it, but...
I'm taking it today.
The Hyper Zecter, and your life.
If we do it here it will cause trouble for the shop.
Let's go out.
Master, me too.
If you go you'd cause me trouble.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Rejoice.
You'll hear my requiem soon enough.
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
THEBEE POWER
HYPER STING
I hope I'm always with Daisuke.
I hope I can get close to the
world's most beautiful woman.
It's delicious!
For this season it has to be pot cuisine right?
It warms your heart and body!
Yeah. It's liver and red bean pot.
I'm proud of it. I'd even say it's art.
Yes, hello?
No way.
For real, for real?
Don't talk on the phone during a meal.
I'm sorry. I'll call you back.
It's just... it was about falling in love.
What?
So the day has finally come?
Who is it?
What kind of person is he?!
Bring him here now!
No, it's not me.
It was my friend.
Tendou, you really jump to conclusions.
I see...
You should have said so sooner.
Hey, Daisuke. How long are
you planning to do that?
Hey, I'm talking to you Daisuke.
Beautiful.
God... Thank you.
Shouldn't you call an ambulance?
But... I feel like we've met somewhere before.
No... there's no way I can forget such beauty.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Kazama Daisuke.
Where am I?
Who are you?
What are you talking about? That's our line.
Daisuke's been watching over your
unconscious body all this time.
Me?
Just what happened? I'll listen if you'd like.
No, it's nothing.
I'm sorry for being a burden.
No way! More importantly, please
let me do your make up sometime.
You are the world's most beautiful...
Beautiful...
Umm... well...
Miracle.
Yes yes. That that.
Umm... excuse me.
What's your name?
Mamiya Reina.
There are thirty-five messages.
Reina! Are you there?!
What about today's practice?
Everyone's waiting!
Reina
Call me!
Looks like you're not back.
Hello?
Reina. Why haven't you been coming to practice?
What happened to you?
Call us if you're taking a break.
Reina.
Call us when you come back.
Mamiya. Did you get bored of this?
Everyone's worried, contact us soon.
Worried...
Hello? Ms. Reina?
Mamiya... Call us!
I can't remember...
I don't remember what I've been doing.
Just what happened to me?
'Opera Circle'
Reina!
Where have you been?!
Everyone was worried!
I'm sorry.
Just what happened!? Tell us!
Well... my mother was sick...
Forget it! It was nothing.
Today... just return to your previous life.
I see.
I'm sorry... it's been really busy.
I'm sorry!
I'll work hard on practicing again today.
Let's work together!
Don't joke, Reina! Do you
think you can be so selfish?
Let me just tell you, you're not
preforming in the next performance.
I will sing in your place.
Wait.
Reina.
For now, just sing.
Enough.
You've gotten rusty, Reina.
Thanks... for waiting...
What is this?!
My love letters.
I got carpal tunnel from
writing replies to all of them.
Seems I am the man that stands
at the top of carpal tunnel.
Is that all you wanted to say?
You called me just to show off?
No. I turned them all down.
Because... I have Misakinu.
My friend, Kagamin.
What?
I need a favor as best friends.
I have to make up with Misakinu.
Stop joking around!
Please! It's the only favor I'll ask of you!
Quit it!
I'm bad with relationships!
Please!
Anyway, with your true identity...
What about his true identitiy?
Nothing.
Tendou. Good timing. I need a small favor.
Please!
I can't!
You can't turn me down, right?
What is this?
The key to Hiyori's apartment.
Hiyori's...
We're not the only ones who miss Hiyori.
She has a spoiled kid.
Can you take care of him?
Please.
The upcoming preformance...
...I have to appear!
I understand how you feel.
It's your first time on stage after all.
But... right now you can't.
I will endure any kind of lesson!
Please!
I've been working hard all this time for this!
Even if it means you have to
start over from scratch?
Yes. I understand.
The upcoming performance is an important
opera by the Red Group's new members.
I will decide in the end whether you sing or not.
Okay. Thank you!
This is the first time, isn't it?
The first time I've seen Hiyori's room.
Guess you're the "spoiled kid"?
If you're that good, then instead of just cooking,
why not get your own customers?
I see... I've always refused... but maybe I'll try it.
Hiyori...
It's the Red Group's New Member performance.
Please.
It's the Red Group's New
Member performance. Please.
One please.
Thank you.
That's good.
You!
Reina, do you believe in fate?
I believe in it.
In fate between you and me.
'Red Group's New Member Performance'
Red Group? It's an opera?
Yes.
I've got it. Why not come
and listen? I can introduce you.
Are you appearing, Reina?
I think...
No... I will. Definitely.
That's good.
I'll be sure to go.
I'm sure you have a beautiful
singing voice. Like an angel's...
No way. I still have a ways to go.
But... it's my childhood dream to sing on stage.
Let me know if I can do anything.
I've got it!
Please come to the New Member Performance.
How stupid.
Please come to the Red Group's
New Member performance
I see.
It's the Red Group's New
Member performance. Please.
So that's what happened.
It's the Red Group's New Member performance.
Please.
Come here.
Good boy! Good job.
I envy that dog.
Come.
He's getting complimented.
You still have a ways to go.
Listen.
We live in a world of darkness.
Don't seek the light.
I'm sorry, Bro.
I was wrong.
Kamishiro Tsurugi wants what?
Yes.
He wants me to help him make up with you, Misaki.
Ah, Of course I turned him down.
What trouble.
If he doesn't give up on me...
I wonder if there's any good way for doing this?
My lover! Misakinu!
You!
Misakinu, look!
'Misakinu's Personal Kakesoba'
I have started a kakesoba shop only for you!
The customer is limited to just one!
Just you.
I'm sorry! I've got a date...
Of course! Now...
On my food cart, let's travel to a world of love.
No! I have a date with Kagami.
We're going out.
Right. It's super love love. Right?
Yes yes. It's really...
Love love.
Master is cooking today? Renge is so touched!
Hiyori... I will take your
feelings and express them.
Welcome.
Umm... I need a favor.
Can I put this up here?
Do you know who she is?!
She's a Worm!
What?
Worm?
No way. Reina is...
My name is Mamiya Reina.
When you want to die, just call that name.
No...
Reina is...
No!
Reina!
Ummm... What is a Worm?
Don't play dumb!
You will...
...be defeated by me!
HENSHIN
Stop!
You bastard!
What are you trying to do?!
Reina... The current Reina isn't a Worm!
CAST OFF
What is going on?
Mamiya Reina.
You have lost your Worm heart.
You will be executed.
That is our law.
Reina!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
CAST OFF
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
Watch out!
ALL ZECTER COMBINED
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
This is...
Tendou!
Hiyori!
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
You're...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Someone important to me is a Worm. That's all.
I will protect this person.
I'm by your side! I'll always be by your side!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.