You're also mocking me, aren't you?
You laugh...
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Give it back!
Give back my TheBee Zecter!
Please give back my TheBee...
I envy you.
A guy like me...
...my tears dried up long ago.
Tendou! Let's eat!
...and. What are these things?
Well. They're my fans.
How cute!
Why don't you eat with us?
I have food.
Fried salmon.
White rice. Tofu miso soup.
And pickled vegetables.
It's delicious.
Deliciousness is a sin.
It causes disorders in a soldier's thinking.
Is that Mishima's teachings?
Young Master!
Young Master! Young Master!
Where are you right now?
Don't worry! I'm just going on a little journey.
For what reason?
As I am right now, even if I obtain money...
...I will use three times as much.
To restore the Discabil family...
...I must learn...
...the common people's happiness.
Mishima.
Please do something about Tendou.
He...
...took my TheBee Zecter.
What an eyesore.
Yeah.
So hurry, do something about him!
I'm talking about you!
This is not a place for soldiers to come and die.
No...
From here on I will be Mr. Mishima's...
...guard?
Wait...
My TheBee just left...
...and why is Yaguruma a new Rider?!
A new Rider?
Yeah!
Get lost.
Your skills have improved.
I must reward...
...my very talented subordinate.
I am gratefully happy.
Common people's clothes please.
Common people?
You don't know?
Like that.
What a mysterious feeling to wear this.
But I must stand at the top of being common.
Customer, what about these?
I will trade these clothes to you.
Always cherish them.
If you give me the Hyper Zecter,
I will take care of eliminating Kabuto.
Hyper Zecter?
I have no business with
lowly Worms like yourselves.
At this rate, it will eventually be Kabuto's.
Are you okay with that?
Get out.
Is that your response?
I see.
Feel like giving me the Gatack Zecter?
I can't do that.
Please give back everyone's Zecters.
Defeating the Worm and protecting
humanity is us Rider's mission.
I will take care of all that.
I understand your feelings for Hiyori, but...
Destroying ZECT and eliminating all the Riders...
You're taking your thinking
too far into the extreme!
It is for the best, so that
Hiyori can live as Hiyori.
But first how can you save Hiyori...
You there!
Don't hide. Come out.
You!
Very perceptive.
What do you want?
I thought I'd tell you about
what happened in Area X.
I'm listening.
I don't care if you're plotting something.
Talk.
That day...
Mishima tried to use that man as a test
subject for the Hyper Zecter test.
But... Hyper Zecter went out of control...
The test subject and that girl were
flung to the edge of time and space.
The edge of time and space?
Correct. At that time...
...a distortion was created from the
Hyper Zecter going out of control.
Mishima and you two were sent to the beach.
The Hyper Zecter is currently...
...in Mishima's hands.
What you do now is up to you.
Tendou Souji.
Tendou...
What is the Hyper Zecter?
You saw it, didn't you?
HYPER CLOCK UP
At any rate, to save Hiyori...
...I need the Hyper Zecter.
So why the cooking?!
An important customer is coming.
You...
Tendou.
What is this important thing
that you have to say to me?
First eat.
Renge too.
How boring. I have no sense of taste.
Then this...
...all the Zecters I have.
I can give them all back.
The condition?
It's an exchange.
For the Hyper Zecter.
I'm so happy.
Keep collecting Zecters. It'll help me too.
What do you mean?
This is a waste of time.
Excuse me.
Wait! I must have the Hyper Zecter!
Wait!
Common happiness?
I do not understand.
What is the joy in living as you people?
Are you okay?
Juka, let's go.
What are you doing?
Trying to sin again?
This is all his fault.
Tendou is aware of the Hyper Zecter's existence.
There's no time left. Eliminate him.
Why do this?
I wanted to see your face happy again.
That's all.
Please eat.
I cooked this for you since you
have not eaten for seven years.
Omelet rice.
I even dreamed of it... omelet rice.
You can begin here.
I will begin too...
I will definitely obtain the Hyper Zecter.
Eat more.
You can have all the seconds you want.
What are you doing?!
You are not the Captain or
TheBee, you're just a coward.
You bastard!
I envy you... Kageyama.
Yaguruma!
The hell I saw wasn't like this...
Shut up!
It's your fault that TheBee was taken from me!
Only by crawling on the ground...
...will you be able to see the light.
Light?
But don't expect too much.
Because it's not like we can be together forever.
I'm hungry...
But... I cannot steal from others.
Thief!
No!
Come with me! We're going to the police.
Mannerless cur!
I challenge you to duel!
Damn... the people... are pretty good.
But...
If I weren't hungry I would have won.
You are... the one from before.
Sorry about before.
You helped me, and I didn't even thank you.
This is...
...for me?
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"If you receive a little kindness,
give them a large serving."
Please eat!
Delicious!
What is this?
You don't know? It's takoyaki.
It's the best! Takoyaki is number one!
Hand Hyper Zecter to me.
If you be good and give it up...
...you will not be held responsible.
I'm sorry!
Right now...
...there is someone that I have to give this to!
Give it to me!
And I'll let you live.
So this is what you were up to?
Give it to me.
I'll guarantee your life.
I was never more than ZECT's dog.
But... A dog, when fed, always repays her debt.
How reckless.
Mr. Tendou!
I'll handle this somehow.
Don't move from there!
Renge!
Give it to me!
Give it to me.
Shoot her!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Henshin!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
After them!
I've got it.
Hyper Zecter was...
Better to destroy it than to let you obtain it.
Kabuto... I just destroyed your future.
Future?
So that's how it is.
The future is already in my hands.
And... I will continue holding on to it.
That's not possible!
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
Hyper Clock Up!
HYPER CLOCK UP
HYPER CLOCK OVER
Hyper Clock Up!
HYPER CLOCK UP
MAXIMUM RIDER POWER
ONE TWO THREE
Hyper Kick.
RIDER KICK
HYPER CLOCK OVER
I am of no use without Young Master.
What should I do?
Jiiya!
Young Master!
I finally understand.
The feeling of gratitude for a bit of food.
And... the kindness of people.
That is... the common people's happiness, right?
Well said, Young Master!
My long journey is over.
From here on, I, Jiiya will do
my best to revive the house.
Then...
That's Jiiya being Jiiya.
Hyper Zecter should have
been destroyed that time.
But...
Why did it appear again?
To recreate the future, it crossed time to arrive.
From the future?
And it has appeared many times before.
Let's call that Hyper Form.
That's probably myself from the future.
You...
If so...
Then someday I will master using the
Hyper Zecter and be able to cross time.
When that time comes Hiyori...
Hyper Zecter.
Hiyori's drawing.
I don't know how far Hiyori was
flung to the edge of time and space.
But for the Hyper Zecter from
the future to bring this picture...
...it must mean Hiyori will eventually be saved.
That's what I believe.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Unless humans become Riders and defeat the Worm...
...we Natives will be in trouble.
Kageyama... Want to go to hell with me?
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.