I can't believe this.
If you were an ordinary guy, you wouldn't
have been given the job as a ZECT team leader.
Why was I brought to Area X?
Now that we have Gatack...
The Masked Rider Project
is entering it's next phase.
Next phase?
And most likely... the Worms are too.
That's far enough!
Hiyori, run!
You're... Kagami...
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Alright! I'm so strong!
It's finally my era!
I will guide this era.
Don't kill!
Stop it!
What is the meaning of this?
Five Worms were defeated.
For zero yen?!
Our contract has been annulled.
Th-that is so forceful...
Now that ZECT has it's most powerful Rider...
...Sasword's abilites are no longer needed.
That's fine.
I have plenty of money.
But...
Tell that "most powerful Rider" this.
I will defeat all the Worms.
If he gets in my way, I will show no mercy.
Despite what Young Master
said, please reconsider.
Even if the reward is half of before. Even a third.
This would be a good time to tell Tsurugi.
I've already investigated
England's famous family, Discabil.
Fiscally they are at an end.
The soup is transparent.
The broth is made with kelp and cutlet.
Delicious.
It can't be...
This flavor...
You!
Hello.
Bro, someone you know?
Yeah.
But... why are you...
Please do not ask why.
I cannot let Humanity's Treasure do this.
Your future is...
...I don't see it.
Stop!
This is...
Uncle! Some ramen!
Don't call me uncle.
It is I.
Tendou!
One with everything.
Righty-o.
Hey! Don't decide it yourself!
Anyway why are you...?
It's training.
The road to cooking is vast.
So...
...why me as well?
Hiyori...
Is the restaurant okay?
Hey! Hiyori.
At any rate, this is how it is.
From now on when you eat
ramen you will come here.
Despite my appearance, I am a ramen connoisseur.
The ramen I eat...
...will be decided by me.
That was good.
Of course.
Since you've eaten...
...you will help out too.
Why must we help out?
Right?
Hey... what are you?
Earlier, I was attacked by a strange thing...
...then I was saved by another strange thing.
That was... you wasn't it?
I don't know what you mean.
So that belt was yours?
Belt?
It's not mine.
Then it was Tendou's.
No.
Right, right. His belt is different from mine.
I don't know what to say!
It sure is raining a lot.
Enough.
Dad.
Mom.
I... don't like myself.
I'm sure I will be alone again.
Tendou...
Kagami...
They always help me...
But...
Since my memory isn't clear...
...I always suspect those two.
But actually...
I don't want to think that way.
Kagami.
Your parents, Hiyori?
The Shibuya meteorite wasn't it?
No.
They were murdered.
Mom.
Dad.
That...
...boy wearing the belt
killed my parents. I'm sure of it.
I see.
So that's why when you saw my belt...
But that wasn't me.
As for the belt, it was made recently.
There's no way it'd exist seven years ago...
Sorry, but I've had a long
relationship with the belt.
Tendou...
When did he get that belt?
And why does he have it in the first place?
What is it, Jiiya?
A parade to see me?
Please eat.
It's the best ramen.
Everyone, please get in line!
When the soup is out we're done!
R-right. It's a parade, is it not?
No!
It isn't.
In front of the line is a mysterious coach.
What is that?!
That is not a coach. It's called a cart.
The people get in line to eat ramen.
La Men.
French cuisine? I would like to taste it.
I cannot allow it.
Did you forget the noblesse oblige?
The high class must behave in a high class manner.
Noblesse oblige.
What a beautiful ring it has.
Tadokoro, what's this?
Lately all the women attacked by the
Worm have the same kind of rock.
Please investigate it.
Okay.
La Men.
I am the man who stands at the top of cuisines.
There's no way I won't eat.
You're...
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"It is enjoyable to eat something delicious..."
"...but the greatest joy is the
time spent waiting for it."
If you want to eat, then properly get in line.
Yeah! He's right!
Yeah!
I am the man that stands
at the top of standing in line.
It's pretty lively.
I'd like to try a full course of La Men!
Handmade bug slice noodle?
What?
A Worm wants to make an order?
The challenge to a duel...
...I cordially accept!
Run.
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
That stone...
Hiyori has the same stone.
What are you doing?
It's just a pebble.
Hey...
Did you have that belt seven years ago?
If so, then the young man
with the belt that Hiyori...
You have no idea what you're talking about.
Just how did you obtain that belt?!
Why did you have the belt
before the Masked Rider Project?!
I was given it.
By who?
Don't joke!
Hey!
I've been waiting.
Shall we?
The stone analysis is in.
It is a piece of the Shibuya meteorite.
What?!
This case might be out of our hands.
What do you mean?
Don't let Kagami know.
This chain of Worms are attacking those
who have a piece of the Shibuya meteorite.
That stone...
Hiyori is in danger!
Hurry up and run! I'll defeat him!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Why do this?
Throwing a glove is a challenge to a duel.
If the opponent picks it up, the duel is official.
Let's go.
Clock Up!
CLOCK UP
RIDER CUTTING
CLOCK OVER
What was that technique?
This high class conduct.
Without a doubt, noblesse oblige.
Is that stone really that important?
This stone is...
Sympathy...
...the greatest insult!
STANDBY
Henshin!
HENSHIN
What a troublesome fellow.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
You plan to enter the ruins of Shibuya?
He seems to be interested in Area X.
The key to everything is in Shibuya
Just what are they hiding?!
That is my... noblesse oblige.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.
Rider Double Kick!
It's been 35 years since the Kamen Rider's birth.
Our fellow Riders continue their battles.
This is the V3 Kick.
The X Kick.
And Super-1 has ten different kick attacks.
The Kick is each generation of
Rider's greatest finishing move.
Alright, me too.
Rider Kick!
By the way...
Who are you?!