MAXIMUM HYPER CYCLONE
Peek.
Peek peek.
Why do you only let me have a glimpse?
Today's recipe is sushi with scattered toppings.
Peek.
This is it?
It's fantastic!
Next time, I want to try
sushi with assertive toppings.
Hiyori... Right now you are there.
And...
...him.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Peek. Peek peek.
Master. Would you please evaluate my meal?
It's great!
All right! At last Master acknowledges me!
Are you okay?
Somehow that doesn't seem like you.
Where's your usual arrogant attitude?
Hey. Where am I right now?
You're here.
No! The other me. Do you know where he is?
Why are you asking?
I'm going to eliminate him.
But forget it if you don't know.
Could it be that just now...
A Worm mimicking Tendou.
Stop!
Tendou!
You're the real one, aren't you?
Of course. Who do you think I am?
He who walks the path of heaven...
I know! I know!
My mimic?
I see. So it's him.
And you led him here.
I was followed?
Give Hiyori back.
No way. Hiyori doesn't
want to see you anymore.
Like I'd trust your words!
It's not a lie. Hiyori told me so.
She told me to erase you.
Hiyori said that about me?
You're full of it!
Talk!
How did you come to this world
from the edge of time and space?!
There's no need for you to know.
Because... you'll be erased from this world.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Then I'll force you to tell me.
Kagami!
Don't interfere!
You can't beat me.
Hiyori and I will live for eternity
at the edge of time and space.
You can't reach Hiyori.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
You never will.
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Tendou!
Why didn't you attack?
ONE TWO THREE
Disappear.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Rider Kick!
Tendou!
Hey! Pull yourself together!
Where's my mimic?
Shook him off somehow.
Hey, Tendou! Why didn't you fight back?
He...
...was the one with Hiyori at
the edge of time and space.
Then he took Hiyori and fled?
Despite that... he's appeared in this world.
In other words...
There must be some exit from the
edge of time and space to this world.
He's the only one who knows that.
It can't be... That's why...
Yes?
It's the Worms. Hurry.
Understood.
Tendou. Get out of here. Okay?
The Worms are coming!
We need backup!
Put some distance in between you!
Pull back the front line!
Gatack is here.
So many...!
I bid you well.
Foolish ZECT members.
And the even more foolish Gatack.
You!
Didn't Kabuto kill you?
You can be food.
Weaklings are my food!
Didn't I say so? Weaklings are my food!
He even kills from his own side?
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
No...
Why was he able to do...
...a Rider Kick?
He's the only path to Hiyori.
But he would never tell me the way.
I...
What should I do?
This ZECT team is too small.
Worms have appeared at various locations.
Just what are they after?
You scumbag!
How boring.
Hurry up and summon the Riders.
Do you want to be my food that badly?
Take your filthy hands off her!
Tsurugi!
Misakinu!
Someone who might amuse me a bit has come.
Stay away!
I will defeat all Worm!
STANDBY
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Then all Riders...
...will be defeated by me.
Sir! Are you okay?
What's the situation?
As expected, Gatack's defeat was a large one.
The Worm attacks only become more fierce.
No.
This is no time for me to rest.
No, Sir.
That Worm can copy all techniques that hit it.
If you attack blindly you'll just lose.
Renge is right.
Tendou.
I heard about the situation from Misaki.
You take it easy for now.
Renge, can I have a moment?
Okay.
Rider Slash!
RIDER SLASH
No! Don't use your technique!
What?
Rider Slash!
Misaki! Misaki! Are you okay?
That Worm can really copy
any technique, as we thought.
I am the man that stands at the top
of everything, I will win next time.
More importantly... it's my
fault that Misakinu got hurt.
Right now, you cannot defeat that Worm.
Face reality.
Reality?
I'm not Misakinu. I'm Misaki.
The entrace to the edge of time and space?
Yes.
I want you to find where the entrance is.
But... How?
When my mimic defeats me... It will
definitely return to the edge of time and space.
That's when you act.
You being defeated?
This enemy is me.
So acting and little tricks won't work.
If I don't return...
If that happens tell Kagami that location.
I don't believe it...
I'm counting on you.
However...
Keep all that a secret from Kagami. Okay?
Tendou, the soup stock is done.
Let's see.
Here.
Try getting more good flavor from the sea kelp.
Okay. I understand.
But... Why the sudden interest
in teaching me to cook?
You've always said that
you've wanted to learn, right?
Now. Let me show you how to boil rice.
Okay!
What's wrong?
No. Nothing.
Hiyori.
No need to suffer anymore.
Because I will erase him.
What's with the serious look?
Henshin.
HENSHIN
What?!
Tendou is going to lose to his mimic on purpose?
Right.
It's so he can find the entrance
to the edge of time and space.
No...
That guy!
Third platoon. Formation B! Move to location four!
First platoon move to point five!
Seventh platoon back them up. Evacuate the wounded!
Those bastards... are headeed to Area Z
What's there?
Development...
...for the Masked Rider System.
Then at this rate... the Masked Rider System
will fall into the hands of the Worms?
Those guys.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Tendou!
Why did you do that?!
I will defeat your mimic.
Stop!
I have to die to save Hiyori!
And I... have to do nothing
and watch you be killed?!
Are you such a small man?
From amoeba to humans...
Don't you protect all life forms on Earth?
It's because you're such a big guy...
...that I want to surpass you!
Tendou!
You truly are an interesting fellow.
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"I am the center of the world."
"So... I will save the world!"
Henshin!
HENSHIN
I will defeat you.
And save Hiyori.
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Yaguruma! Kageyama!
You came!
Tadokoro... I envy you.
Always surrounded by your
cute subordinates. Seems so fun.
Do you guys feel like leading Shadow again?
If you want to...
That's... TheBee Brace!
I'm enjoying the infinite pitch black Hell.
Let's all fall together.
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
You're good... but just...
...a copy of the old me.
I already hold the future in my hand.
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
That's...
KABUTO POWER
THEBEE POWER
DRAKE POWER
SASWORD POWER
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
It's ten-thousand years too
soon for you to copy me.
Now... Take me to where Hiyori is.
Hiyori!
Why did you come to this world too?
There's no reason for you two to fight.
I've already made my decision.
I'm never returning to this world again.
Why?
Hiyori, what are you saying?!
This is what will make me happy.
See?
Hiyori and I will live outside this world.
Just the two of us.
Don't be ridiculous! He's a Worm!
Stay away!
Hiyori...
You...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
ZECT members! You're too weak,
not worthy to be my food.
Please protect it... my world.
I'll destroy it... this world!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.