Watch in a well-lit room away from the TV.
Kamen Rider Kabuto : Hyper Battle DVD!
The birth of Gatack Hyper Form!
Hyper Kick!
RIDER KICK
So cool!
Right?
Alright...
I'm also getting a Hyper Form.
Now come, Hyper Zecter!
What are you doing?
Hyper Zecter belongs to Kabuto.
Only Tendou can use it.
I see.
Tendou, eh?
If I could be Tendou...
Yo.
Tendou!
I...
...want to be you!
Impossible.
Give up on it.
Wait, don't say that.
The secret to becoming Tendou, eh?
Alright. I'll teach you!
Tendou Souji's Five Secrets!
One, cooking.
Tendou is good at cooking.
Prepare the inside rare.
You can prepare this quickly and gracefully.
Try it.
Alright...
Wow!
This is no good.
The training's really starting from step one.
Right...
Two.
Be kind to your sibling.
Big Bro, good morning!
Good morning!
Today, you can call me "Big Brother".
That's... kind of weird.
A cockroach!
Cockroach?!
Juka... leave this to your big brother!
Cockroach!
Over there, Kagami!
There! There! There!
Hey, hey. You're not acting smart enough.
If it were Tendou...
Henshin!
He would do it gracefully and elegantly.
Because the world revolves around him.
CAST OFF
Just look at this confident fighting style.
And I, Kabuto Zecter,
like that kind of confidence.
Kabuto's finisher attack, Avalanche Smash!
Using it in Kunai Mode, he cuts the Worm up!
Yes. The various personalities
are the good parts of the Riders.
Henshin!
The wasp Rider, TheBee, is a leader type.
He has to be competent in leading during battle.
His creed is Perfect Harmony.
The Zecter chooses
qualified humans to be Riders.
If you only think about yourself,
TheBee Zecter will abandon you.
TheBee's finisher attack is Rider Sting.
RIDER STING
"Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee."
Henshin!
Drake is a dragonfly Rider.
Like the wind, he loves freedom.
Although it seems like he
loves things besides freedom.
He's also good at underwater fighting.
Dragonfly larvae live underwater, after all.
And he handles guns splendidly.
RIDER SHOOTING
Drake's finisher attack, Rider Shooting.
He's okay even if the Worm is far away.
Henshin!
Sasword is a scorpion Rider.
No matter what, he reaches the top.
Although, he also masters weird things.
Sasword's finisher attack, Rider Slash.
RIDER SLASH
With the sharp sword, he cuts down Worms.
A noble deed must be nobly returned.
Noblesse Oblige.
And he has a secret.
Henshin!
Grasshopper Rider, KickHopper.
A Rider revived from Hell.
KickHopper's finisher attack,
Rider Jump and Kick.
What destructive force!
Mr. Yaguruma, just what happened?
The Hopper Zecter's back color
is different. He's reversible.
Henshin!
Gatack is the stag beetle Rider.
His finisher attack is Rider Cutting.
RIDER CUTTING
He uses Double Caliber to cut Worms in half!
What's Gatack's characteristic?
No matter what, doing one's
best to be straightforward...
...I suppose?
Man! Cockroach?! Just where are you?!
How cheeky!
Straightforward, isn't he?
Do something about him.
Big Brother... is fighting!
I'll beat everyone up.
Big Brother...?
Big Brother...
Good morning!
Good morning...
Three.
Listen to your grandmother's
or grandfather's words.
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"If I wish for it, fate will always be my ally."
My grandfather once said...
"Arata! Why don't you call?!"
What?
What happened?
Four, fashion sense.
Looking good in all clothes.
He's sharp in any clothes he wears.
How cool!
I also want to try on various clothes.
Ta-da!
This is needed for undercover work.
And looking good daily is a good attitude.
Not bad.
Ta-da!
It's hard to look good in everything.
And five. Fighting smart and stylish.
Now, try it.
My grandfather once said...
"Oh..."
"...my legs hurt."
Hey, hey. Is he okay?
My head hurts.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Alright! Finisher attack, finisher attack!
ONE TWO THREE
What is he doing?
Isn't he imitating Kabuto
and trying to do a counter kick?
Oh, watch out!
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
So lame...
Alright, one more time!
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
No!
That's it...
I'm Kagami Arata.
Not Tendou.
I... am me!
That's right, Kagami.
You did well to realize that.
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"There is nothing wrong with imitating a person..."
"... as long as it's to find out who you really are."
Two Hyper Zecters?
Hyper Zecter can travel through time.
A Hyper Zecter from the future has come.
Yeah, I asked him to come.
Let's go!
Kagami, you should grab onto the future too!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
CHANGE BEETLE
Alright!
Hyper Cast Off!
Hyper Cast Off.
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
CHANGE HYPER STAG BEETLE
HYPER CLOCK UP
Hyper Clock Up!
MAXIMUM RIDER POWER
ONE TWO THREE
Hyper Kick!
RIDER KICK
He who walks the path of heaven...
...will rule over everything.
There can only be one me in this world.
Yep... There's also only one of me.
I won't copy you anymore, but...
I wish I had a cool quote too.
I thought of one for you.
Try reading it.
Alright.
Every morning, before a mirror,
the man who washes his face.
Kagami Arata.
Mirror (Kagami)
Washed (Aratta)
That's lame!
Don't tell me... you don't wash your face?
I do wash my face!
Those two are fighting again.
Don't mock me!
That means they're good friends.
There's also only one of you in this world.
Don't forget that.
Keep cheering for us.
Later!
I can't beat you in the smelly department.