My grandmother once said...
"Fighting is something done from the stomach."
Put your gut into it!
It can't be....
I don't believe it....
Tendou...
Why are you...?!
Just what is going on?
There!
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Tendou!
What is it?
If you leave your mouth gaping
open like that bugs will get inside.
Why are you a part of Shadow?
What's going on?!
You joined ZECT as Kabuto, didn't you?
No.
No one knows I'm Kabuto.
I became Shadow's captain
by being Tendou Soujirou.
Is that possible?!
Who do you think I am?
It is I.
Greater than all the world's
population of six billion people...
I'm number one.
With my excellence, ZECT decided
I could have anything I wanted.
That's how it is.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
I'm worried about Tendou,
but we have to solve this first.
Wakabayashi Tatsuhiro.
He's a famous surgeon at
Serenity South General Hospital.
Out of the two Wakabayashi, one has to be a Worm.
But why doesn't the Worm try to kill the real one?
And there are more mysteries.
While we both were watching the two Wakabayashis'
a Worm using the same method attacked a person.
In other words the two Wakabayashi have an alibi.
Perhaps they're just humans?
Like identical twins.
That's not the case. I checked.
Where are you going?!
Are you planning to do it alone again?!
I'm still on vacation. What I do is up to me, right?
Still hurt about being used as bait?
Of course!
Not only used, I was almost killed!
It's like a denial of everything I am!
More ice cream please.
Unless I show I can do
something. I won't be satisfied.
Kagami.
Lately you've been missing work too much.
I know.
So you're really dissatisfied?
Of course!
I've showed my worth as Shadow's leader.
So what's with this Tendou guy?!
ZECT is a collection of powerful people.
It's true you are chosen by TheBee.
Your power is valued.
But his leadership is greater than yours.
This was the result from various data.
Understand?
But!
Just who is he?!
Can we trust him?
That is none of your concern.
He is a first rate human.
We search for such people.
That's all I can say.
Do not waste my time!
So...
Now we will split up and
follow the targets. As well as...
We will begin an investigation.
My grandmother once said...
"Work is as sticky as natto"
Understand?
Right.
Where's your reply, Kageyama?
I can't hear you!
One more time.
Right!
Delicious!
So, what operation did you do today?
Labor problems.
I see. Good work.
Good work.
What?!
What are you saying?!
I'm saying you should join ZECT.
If you join now, I'll let you be
my subordinate. You'll like it.
I refuse.
No one can catch the wind.
And what a surprise to see you join ZECT.
I'm saying this for your sake. Think it over.
As long as you're a Rider and alone,
ZECT and the Worms will target you.
How long can a flirt like you endure?
I see now.
You just joined ZECT because
you were afraid for your life.
I misjudged you. How disappointing.
That and...
This.
What?
What's next?
This.
What?!
The orange.
Yes yes, that that.
Hey... you're...
Hello!
You're by yourself today?
Yup. Daisuke and I need private time after all.
What about your father and mother?
I don't have any. But that's okay, I have Daisuke.
Gon.
Excuse me. Was Gon a bother in any way?
Gon... Strange name.
Yup. I had no name so I came up with Gon.
Isn't it cute?
You have no name?
More importantly, definitely let
me do your make up sometime.
Even a goddess would bow before your beauty.
You are truly...
Daisuke, you really will take
any woman won't you?
That's amazing.
I suppose.
You're...
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Gon.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Riders that don't join ZECT must be eliminated.
That's the captain's orders!
It can't be! He...
Daisuke!
Those in my way...
...should destroy each other.
You!
What's wrong with you?
You're scum y'know that?
Having your subordinate try to kill me...
No, Daisuke. If he wanted to
kill you, he'd do it himself.
That's the kind of person he is.
You have excellent perception.
That is right.
But... it's a fact your subordinate attacked me!
Aren't you responsible for
those under your command?!
Now that you mention it, you're right.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Forgive me.
What? You're acting so docile.
I think I understand the situation.
I'll have my subordinate apologize directly.
I'm sorry.
This good enough?
Well, he did apologize earnestly. So I'm okay.
Good man.
But I will not be satisfied with this.
Kageyama. As punishment,
wash this restaurant's dishes.
Why go that far?
You be quiet.
Kagami, show him.
Show him how to wash dishes.
That's no good, Kageyama.
You have to wash it thoroughly.
See. There are still some dirty spots.
You don't leave me any choice.
Kageyama! After you finish that, return to work.
I have something you have to do.
Okay.
Sincerity South General Hospital
Wakabayashi is the same again today.
I guess.
Looks like nothing's wrong.
Hold on!
Look.
Next.
What's wrong?
Um umm...
My stomach hurts and...
My eyes hurt and...
My head hurts...
Let's do a thorough examination.
Doctor Tendouji.
Huh?
Understood.
I will...
...take a thorough look.
Hey, Tendou!
What's going on here?!
I'm doing undercover investigation just like you.
Speaking of which.
Even I couldn't get into a
hospital as easily as this.
ZECT is quite powerful.
And?! That's why you're doing
a thorough examination on me?!
Here....
...you need an operation.
What'd you say?!
Believe in me. Nothing bad will happen.
Delicious!
What what what?
Hello?
What?!
An emergency operation?!
I'll be right there.
I wonder if it's the patient I just saw?
Who should go?
I'll go.
Just what is Tendou thinking?!
And... what is my fate?
Wakabayashi, are you okay?!
Give me the usual.
Okay.
Alright!
Scalpel.
Here.
Hey. Wait!
Doctor.
I made an incorrect diagnosis.
This patient is healthy.
Although his personality has a problem.
What?
Hey, Tendou! What are you doing?!
Hey!
You're the real Wakabayashi.
You're not a Worm.
Y-you are?
The result of the investigation showed you
had a habit the other Wakabayashis didn't.
Before the operation you'd
have the nurse fill you with spirit.
Will you talk with me?
A deal? With a Worm?
Yes.
P-please!
Let me live!
I have many patients!
I must save them!
Please let them live!
I don't care what happens to me!
Okay.
I'll grant your wish.
So such strange Worms exist.
And...?
I was surprised.
They looked just like me, and...
...they had the same doctor skills as me.
So... they were a great help.
Since then we'd switch off.
Unbelievable!
But...
We still lacked hands.
So... the Worm pretending to be you called
its comrades and they also mimicked you?
We've reached the time limit.
As promised, we are taking it...
...your life!
There are four?!
You sure are a busy person.
But thanks to that we had quite a hard time.
It was difficult to investigate
them all simultaneously.
It can't be...
You joined ZECT to do that?
These hands have saved many humans.
We can and will save many more.
Rubbish. If you attack them
then this is pointless.
My grandmother once said...
"The whisper of the devil can sometimes
sound like the voice of an angel."
You may be strange Worms,
but in the end, Worms none the less.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Transform!
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE DRAGONFLY
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Rider Shooting.
RIDER SHOOTING
CLOCK OVER
You won't get away!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Clock Up!
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Mishima.
Allow me to demonstrate...
...how to truly fight.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
I can... do it!
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Pay close attention. This occurs in the instant between the
discharge of Kagami's gun and the bullets hitting the Worm.
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
I did it.
Mishima.
I did it!
All on my own.
I defeated a Worm...
I did it!
Alright! Did you see that, Worm?!
Really...
What an interesting fellow.
Mishima...
Please don't abandon me.
Please! Please!
Do not worry.
You are still TheBee's chosen one.
And you're back as Shadow's leader.
Really?!
What about that Tendou Sojirou guy?
He's gone missing.
It's disappointing but it can't be helped.
More importantly... I have a new job for you.
Okay...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Gon. Cut it out!
Don't get in the way, get out!
So your memory's back?
This man is scum. He's an insensitive man who
doesn't understand the feelings of children.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.