Begin the experiment.
We should stop it!
Ignore it.
That is the man, Gatack Zecter has chosen.
Many subjects have lost their lives already.
So far, Gatack has not chosen any of the subjects.
However... Gatack is the pivotal
point for the Masked Rider Project.
We cannot give up now.
You know of Abraham, correct?
Yes.
He, to lead a new religion of God...
...went as far as to take his child...
...and sacrifice his life.
In other words...
Even your son...
...you are prepared to offer your son as a subject?
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Tendou!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Today's breakfast is stir fry crab, bacon, egg, and...
Minestrone.
The beans in this soup seem well done.
These beans are good!
Excellent perception, Juka.
When I cooked the beans...
First cover in olive oil...
...then remove the shell.
By the way, do you know what day tomorrow is?
Of course!
Tomorrow...
...the people of the world
will celebrate your birthday.
Tsurugi, Young Master
Birthday Celebration
Last year was so fun. Mika, she...
Let us do something different this year.
How about a birthday party outside?
No Entrance
The Worm is in there...
That's very probable from
the eyewitness accounts.
Yes?
Tadokoro has been hospitalized?!
Understood.
Is Tadokoro okay?
How is he?
I'll go for now.
You continue standing watch.
Who's there?!
Oh... sorry.
I see.
The neighbors asked you to investigate?
Actually I've experienced it too.
Umm... by a stray cat.
A stray cat?!
Yeah.
It eventually caused the
operations to get canceled.
I understand.
That's what I'll report.
Mister, this way!
Hurry!
You're late.
What?
Were you waiting for me?
Ms. Yumiko is sick, so she took the day off.
So...
Today you're the chef.
"So..." what? You can just do the cooking.
Yumiko gave the burden to you.
But I won't be responsible...
...if the restaurant suddenly
becomes really intense.
Thank you.
You really saved me.
Hey... do you have water?
Food?
Sorry... don't have any.
What the heck...
Tsk... I save him and this is how it turns out.
Come to think about it...
...I do have candy.
Have you been hiding here the whole time?
Makoto.
That's my name.
I see... so your father is a
live-in guard at this factory?
But... that day I saw it!
Weird monsters were attacking people!
Despite that... no one believes me...
Everyone kept making those scary faces...
Even my dad...
I found this room while running around.
I see...
You did really well all by yourself.
But it's fine now.
I'll help you escape.
No!
I've tried it a bunch of times already!
There are so many of those monsters!
Believe me!
No! Weren't you totally helpless earlier?!
Well...
Mika...
Mika!
That dream again?
This smell...
It might be food worthy of my eating.
Excellent senses, Young Master.
Jii was also wondering that for awhile.
That's a nice telescope.
My dream is to see a Moonbow with this.
"Moonbow"?
It's a rainbow made of moonlight.
They say if you see one...
...it'll bring you happiness.
I hope you see it someday.
But there's no way I can see it here.
Hey...
You can't do anything here.
Let's be brave and go outside.
I'll definitely protect you, Makoto.
Mister!
Return to that room!
I'll come back and save you!
It's a promise!
That guy...
...from before...
This unflattering room is
some kind of store house?
No. This is a dining place
for the working class.
The smell from before
was from this restaurant.
But perhaps... this place is
inappropriate for you?
No.
I've always wanted to
try a regular man's flavors.
I understand.
Hey.
There's a weirdo here.
What?
Well look who it is, it's the Young Master.
You mimicked me?!
Kageyama!
Big trouble! There are Worms
in the factory up ahead!
I know!
We were already investigating!
Because you entered without permission,
they're now aware of our activity!
I apologize about that. But there's a child inside!
We've got to hurry and save him!
Rubbish.
That's a Worm.
No...
There are only Worms left in that factory.
Makoto is...
...a Worm?
I don't believe Makoto is a Worm.
We should save him right away!
Your opinion has already
been sent to headquarters.
But the fact is that factory is a Worm nest.
And they are hiding something
that they don't want known.
Headquarters has already given
orders to have the factory destroyed.
Destroyed...
I cannot accept that!
Kagami.
It's time for your part-time job, right?
This is no time for that!
Go!
And... don't come back.
Tadokoro...
Tadokoro sure is kind...
Do you know why he's hurt?
Who are you?
Headquarters ordered him
to produce a test subject...
To keep his cute underlings out of danger...
...he sent himself as test material
He got hurt that way...
You're with the organization?
Just what experiment was it?
An experiment for becoming the new Rider... Gatack.
A new Rider...
Gatack?!
If we can make him, he will probably
be ZECT's most powerful Rider.
Powerful enough to take on a Worm nest... alone.
Kagami!
Jiiya.
This flavor is similar to Jiiya's.
Excuse me.
I see.
But this lacks a single flavor to suit you.
Are you okay with him using it himself?
His hand mannerisms show he is no ordinary cook.
Jiiya's cooking truly is the best.
Your compliments are wasted on me.
Which reminds me, I've been
worried about the soup...
Let's see.
It's so fine.
It's the first time I've tasted this.
Hiyori made that.
I will give you this honor...
Make the food for my birthday celebration.
Why me?
I refus...
It's a position sought by
chefs around the world.
You'll treasure it for the rest of your life.
He's so casual... eating and
running away without paying...
This flavor!
That old man...
It can't be...
Stop it!
Are you just going to waste
Tadokoro's sacrifice for you?!
Let me go!
There's someone waiting for me to save him.
Kagami!
I need your power.
Now come...
Gatack Zecter!
Kagami!
Hang on!
Can you hear me?
Kagami!
Hang on!
I can't figure it out!
What flavor did he add?
What?
Kagami is badly hurt?
He was mimicked by a Worm.
He acted rashly to protect a boy from that Worm.
I need you to lend me your power.
I refuse.
Tendou?!
Hello?! Hello?!
What's wrong with him?!
Foolish Kagami... always causing trouble...
He was so careless with his life...
You!
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"Once you know the real thing...
you won't be fooled by an imitation."
A Worm that would mimic hasty Kagami...
...will definitely come to eliminate the original.
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
'Operation Shut Down Notice'
Take your positions!
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I... can only be myself.
But... I am who I am.
Naive... as usual.
Henshin!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.