Cast Off.
CAST OFF
There's no reason for you two to fight! Stop it!
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
Kabuto!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Isn't that enough?!
My mission is to eliminate Kabuto.
Eliminate?!
You can't be serious!
The Masked Rider system belongs to ZECT alone.
Now move.
I'll be breaking your belt. Don't begrudge me.
Tendou!
This is also for the Perfect Harmony
of the organization.
Y-you!
To escape from further harm....
...it was best to play dead.
It was fake, I didn't die.
You scumbag!
Don't scare me!
I really thought you were dead.
That's...
Don't tell me you...
Back there...
Hey...
Tendou?
Hey!
Hang on!
Tendou!
Man...
Tendou sure is late.
I wonder if something's happened to him?
You know him.
I'm sure he's okay.
You're right!
It's my brother after all!
I really like your drawings, Miss Hiyori!
I'm sure they're pretty poorly done.
No. That's not true.
When I look at them...
I feel all warm inside.
Warm...?
Yeah!
Could it be the person in this picture...
...is a person who saved you. Miss Hiyori?
It's Tendou!
Hello?
Kagami?
My brother was...?
Where's Tendou?
It's pretty serious isn't it?
Yes.
It seems pretty serious.
It's pretty bad right now.
Okay.
You need to relax more.
Yo!
I think the examination is over.
Moron! You're the one that needs to be seen.
I'm doing great.
You always overreact.
You shouldn't say that!
Kagami is the only person who
worries about you like this.
Alright... I'll stop embarrassing Kagami.
Hiyori.
Prepare for supper.
Why me?
Kagami.
Ingredients.
Why me?
We should have curry rice.
Okay.
Asegawa.
Yes.
Kashmir curry!
Kashmir?
Kashmir.
Thai curry?
Whatever.
Excellent job, Yaguruma.
It was nothing.
Kabuto didn't appear did he?
Don't you think TheBee can
handle things by himself?
No...
I didn't mean it that way.
I have defeated Kabuto.
He was the organization's
enemy in the first place.
Good work.
There only needs to be one Rider.
Really?
You finally got Kabuto?
I knew you could do it, Yaguruma.
I've destroyed the belt.
He will never appear again.
This looks delicious.
It is!
Isn't it?
Umm...
Is it okay if I go back now?
What's wrong with you?
You've been rude all this time.
Nothing....
Do you have a problem being here or something?
Not really...
Now.
Please get in line.
Stay in order. Please head to my brother.
Private Room
Lord Tendou Souji
Oh, please wait a bit more.
Please stay in order.
Don't worry, there's plenty.
Here you go.
It's hot, so please be careful.
Should you be doing this without permission?
My grandmother once said...
"Sickness occurs because of the food."
You can't spell great without 'eat'.
Excellent work, Tendou. I heartily concur.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Misaki?
Misaki, you're worried about
Tendou as well. Aren't you?
Wasn't he defeated by TheBee?
He was, but...
What?
By the way...
That nurse outfit looks pretty good on...
Come this way.
What?!
Just come with me.
What is it?
I was trying to stop the battle
between TheBee and Kabuto.
But then...
There's no reason for you two to fight!
Please stop!
So, TheBee won by taking advantage of the
opening Kabuto gave while saving you?
Probably.
Kagami!
You bastard!
Are you really Yaguruma's subordinate?!
Are you trying to insult your superior?!
Hey.
That... wasn't really an insult.
Then why don't you believe in Yaguruma?!
I'm sure Yaguruma beat Kabuto
without such cowardly ways!
I saw it!
Shut up!
Stop it.
Yaguruma.
Don't be so emotional.
If you do that your Perfect Harmony,
your ultimate connection, will be lost.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
It's the Worms.
Destroy them.
Leave it to me.
It's the Worms isn't it?
I'm going too.
No.
Kagami.
Yes?
Let's return to the hospital.
It'll be okay.
He can't transform anymore.
Hey!
We... fight as a team.
Kageyama...
We still might need Kabuto's power....
I'm glad everyone was pleased.
Yes.
So...
Why don't we leave the hospital?
Okay!
Hey!
Please!
Don't kill!
Stop it!
Hiyori?
What is it?
What is that?
This is...
How do I put this?
It's important.
Is it yours?
Yeah.
Well...
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
What are you planning to do with my belt?
Tendou...
I'm going to have Misaki repair it.
My way of thanking you for saving me.
I don't remember asking for your help.
And what needs repairing?
It's fixed!
Does it have the ability to repair itself?
In my long association with
the belt, it has no such ability.
Since it's fixed...
It's the Worms. Please come.
Are you planning to follow that Yaguruma guy?
I'm not like you.
The team's Perfect Harmony will defeat the Worms.
That's where I belong.
The moving, hard work of the regular man?
You really are a piece of something...
Forget it! Go home and take a nap!
Still a funny guy.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
All platoons, stay away from the enemy.
It's molting.
Find the most advantageous point and herd them!
Roger!
Platoon A, open the right side.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Yaguruma!
Kageyama!
That guy...
Why are you...?!
Transform.
TRANSFORM
He transformed?!
That's not possible!
Captain!
Are you planning to let your subordinates die?
I will defeat you.
I have to defeat you.
If I don't...
...I'll lose myself!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Are you okay?!
Kagami...
Gotta keep trying...
Kagami, that's enough.
At least you can get away!
Shut up!
I'm not going to lose.
I'm not going to lose!
We should fall back.
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
You'll regret this...
You'll regret becoming a Rider!
You are the one who'll regret it.
What?!
Disappear!
You have strayed from your path.
What?!
CLOCK OVER
Please wait, TheBee Zecter!
Come back!
Yaguruma!
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick...
RIDER KICK
Hang on!
Protect the wounded!
Roger.
I'm going to protect everyone!
I will protect them!
That's...
TheBee Zecter.
I'm going to... defeat all of you!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Now I'll work with Tendou to defeat the Worms.
The first orders for the new TheBee.
Defeat Kabuto.
A bee is one that stings.
A bee that does not sting... is worthless!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.