Seven years ago, on that day...
Because of a tiny speck that fell from space...
...I became alone.
The city of Shibuya became a mountain of rubble.
And in my heart...
...a tiny hole was opened.
But...
That speck from space...
...wasn't all that came down.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
It's okay.
I'm by your side.
I am...
...by your side.
It's the Worm.
The location...
...Kouan area C-3
Send the Zectroopers.
We'll also be right there.
Camera.
Check.
Clear.
Platoon A.
Keep going at thirty degrees.
Formation Alpha.
No life signals detected.
C Platoon, go inside.
Advancing to point two.
Way to point two clear.
No jamming signals.
Ok.
Platoon E.
Back up Platoon A.
Formation Beta.
Guard's death, confirmed.
Platoon X.
Surround.
Platoon C.
Prepare for battle.
Fire!
I'm sorry!
You're late, Kagami.
All the levels are rising.
Back away and focus your attack.
The number of Worms have increased.
Still no data.
Thermo level 384 degrees Kelvin and increasing.
Gravity level 240.
It's molting.
Defeat them before they Clock Up.
They vanished.
Retreat.
Add, six wounded.
Calm down.
Use a gas bomb to cover your escape.
H-hang on a second!
We're retreating.
The Worm have stopped.
Wounded, six.
Dead...
...twenty one.
Tadokoro.
'No roaring engines. Babies are sleeping'
Stop!
Get back!
I'll stab you!
Calm down!
I'll kill you, I swear!
Alright! Alright!
Move!
Watch out! Run!
That was close!
Why didn't you run?!
Hey!
No one can stab me.
What?!
I will decide what path I will walk.
And one more thing...
If I clumsily dodged... my
precious tofu would crumble.
Really?
Luck isn't always going to save you!
If things went wrong, you might have been stabbed!
Don't mention things like "good luck" around me.
First of all, such a knife cannot kill me.
You forgot something.
That's my wallet!
Who are you?
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"He who walks the path of heaven..."
"...will rule over everything."
My name is...
Tendou...
Souji.
Big Brother, good morning!
Good morning.
Big Brother, today's breakfast looks so good!
Save that line for after you've eaten it.
Let's eat!
Delicious!
You changed the soup stock didn't you?
You noticed!
Changing the miso broth is an important point.
But...
I'm grateful that you cook for me like this, but...
...shouldn't you go to school, or get a job?
I'm busy with preparations.
That again?
And just what are these preparations for?
I don't know either.
So... I wait here like this.
But...
...that time will definitely...
...come.
That's the only thing I'm sure about.
I don't really get it...
But whatever.
Big Bro, what you say is never wrong. Right?!
The next train will be arriving at platform five.
Please stand behind the line.
Yes?
Hello?
I have it.
You can return.
Excuse me?
You weren't followed right?
Of course, I made sure of it.
So what's that?
No need for you to know yet.
That's weird.
But right now I'm a ZECT member.
It's fine.
Show him.
It's our first anti-Worm secret weapon.
Then... it's finally complete?
The Masked Rider System.
Tadokoro.
Please let me use it.
Please.
He's not your dad, he's not
going to spoil you with a Zecter.
That doesn't matter.
Someone qualified to wear the Rider Belt...
...will soon be sent from headquarters.
Yo.
How long do you plan to make me wait?
But... I wanna go home.
For real.
Wanna go eat?
Okay!
I know a good restaurant.
You are not worthy of being shop owners.
Your customer is waiting all
this time for you to finish talking
Poor thing.
Where does it hurt?
So you have trouble talking to people...
...but no trouble talking to machines?
You didn't get a puncture, but the front is heavy.
It's because of the tank bag.
In here is a guy that's the hope for all humanity.
It's a lighter load than me.
Hiyori!
You're going to the restaurant, right?
I'll give you a ride.
I have this.
Who was that?
A friend?
It's the guard that was killed the other day.
Should we surround him?
No.
This is all we cops can do.
What do you mean?
Well, I don't know the details either...
But it seems the higher-ups are in
contact with an organization that is acting.
What's going on?!
What's wrong?
It's a Worm.
The Zectroopers are already on the way.
This time make sure...
...they are eliminated.
Roger.
Misaki.
The person from headquarters...
He hasn't contacted us yet.
I don't believe it...
It's finally awoken.
Platoon A, Formation Alpha.
Target 3-2-4.
Fire!
Hiyori?
Please stop!
Your fire will hit her too!
Hey!
It's molting.
Aim at the target!
Tadokoro!
Please let me use the Masked Rider System!
I beg you!
No.
We don't have permission from headquarters.
But at this rate...
Tadokoro, please let me do this!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Let me use the Masked Rider System!
Kagami!
Calm down!
Please!
Cut it out!
Kagami!
I will talk to headquarters.
I am entrusting the Rider System to you.
I won't forgive you.
I will defeat all you damn Worms.
Every last one!
The chosen one...
....is me.
You're...?!
Now I will shape the future using these hands.
I have been waiting for this moment.
No...
I have been living for this moment.
Stop! That's mine!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Clock Up...
Grandmother was right.
If I wish so...
...fate will always be on my side.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Those that are not a member of
ZECT are not qualified to be Riders.
If one transforms, can they
match the Worm's Clock Up?
We risk our lives to fight the Worms.
We protect peace.
Who can you save if you get killed?
Looks like the hero type doesn't suit you.
I see.
So at last, Kabuto is...
In that situation, we'd need to eliminate him.
It is only natural...
I am the strongest, aren't I?
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.