HYPER CAST OFF
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
Hyper Clock Up!
HYPER CLOCK UP
Freeze!
Goodbye!
Time only flows... for me.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Your helpless flailing is quite boring.
What are you planning to do with them?!
The words of humans are quite inconvenient, yes?
I supposed you'd have to say the
Native members are "hostages".
Hostages?
ZECT won't negotiate with the Worms!
When that happens I'll just kill them.
But...
I'm hoping that won't happen.
ZECT members.
This proposal shows my compassion.
The Anti-Mimic Bomb that
steals our mimic abilities...
Exchange that last one for the hostages.
If you refuse, all the hostages will be executed.
We're not meeting their demands.
Right?
What do you think? My friends.
Then... you're saying we should
comply with their demand?
I am the man who stands at
the top of falling to Hell.
The top, eh?
I envy you. Facing forward even
in the world of darkness.
Who are you guys?
I... want to eat Bro's mabodofu just one more time.
Right now, tofu is too shiny for me.
Right?
Yes.
Tufu... is not something you hunger for.
What?!
I remember you well! The guy
who walks the path of heaven!
Seems the citizens of darkness
are putting on airs.
But you guys haven't seen true darkness yet.
Bro.
Let's beat this guy up.
Rather than just defeating him...
Let's have a tofu duel again.
I'll show you true darkness.
Very well.
But let me warn you.
I will definitely pay you back for my loss.
Sorry, but I'm sold out of tofu!
Sorry.
It's our fault that Tadokoro was....
What do you want?
Tonight ZECT is fulfilling the Worms' request.
The Worm's request?
Exchanging the hostage
Natives for the Anti-Mimic Bomb.
And you have been picked as the negotiator.
Why me?
His Eminence greatly recommended you.
You should know who.
Father did?
To save the Natives...
...we're giving up the Anti-Mimic Bomb?
I refuse to be a negotiator for that!
If you wish to defy the
organization's decisions, then quit.
Are you okay with that?
Really?
Kagami!
Sir!
Master! Big trouble!
Be careful! You'll crumble my tofu.
But! It's big trouble!
If I recall, up ahead is the
tofu shop that Bro uses.
Do you plan to challenge Tendou with that tufu?
Look forward to my Hell tofu.
What troublesome people.
This area is completely in control of us Worm.
Just now...
You laughed at me, didn't you?
Go... To...
Hell!
TRANSFORM
Transform!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE SCORPION
RIDER KICK
RIDER PUNCH
RIDER SLASH
Brother...!
Smile... Smile.
I heard from Renge.
Why didn't you accept the
ball your father pitched?
He's following the Natives' orders
and giving them the Anti-Mimic Bomb.
How can I listen to such a person?!
Then why did they choose you to be the negotiator?
Do you think it was because you'd
make the mistake of handing it over?
If it's someone that knows
you well... then I don't think so.
Then...
Your father's feelings...
...you should catch them.
Mika...
What are you doing?
I... am the man that will stand
at the top of being a failure.
No... I'm already there.
Where is Yaguruma? He wanted
a tofu duel after all.
I wasn't even able to eat that tufu.
Misakinu's heart will never return!
Of course!
When you look at Misaki...
...you do not see Misaki.
What?
Delicious!
Tofu is the limit of soy sauce.
Tofu is neither yogurt nor cheese.
That means tofu is tofu.
I see...
It's true. I kept seeing my sister in Misakinu.
I will without hesitation receive this.
I'll take this too.
Looks like I'll have to
find "tufu" from somewhere else.
Do you want something?
I will carry through with the negotiation.
It's too late.
You're in the way. Step aside!
I'm going to the negotiation alone.
If you fail, we have a
missile ready to hit the area.
Understand?
Misakinu!
Look! This tufu is you.
Just as I properly see the tufu...
...with unclouded eyes, I see Misakinu.
I won't see the ghost of
my sister within you anymore.
So... please properly look at me, Misakinu!
Okay.
Yes!
I also... must see Tadokoro with unclouded eyes.
Yes.
Kagami accepted the
negotiator job with the Worms.
Misaki!
Misaki! Renge!
You're planning to save
Tadokoro and the others, right?
We're going with you!
The area is full of Worms. It's too dangerous.
It's never not been dangerous before.
But... we've worked together to fight.
...with Tadokoro.
I also cannot just watch my comrade be killed.
Misaki, when the hostages are
released, take everyone to safety.
And you?
I'll stop him, somehow.
Tadokoro. Come.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
I knew it.
RIDER CUTTING
Deceitful humans.
Prepare to fire the missile.
Yes, sir.
Kagami!
Kagami! Run!
Tadokoro!
Tendou... you've come too?
I just came to get tofu.
How funny.
Coming all this way just to lose?
Although, I owe a debt to you as well.
Transform!
Hurry!
Misaki!
Get on!
Human? Worm? Which is which?
Renge!
Hurry! This way!
Misaki! Go!
It may be true that you can stop time...
But I've already seen through your trick.
DRAKE POWER
HYPER SHOOTING
KABUTO POWER
THEBEE POWER
DRAKE POWER
SASWORD POWER
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
MAXIMUM HYPER CYCLONE
All the hostages have been saved.
We've escaped Area C3.
There's no longer a need for a missile attack.
I see.
Cancel the attack.
Yes, sir.
Kagami! Why did you come to save me?
Didn't you say it before, Tadokoro?
If I think I'm right, then I should
dash straight forward.
That's who I am.
Tendou's hot tofu really is the best!
Yeah.
But...
I feel like I've forgotten something.
Bro...
Tendou's not coming, is he?
I'm just a loser anyway...
Oh well.
That mitt.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Hiyori doesn't want to see you anymore.
Then all Riders... will be defeated by me.
This enemy is me.
So acting and little tricks won't work.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.