The future is already in my hands.
And... I will continue holding on to it.
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
HYPER CLOCK UP
MAXIMUM RIDER POWER
ONE TWO THREE
Hyper Kick!
RIDER KICK
HYPER CLOCK OVER
Chosen one.
Please stop collecting the Zecters.
There will be trouble for me if
the Riders do not defeat the Worms.
You're part of the organization?
Or...
Furthermore...
...do this for the person important to you.
Who are you?!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Alright! Master!
Listen.
When I am cooking, the area around me
is God's territory. Always stay back.
Okay, Master!
One more thing. I am not your master.
Okay, Master.
Master!
Leave this cleaning to me!
You truly are impressive, Big Brother!
I thought you got a big promotion at work,
but this time you've got two disciples.
Like I said, they're not my disciples.
H-hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Master!
Owww...
That hurt.
It's because you broke the dishes!
What about you, Mister?!
You're naive!
Relying on Tendou since you defied Mishima
and are in trouble with the organization!
You're the naive one! Trying to trick
Mr. Tendou into giving back your TheBee Zecter.
You stupid kid!
You little wimp.
This might be tough.
My friend! Kagamin!
I'm glad you came!
No... wait.
Mr. Jiiya is...
Don't be so reserved!
Come in!
It's fine!
Jiiya, make my best friend feel welcome!
Mr. Jiiya!
Let's get in the bath!
No, this is no time for...
Come now.
Like I said, I...
Beautifully...
...shining brightly, you are truly...
...my friend. Kagamin!
Umm...
How long is this going to continue?
He wants to make his best friend feel welcome.
After this... Young Master will sing,
play the piano, and dine.
During his afternoon nap, I, Jiiya...
...will read a picture book.
Hey.
I don't have time for this.
I no longer need Sasword Zecter.
But...!
Discabil's hereditary famous sword, Discalibur!
With this...
...no Worm...
Here's my report. H.Q. doesn't have any info
on the location of the new Rider, KickHopper.
I see.
Tendou!
For now, at least return Sasword Zecter.
Without that, Tsurugi is...
What about Tsurugi?
No...
...nothing...
Now that I have already
obtained Hyper Zecter, of course...
...someday I will take Gatack Zecter.
What?
Stop.
If I ever need to fight Kagami,
no one is to interfere.
Right?
Yeah.
When that time comes,
we'll deal with this one on one.
Kagami! Try to get mine back from Tendou too.
Please!
You were the host, right?
Aren't you angry to have your TheBee Zecter taken?
I am angry! So please get along with
Tendou and have him return it.
You're Tendou's friend, right?!
I am not his friend!
Then you... should be my friend!
Look at this.
This face!
Is this for real?
That's bad!
You girls!
When the food is out,
you should eat it immediately!
That's common courtesy when eating.
What's with this old man?
Totally annoying.
Old man?
Totally annoying?
You girls!
That face is...
...pretty bad for business.
Agreed.
Hello!
I just wanted to follow the
commander's orders to come here to eat.
Thank you for the meal.
I worry about this shop's future.
Okay okay okay okay!
Then let me work here!
Then I'm a candidate too!
Okay.
But I will only use the one who can cook better.
The topic of the cooking is "Karei no Nitsuke"
Isn't this a French cuisine restaurant?
To be a good chef you
must first make good meals.
Tachikawa Daigo.
Protect this man from the Worms.
From the Worms?
What's wrong?
No... Defeating Worms is no problem, but it's not
often that we need to protect someone from them.
These are orders from H.Q.
Okay.
This is "Karei no Nitsuke".
The flavor and presentation both pass.
Alright!
Thanks for waiting!
Here you go.
What is this?
Like you said. "Curry mo Tsukemono".
Boiled Karei
Go ahead.
Curry with pickled vegetables
Oh well.
This match... goes to Renge.
Why?!
Alright!
I protest this!
I remember all the flavors
of the famous restaurants.
This cooking is Ginza's five-chome's...
Hide
Cooking
...Hide's cooking
Don't tell me, you secretly
brought it and switched them?
Ridiculous!
Who would do that?!
I don't mind calling the shop to check.
Please, one more...
I just...
I just wanted to be Mr. Tendou's friend.
Stop the crocodile tears.
It is difficult to watch
I've always hated you.
What was I trying to be your disciple for?
Mister, you really are the worse, aren't you?
What?
Get out.
You do not belong on the path of heaven.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye bye.
I've found you.
Tachikawa Daigo.
You need to die.
Please run. I was told to protect you.
Thank you, Kagami Arata.
Why do you know my name?
Henshin!
HENSHIN
He's a Worm?!
Why is a Worm being attacked by Worms?
Please help me.
You...
...you're asking me to save a Worm?
If you won't help me...
HENSHIN
CAST OFF
So you've become a fool that no one will deal with.
Kageyama Shun.
What do you want with me?
We can get TheBee Zecter back from Tendou.
Really?
Unlike humans, we do not lie.
But first...
...you must kill this man.
This man is a Worm.
Do it, no questions asked.
CLOCK UP
Tachikawa...
Just... who is he?
If I kill him...
I will be TheBee once more.
Die!
What's with you guys?
We were ordered by H.Q. to protect this man.
Like I give a crap!
Prepare yourself!
The man I know...
...isn't the type who would
betray ZECT like this.
Who cares about ZECT?!
As long as I can become TheBee, I...
I... before being TheBee...
...I was a member of ZECT.
Wait!
I...
Save me...
Useless man.
Do it.
Kageyama.
I've been waiting.
Yaguruma.
Kageyama.
Smile.
Smile!
Henshin.
HENSHIN
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
RIDER JUMP
RIDER KICK
Master! Let your disciple carry those for you.
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"Life is a long path to a goal."
"Drop your heavy luggage and enjoy
walking with your hands empty."
That's true.
It feels good to have my hands empty.
No!
I'm saying I don't need a disciple!
You again?
Unless humans become Riders and defeat the Worm...
...we Natives will be in trouble.
Natives?
Yes... the one important to you too...
He's...!
Henshin!
HENSHIN
The "important person" you mention,
do you mean Hiyori?!
You know something about Hiyori, don't you?!
Renge!
You should run!
Never.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Are you okay?
Hand him over!
Renge!
Why are the Worms chasing him?
None of your business!
If you don't hand him over, she's dead.
Master... forget about me...
Attack.
Giving up so easily, is a bad habit.
I'm sorry.
Look carefully.
What is the glow of the sunlight really?
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
Kageyama.
You look great.
Want to go to hell with me?
Is there a hell even worse than here?
If you were my...
...little brother...
Hyper Clock Up!
HYPER CLOCK UP
You're the only one who would look at me.
Let's walk together.
With no goal in sight...
...let's tread in the darkness.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
CHANGE PUNCH HOPPER
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Kabuto and Gatack. Red shoes that have a will besides your
own... they will keep dancing till all Worm are defeated.
If I ever go berserk and try
to kill Hiyori... you will kill me.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.