ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
I did it.
All on my own.
I defeated a Worm...
I did it!
Alright! Did you see that, Worm?!
Really...
What an interesting fellow.
I have a new job for you.
Okay...
Let me go!
Gon.
Daisuke!
Daisuke...
Hey, what is it? What's wrong?
Someone attacked me.
What?
Are you playing a trick on me?
No, Daisuke. It really happened.
Okay, okay. I get it. Let's go.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
It was truly a one-on-one battle
against a Worm with my life at stake!
A battle between Worm and
human, with the future at stake!
To beat him, I put everything into my last bullet.
That's how it happened.
Not to brag of course.
That was all bragging.
Anyway, that's the eighth
time I've heard that story.
Understand?
I understand. If you say so, I'll start from the top.
Yes, it was truly a one-on-one battle...
Against a Worm...
...with my life at stake!
I'm saying enough!
More importantly.... I heard that you quit ZECT.
Yes. My reason for staying in ZECT is gone.
That's too bad.
I thought you'd continue to work for ZECT.
Really?
I think Tendou is better off alone though.
It suits you better, Tendou.
What's with you?
That's not what you said before.
That was... well...
I said it before, I will not be
a part of any organization.
My container is just too big.
It's as simple as not entering
a bath that's too small.
Hey, Gon. Eyeliner #3.
Didn't you hear me? The eyeliner.
I'm sorry.
Come with me.
What's wrong with you?
You've been acting strangely.
Someone might attack me again.
Be quiet and focus on the job.
I'm sorry for that.
Hey, Daisuke.
What is it?
Always hold my hand, okay?
Be sure not to let go.
There's no way I can do that.
Hey!
What is it? Where are we going?!
Hey...
Wait. Wait, Gon.
Hey! Why do I have to be here?!
Because I'm afraid.
Whatever. Just hurry up.
Hurry.
Beautiful.
You shine brighter than the summer sun.
You are truly beauty's...
Beauty's...
Ummm...
...personification.
Yes, yes. That that.
That way.
To beat him....
...I put everything in my last bullet!
So that's how it happened.
Not to brag of course.
Enough.
This is the fourth time I've heard it.
It's my twelfth time.
Let me go into more detail.
Yes...
It was truly a one-on-one battle
against a Worm with my life at stake!
A battle between Worm and
human, with the future at stake!
Hello?
I put everything in the last bullet!
Hey, are you listening?
Do you remember that promise you made to me?
Promise?!
You said you'd be my make up model.
I showed I can do it!
Big bro, good morning!
And in the next moment...
Down the hatch!
What's the matter?!
It's just so delicious, I lost consciousness.
It's boiled onion pottara.
Bathed in olive oil, you add a
whole onion when it's lukewarm.
The sweetness and scent of the
onion can even reach the heart.
It makes your soul feel relived as you eat it.
By the way, what's Mr. Kagami been doing lately?
I haven't seen him come by recently.
Yeah. He's still being interesting.
And here's a weird one.
Excuse me, can you turn your body more this way.
Yes, like that. Here I go.
Don't worry about the camera.
Just look at me.
Yes. Relax.
Gon.
No, this one.
You truly are the ultimate photo specimen.
My eye is never wrong.
Gon.
Lip brush #6.
This way.
Gon. Cut it out!
Enough. Go over there.
I'm sorry, Daisuke.
My model today is important.
Don't get in the way, get out!
You...
What about your father and mother?
I don't have any. But that's okay, I have Daisuke.
Did something happen?
I made.... Daisuke mad...
What's today's recipe?
What's wrong?
I see... Kazama Daisuke is an idiot.
Seems like he did not understand
the hurtful nature of his words.
But... it was my fault.
Hey, Hiyori. I want to apologize
to Daisuke. Come with me.
Daisuke has a weakness for women.
Okay...
You said you didn't have parents, right?
Are they dead?
I don't know.
Don't know?
Well... I don't remember anything.
What do you mean?
How do you know Daisuke?
My mind was all blank. I didn't know what to do.
Then Daisuke bought me some strawberry milk.
'Strawberry Milk'
He suddenly said "Here, drink it".
Seems like she has amnesia.
Anyway, come with me to
apologize to Daisuke. Please.
Take care of the restaurant.
So you don't have a father or mother either?
Yeah.
Who is that Tendou person from before? A friend?
I don't know yet.
Hey... can we hold hands?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I guess I can't if it's not Daisuke's hand.
What a nice restaurant.
Yes. They have good coffee here.
But what a surprise.
I've met so many writers before...
But never one as beautiful as you.
Thank you!
Then let's get straight to the interview.
Okay.
First, why did you become a make up artist?
What are you doing here?
That's my line.
Did you see Gon?
She said she wanted to apologize to you, but...
I'm working right now.
Please don't interfere.
You're scum.
This man is scum! Write that in your article.
He's an insensitive man who doesn't
understand the feelings of children.
Stop it!
I know how children feel.
Children that age are very tricky!
She said she was attacked by someone.
Who knows if that was real or not.
Attacked?
Gon!
CLOCK OVER
You...
Run.
Gon! Gon!
Are you okay?! Gon!
Gon. Open you eyes! Gon!
Gon!
Are you okay?
Kotogawa Station
Gon. Are you okay?
Gon! Can you stand{up?
Gon.
Gon... are you okay?
You were on a bus to Kotogawa Station?
So your memory's back?
So? What happened then?
That's all I remember right now.
More importantly. I'm sorry, Daisuke.
I got in the way of you job earlier.
Yeah. Exactly.
I did today's recipe.
Please try it.
Go ahead.
What's wrong?
It's bad.
You're the first person to eat
my cooking and say it's bad.
It's just... I feel like I've had
more delicious miso soup before.
Gon...
If your memory is back, why don't you go home?
Daisuke...
It's only natural. We only
happened to meet in the city.
There's no reason we have to always be together.
And...
I'm going to become more famous.
I'd rather not be seen with a kid around.
I get it.
If I'm in your way, Daisuke, then forget it.
Gon! Wait!
You... really are scum.
I thought you were a better guy than that.
How's it going?
Remember anything?
Mom...
I'm going to get killed...
Don't kill...
Don't kill! Don't kill!
Gon...
Please! Don't kill!
Don't kill!
It's the same... as my memory.
Hiyori!
Hang on! Hey!
Gon...
Where's Gon?
What do you want?
Why'd you call me here?
If it's about joining ZECT,
I already refused before.
The situations changed.
Daisuke!
Get me out of here!
Get me out!
Gon!
Daisuke!
How you act... will affect
how this girl is treated.
Get me out!
Daisuke!
You bastard...
From here onward you are a member of ZECT.
First, kill Kabuto for us.
No way.
Daisuke!
I have no relationship with Gon.
Do what you want.
Daisuke!
Get me out!
Daisuke! Daisuke!
What's wrong?
You said I was scum, but...
Unfortunately....
It seems I can't just be scum.
What are you thinking?
Picking a fight here?
My grandmother once said...
"Immature fruit is sour....
...producing immature fights."
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
I will defeat you!
I must defeat you!
Die, Tendou!
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Please die.
If I don't kill you... Gon will be in danger!
So that's how it is.
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Shooting.
RIDER SHOOTING
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
The agreement was that I'd defeat
Kabuto, then you'd let Gon free.
It's no surprise that ZECT would do this.
It's my fault. It's all... my fault.
Goodbye, Gon.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.