With this, Kabuto is an enemy to
society, no... an enemy to peace
Hey, that's cruel!
Stop it! What are you doing?!
Renge!
Do you know what you've done?!
Tendou!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Hey.
What's wrong?
When did you get that?!
Run!
Hey! Please wait! Hey!
You're not hurt, are you?
Stay away! Stay away!
This person is not a Worm.
Go away, Worm!
Leave the Earth!
Please stop it. He's not a Worm.
Then what is he?!
You're sticking up for a Worm?!
Please calm down. Just listen to me...
Kagami!
Are you okay?
Man... what a true hero you are, Kagami.
Let me introduce you.
Mr. Negishi of the Natives.
Poor thing.
The desire to live as long as possible...
Doesn't everything alive feel that way?
Their only fault is they
did things the wrong way.
Negishi...
Oh no...
I...
...might seem naive, but...
I want to create a truly peaceful world.
A world where humans and Natives don't fight.
A world where humans and humans don't fight.
I want to create such a world.
Will you lend me your strength
to make that happen?
Yes.
If you want me, then I'd be glad to do so.
Thank you!
Tadokoro! It's Kabuto!
Tendou, stop it!
Misaki, stand back.
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Kabuto?
This is unforgivable...
Kabuto...
Just what I'd expect from you, Negishi.
Oh? What can I do for you, Mishima?
So you already knew
about the berserk switch?
Oh... what could you be talking about?
Let's quit the act.
Right now, he's in my hand.
Your plan is wonderful.
But it's lacking something
to make it complete.
I have a good deal for you.
Thanks for coming.
It's okay, it's the least I can do.
Hey, what are you making?
A menu I'm thinking of releasing at Salle.
But it's not finished though.
It tastes great!
The cooking is very similar to Tendou's.
It has a gentle flavor to it.
Minha vó uma vez disse...
"Cooking spreads from one person to another.
The flavor connects one person to another."
'Heaven'
Master...
Yo, Tendou.
Let me tell you something good.
We're going to leave on
a journey to seek the light.
I see.
But first take that necklace off.
What?
You want this too?
But I won't.
It can't be! It can't be!
I thought so.
ZECT exists to establish peace.
It's been decided that I will...
Be the one on top.
You're fired.
Please let me work under you!
How can you sink so low?
Please understand our sentiments.
All this time you were with us Native,
while patiently waiting with your secret plan.
But...
...your secret is out.
We know about the berserk switch!
Shut up!
Bastard!
I said shut up!
Welcome home.
He's still alive, right?
He's a stubborn one. He has endured
this harsh environment for many years.
Kill! I'll kill you!
How scary.
That's why humans are so troublesome.
I'm...
...human?
You don't remember?
You...
...were transformed from a human to a Native by us.
You're the commemorative first one.
Even after that, you endured many more experiments
so that we could create the Masked Rider System.
And then... you had him mimic me?
You bastard... how did you get in here?
HENSHIN
CLOCK UP
What are you doing?!
Setting you free.
I'm...
...free now?
As long as you don't hurt others...
...you can live in this world.
The world is not your enemy.
There are a lot of bad things like this.
But... Hiyori is facing this.
She's working hard even now.
Hiyori...
I can't forgive her!
Tendou.
You people...
I will eliminate you!
Henshin.
HENSHIN
As a tool for turning all
of humanity into Natives...
Thanks to that, I've become the ultimate Native.
Kagami... those necklaces...
...turn humans into Natives.
I don't believe what you say anymore.
You have killed my friends...
my friends who seek true peace.
I... cannot forgive you.
You're serious?
Justice is on our side.
I..
...will defeat you.
Rubbish.
Minha vó uma vez disse... "Justice is myself."
I am justice.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Is that it?
Hurry up and get serious!
Using the sun as your start, walk the true path!
Shut up!
Even with you gone... I will walk my own path!
Try becoming Hyper Kabuto.
Even then I won't lose!
It's a duel, Kagami.
RIDER KICK
You're open, Tendou!
Tendou...
Kagami Riku, who lead ZECT, was found
to be in league with the Worms.
Kagami, big trouble.
Father...
Father!
Pull yourself together!
Kabuto...?
He's gone.
I killed him.
Kabuto is our enemy!
Father?
Move if you don't want to get hurt!
You're late, my friend.
I...
...have seen darkness that
you do not know of, Bro.
I wanted you to take me, but...
...I can't leave this darkness.
Goodbye.
Bro.
Partner!
Partner.
We're eternally together.
Let's go...
...go to catch the light
that exists only for us.
Turn all of humanity into Native?
The peace that Negishi mentioned...
...this is what he meant?!
Then...
...I will fight eternally with humans.
Thirty-five years ago...
...even though we became their servants...
We kept a berserk switch as our trump card!
Kusakabe and I put humanity's future...
...in your hands.
Forgive me!
Father.
Thank you...
...for entrusting me with
such an important duty.
Arata... we no longer have a chance of winning.
I'm glad to die.
But just you... Just you...
...live!
Don't kill...
I will be by your side.
It's okay.
I'm by your side.
I will...
...be by your side.
I see.
That time...
...the one who received the will to live...
...was me.
Final Episode
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Final Episode!
"There is only one name in this
world that you must remember."
I am the world. As long as
the world exists... so will I!
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.