MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
Take me to where Hiyori is.
There's no reason for you two to fight.
I've already made my decision.
I'm never returning to this world again.
Why?
Hiyori, what are you saying?!
This is what will make me happy.
See?
Hiyori and I will live outside this world.
Just the two of us.
Don't be ridiculous! He's a Worm!
Stay away!
Hiyori...
Watch out!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Watch out!
Kagami!
Farewell.
Wait! Hiyori!
Hiyori!
Hiyori, that girl...
Why does she want to stay with your mimic?
Does she really not plan to return?
Hiyori...
If she thinks she's happier that way...
It's painful, but there's nothing I can do about it.
Master!
What?
You saw a total eclipse?
Yes... But for only a short period of time.
So there is an exit from
the edge of time and space!
But... If Hiyori doesn't want
to return, then there's no point.
I...
For some reason... don't think that's true.
Thanks for earlier. It'll always be us!
I'll be by your side. I'll always just be by your side.
ZECT members!
You're too weak, not worthy to be my food.
Let's go.
You're not going to defeat that Worm?
I envy you. You still have the
cinders of heroism left.
But Bro, in the past you used to...
That's all been crushed.
It's the same no matter how you live.
What's the situation?
The Worms keep breaking past the
defense lines and are headed for Area Z.
Area Z?
Apparently it's the location where the
Masked Rider System is being developed.
It would be bad if they took that.
I have no choice but to go.
I'm going too.
You, return to the hospital.
If you go alone...
...you cannot defeat that Worm.
Give this up and fall back
to the final defense line!
Retreat!
Roger.
We're retreating.
Help the wounded!
Hurry!
You are a prospect amongst the foolish
humans... Worthy to be my food.
Tsurugi!
STANDBY
I will protect Misaki.
HENSHIN
How will you protect her?
I... will give everything!
What a noble attitude.
But how long will it last?
That's enough!
Stop it!
But you were right, I've accepted reality.
I can't beat him.
But! I can protect Misaki!
Tsurugi...
Rider Slash!
Tsurugi! Hold on!
I-it's okay. Just go.
I'm sorry for not understanding
how you self sooner, Misaki.
Why are you suddenly saying this?
I am...
...the man who stands at the top of seeing reality.
N-now...
Please go, Misaki.
Misakinu... is fine by me.
Hurry! Carry him!
Tsurugi!
Tsurugi, that guy... putting up such a brave front.
Brave front?
That's it...
Hiyori is the same way.
She's just putting up a brave front.
Hiyori wants to return to this world. If she didn't...
...she wouldn't draw such a warm picture.
Do you like tulips?
I just wanted to draw that picture.
Flowers don't suit me.
It's the flower called hope.
Without that, we cannot live.
Delicious.
Hiyori...
Hurry and bring Hiyori back.
Okay.
But right now we have to defeat the Worm first.
But how do we fight?
Earlier you said... together
we can defeat him, right?
Y-yeah. That was just to raise your spirit.
That's right.
If Kabuto and Gatack attack simultaneously...
Then he can't copy the attack.
R-right. That's what I meant to say.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
Master, it's the solar eclipse again.
So using the Hyper Zecter creates a
tear in time and space somewhere?
Tendou.
You, go get Hiyori.
I'll hold up till you return.
And then... the two of us will defeat that Worm.
Okay.
They're getting through.
Fall back! Keep falling back!
Hurry!
Wait!
I can't let you die.
I won't die that easily.
You haven't learned a thing.
Come to be defeated again, Gatack?
Rider Slash!
Oh oh, another friend has come to save you.
Kageyama!
Now come...
TheBee Zecter!
HENSHIN
I did it! I've obtained TheBee again!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Cast Off.
Attack simultaneously with me.
Like I'd take orders from the likes of you!
Hold on a minute!
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
RIDER CUTTING
Rider Sting!
Rider Cutting!
Yo.
You...
Please, wait, TheBee Zecter!
Bro!
You've come to save me, right?
Please avenge me.
Partner.
You're still saying that?
How stubborn!
Didn't Hiyori say that she
doesn't want to go back?
Hiyori is happiest when she's
living outside that world, with me.
I'm not walking the path of heaven.
I will live as Hiyori's big brother,
Kusakabe Souji, and live to always protect her.
Can you do that?
I...
...cannot always be by Hiyori's side.
Tendou!
See! He'd rather protect the world than you.
I will protect the world.
The world where Hiyori should return.
I'm a Worm.
I shouldn't be in that world.
You just happened to be born a Worm.
That's all.
The Worms are humanity's enemy, right?
No!
I do not fight because they are Worms.
They wrong humans, they trample
over their little hopes and dreams.
I only fight those people.
What wrong have you done?!
Look at what state you're in,
isn't Kabuto going to come save you?
Shut up!
Like you'd understand the bond between us!
Is it okay... for me to live?
I'm happy that you were born, Hiyori.
That's why... I will protect you
and the world you live in.
Seven years ago, when I first
met you under the rubble...
That's when I made that decision.
Now...
Let's go home.
Hiyori...?
It can't be! Hiyori!
Welcome home.
I'm home.
You're going, right?
You're okay with that?
Please protect it...
My world.
They're even at Point Six. Pattern grey!
The final defense line will break soon.
If they're going to steal
the Masked Rider System...
...then our only choice is to blow up Area Z.
This is boring.
This is the God of Battle?
I'm taking that title.
Tendou! What about Hiyori?
I saved her, thanks to you.
I see... that's good.
If we work together, we won't lose to anyone.
Is this the "bond" you mentioned?
What a laugh.
Are you the one that laughed at my partner?
Yaguruma.
Why don't you laugh at me too?
Henshin.
HENSHIN
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
We need to all attack at once.
I'll reflect any attack you send against me!
Let's go!
Rider Jump!
ONE TWO THREE
RIDER JUMP
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Wh-why?!
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
GUN MODE
KABUTO POWER
THEBEE POWER
DRAKE POWER
SASWORD POWER
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
MAXIMUM HYPER CYCLONE
I owe you one.
Next time... cook me something.
Bro!
Please wait, Bro!
HENSHIN
CAST OFF
I'll destroy it...
...this world!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I will fight... to protect Misakinu.
Just wait, Misakinu. Very soon my
sparkling love will reach you.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.