Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
What you said is right...
But...
I don't like it!
Stop it!
There's no reason for you two to fight!
Gon...
Don't get in the way.
It's not like I came here to stop you.
Beat him some more.
Daisuke is too naive about women.
You're in the right.
You're pretty perceptive.
I guess.
Daisuke is just mad.
It's because you were more cool.
Rubbish.
You...
...have a good guardian.
You really are a despicable person.
Like in Eden...
Ummm... that...
A poisonous snake.
Yes. Yes. That that.
That which has some poison is beautiful.
I can't deal with you anymore.
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?
The wind merely passes through.
Bye bye.
Daisuke, wait!
You're...
What are you doing?!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Let's eat!
Bro, Today's breakfast is great as always!
This is from Hiyori.
Ah! The takenoko that you gave her!
That's the best!
I'm no match for her flavoring.
She's one of the Seven Wonders Of The World.
Hey.
I've always wanted to ask.
Seven years ago when the meteorite hit Shibuya...
Tendou, after saving me, you
headed back to the rubble. Right?
You said there was someone you still had to save.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey... could that have been Ms. Hiyori?
I knew it!
Just kidding.
It was a lie?!
Not a lie.
I saved Hiyori and all of the
foolish humanity's future.
There you go again.
Starting today, a new member will join our team.
Enter.
Kageyama!
Yo.
Long time no see.
Please work with Misaki so you
can learn to be an Operator.
Okay.
Wait a minute! Isn't Kageyama a member of Shadow?!
Shadow has been dissolved.
I'm tired of the front line battle.
Let me hang out here for a while.
Hang out?!
Oh.
Pardon my rudeness.
Please don't be angry Misaki.
Let's get along, Misaki.
Be sure to wear a necktie.
I'm tired of that stiffness.
Hold on a second!
Misaki.
Right now, former Shadow
members are being eliminated.
Then Kageyama is in danger?
Be careful.
Someone might be gathering
information about the organization.
This...
And this...
Kageyama.
Why was Shadow disbanded?
I messed up.
Kageyama.
It couldn't be helped.
We didn't have a leader.
For some reason I feel responsible...
Well... each of us had our
own personal situations.
We were idiots for falling
for the Perfect Harmony.
Are you serious?
Hey. Don't get mad.
Kageyama, do you really think that's okay?
Of course it's not okay.
Then why?!
What can I do right now?!
Shadow's been dissolved.
I don't want to waste my
time on such frivolousness!
That's fine! I'm out of olive oil.
Can you go get some?
Okay.
Sorry. It's usually delivered,
but they haven't called.
I'm off.
Have a safe trip.
I wonder if Hiyori will be
okay alone. I'm so worried.
I also frequently use this.
The flavor and scent are first class.
But...
I cannot let anything interfere
with my coffee time.
The person killed was a ZECT member, wasn't he?
Furthermore, he's a former Shadow member.
No...
Yaguruma!
Don't let your guard down! Fire!
Okay!
He got away?
Yaguruma!
You saved us!
This area isn't in your jurisdiction.
Why are you here?
I know.
But as a former leader of Shadow,
I couldn't ignore this incident.
Do you have permission from
headquarters to do this?
From here on...
...I cannot stand by and do nothing while
my comrades are being eliminated.
I'm not going to do anything.
Just what is going on?
Shadow members are being eliminated one by one?!
I will protect my comrades' lives.
That is a absolute connection.
The mentality of Perfect Harmony.
Yaguruma!
I knew you were the only leader for Shadow!
Please... please come back!
Kageyama...
But Shadow is already...
And I also...
I'll gather everyone.
When everyone hears that their great leader
has returned, I'm sure they'll come!
Kageyama.
Yes.
Will you again join me in Perfect Harmony?
Okay!
I will definitely protect my comrades.
Do you know where the
other members are right now?
Hello.
Excuse me.
Find the olive oil?
Don't try to sneak up on me.
I came all this way to buy some, but...
What's with this mess?
Inside there....
Yo.
You are...
Tendou.
What a rude shopkeeper.
Your customer wants olive oil.
Call the store owner.
He's not here.
I also wanted to use this store's
olive oil for my celebration feast.
What are you celebrating?
My era will come again.
I'll say that much.
That's nice, but...
Where's my olive oil?
Show me to the store owner.
I cannot.
But if I obtain some....
I'll share it with you.
Get this new weapon to Kabuto.
Why are you suddenly asking?
First of all, I don't know
Kabuto's location or identity.
I don't care how, just get it to him.
Understand?
Where are you going?
To get some olive oil.
Tendou!
For you.
It's small for a box of olive oil...
That's not it! Listen...
This is....
I knew it.
I want to bring Shadow back together.
So I need you.
You're the store owner aren't you?
You made me search for you.
You...
How did you know of this place?
You cannot deceive me.
The restaurants in this area
often use this olive oil.
Are they also customers?
Watch out!
Yaguruma!
Kageyama! Where's Shadow?!
They're heading this way right now!
Alright.
I will protect you both!
Stay here.
Don't go outside.
Tendou...
Nothing...
It's okay.
I'll be right back.
My grandmother once said...
"There are two things men must not do.
One is to not ever let a girl cry...
The other is to not handle food crudely!"
Henshin.
HENSHIN
Yaguruma!
Kageyama!
Back me up!
Okay.
This is Shadow's reunion battle!
I will protect your lives.
I will protect you!
Kageyama....
You...
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Captain, your orders?!
Have each team pick a
target and focus their attacks.
Roger.
I'll defeat the rest.
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
Kageyama...
What is the meaning of this?
This was all an act to squeeze out the traitor.
An act?
Why do this?
If someone is leaking Shadow's information...
One who has lost the title of TheBee and
was dismissed from Shadow might hold a grudge...
You...
And that's supposed to be me?
But I overestimated your intelligence.
I thought you were aware that I became TheBee.
I mistook you for someone
who would be more competent.
Kabuto, here!
When did you..?!
What is this?!
Kageyama!
Please wait.
Now that your suspicions have cleared...
Please let me join Shadow once again.
You are no longer needed
for Shadow's Perfect Harmony.
In fact, you would just bring discord.
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Pay close attention. This battle occurs only a
second before the olive oil falls to the ground.
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
Hiyori...
The traitor leaking Shadow's information...
...has been identified.
I'm sending over the data now.
Kagami...
You...
...killed my parents!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Your power is needed.
He wore the same belt...
...as the one from seven years ago.
Are you the traitor?
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.