Get in position!
Captain!
What?!
The operation has been suspended?!
You're awake?
Well that's good.
Looks like you're through the hard part.
I... failed to become Gatack didn't I?
If it wanted you to, you wouldn't
have had any problems.
That's true...
I...
Even when I try my best... I still fall flat...
I'm an idiot, aren't I?
This is my lamest moment yet.
There's no way I'd be qualified.
If you don't make it then you don't make it.
At least you did your best.
Misaki.
What about Makoto's rescue?
I'm sorry...
It's official that everyone
in that factory is a Worm.
That's why headquarters...
...has decided to eliminate the factory.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Even if we're letting them borrow
the restaurant, isn't that too much?
And...
Why do I have to wear this?
I cannot make any complaints to that person.
Who is that old man?
If I'm the world's treasure...
Then that man is humanity's treasure.
Let's do as he says.
I haven't had such a small birthday party...
...since I was kid.
I know the mystery flavor from yesterday.
Will you take a taste?
Very well.
I am the man that will stand at the top of tasting.
Not you.
If you'd please.
You did well to figure it out.
Shredding kelp and sprinkling on top,
giving it a unique flavor...
Very impressive.
Let me see.
I see. The same flavor as yesterday.
I am not asking one such as yourself.
You've been addressing the wrong
person with respectful speech.
It's only naturaly to respect this person.
Jii uses respectful speech for Young master.
Then you should respect me.
Why would I do that?!
Why was the extermination plan stopped?!
That factory is too much for the likes of you.
That's not true.
Mishima. You underestimate my power.
Are you listening?!
Have Sasword help you.
You can do it.
This is the first time I've had this cuisine.
It's just meat and potatoes.
Delicious.
This is the first time I've
had such fantastic meat.
It's just shredded meat
I bought at the super market.
Next time I'd like this
shredded thing... using steak meat.
And these potatoes?
That's also from the neighborhood supermarket.
Super.
I bet it must be a famous store.
This is...
A famous British product, the hereditary
Duscabil family pure silver fork.
Please accept this.
What? Do not hesitate.
There is no need to give me change.
Hold on.
Don't tell me this is how you intend to pay?
Yo.
You!
Tendou Soujirou!
What are you doing?!
I might still make it.
I'm going to save Makoto.
I told you! Headquarters has decided he's a Worm.
But I'm not convinced.
Even if there's only a one percent
chance of Makoto being human...
...then I want to make that bet.
Think about Tadokoro's position,
if you disobey headquarters' orders!
Hey!
Let him go.
Kagami.
It's true that you are an idiot.
But I don't hate you for being an idiot.
Tadokoro...
If you think you're right,
then dash straight forward!
That is who...
...Kagami Arata is.
Okay.
What?
Come to wash dishes again?
Hey.
Time for work.
No.
I still haven't heard my song.
Song?
The song to celebrate my birthday.
This is perfect.
You sing it.
If you don't... I won't move.
Stop screwing with me!
Hey. Excuse me...
Tsurugi, once in such a mood,
will not listen to anything.
Please... please... sing...
Today is a lovely birthday.
It's kind of... bland.
Please smile more.
Everyone's beloved, Young Master!
Congratulations!
I feel disgusted.
Please put more feeling into it.
Everyone's beloved, Young Master! Congratulations!
I feel really creeped out.
It must be hard for one used to command.
Happy happy birthday!
Exciting...
All platoons, split up and
prepare to enter on the signal!
Yes, sir!
Wait.
You guys go home.
All Worms are my prey.
I will defeat them.
What?!
Enter!
Yes, sir!
Makoto, it's me!
It's Kagami! I've come to save you!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
STANDBY
I told you already. All Worms are my prey.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Cast Off.
Makoto!
Mister!
You're okay?! Let's go!
This place... could it be Worm eggs?!
So this is what they're hiding?
My grandmother once said...
"It is fun to add a secret
flavor so that no one knows.
But...
It's more fun to find it."
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
There's no end to them!
Rider Slash!
RIDER SLASH
I feel it...
...his power...
He's here...
Where is he?!
Stop it!
A new Worm?
Their numbers aren't going down!
I was wondering who it was...
...so it's me?
You!
You plan to fight me without armor?
Makoto, hide!
Enough.
I thought if I let Mister go, we'd escape
the extermination operation.
But now our business is at an end.
Makoto...
Don't tell me...
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
The hope from willpower...
...that must not be crushed.
When fallen into despair...
A man...
...using true hope...
...will save them.
A Worm that abuses the trust between people...
...I will never forgive that!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Stop it, Mister! Don't destroy me!
If you destroy me, Makoto's
memories will be gone too.
K-Kabuto!
Move. I'll finish it.
Mister, save me!
Stop, Tendou.
You're...
Kagami?
Please leave this to me.
Very well.
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE STAG BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Mister... you aren't really gonna...
What?
There's something I wanted you to see.
It's a rainbow made out of the moonlight.
They say if you see one...
...it'll bring you happiness.
Preparations for the detonation are complete.
Okay.
I won't be responsible for what happens... Mister.
CLOCK OVER
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Detonate!
Makoto!
Your son...
...has become Gatack.
But is this truly...
...for the best?
Mozart...
While creating a song for the dead...
...he died.
But... did that song kill him?
Or was the persistence in creating that song...
...what kept him alive?
In other words...
Gatack is a double-edged sword.
It might take your son's life... or might save it...
Mozart...
Naive... as usual.
I...
...can only be myself.
But...
I am who I am.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Why was I brought to Area X?
It's training. The road to cooking is vast.
Hiyori has the same stone.
What are you doing?
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.