My grandmother once said...
"My evolution is faster than the speed of the light"
"Nothing in this universe can
keep up with my evolution."
KABUTO POWER
RIDER CUTTING
HYPER SWING
Looks like there is a Worm
presence in this school.
What should we do?
Close the school and investigate?
If we do that the Worm will just flee.
And we cannot cancel the camp
that Juka has been looking forward to.
This song again?
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Tendou, did you hear? That "shameful"
team won the local tournaments.
Won?
Seems they won thanks to their ace, Aotaka.
I see.
Seconds.
But why are you eating at my house?
Don't judge me.
By the way, where's Juka?
Good morning!
Today we're finally having the badminton camp.
I've been impatiently waiting
for this chance to camp.
Eat up, Juka. You'll be late.
Okay!
That technique doesn't seem human at all.
H.Q. still hasn't made a decision?
We watched for a week, but there's
been no follow-up it seems.
Then... I'll see whether he's
a Worm or not in a match.
Hey. Is that a good idea?
I've practiced this many times in the past.
No one can beat me in baseball.
I challenge you!
Not bad.
Throw it harder though.
I will put my all into your next pitch.
That pitching was quite good.
Director.
At this rate, we'll win the
prefecture tournaments. No...
The national tournaments wouldn't be unlikely.
Leave it to me.
I won't rely on that charm anymore.
I'll just work harder tomorrow.
You again?
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Each of you report on your findings.
First, about the missing choir club.
Seven years ago there was a
choir club that won the nationals.
But due to financial reasons, the club was closed.
That's the source of the rumors.
That's all?
Seems the choir students who
graduated are now living normal lives.
Then whose singing is it
that we occasionally hear?
About the cursed mirror.
It's a bit warped, so its angle is off.
Just a silly school rumor.
That part of your life is over.
Bro...
Didn't I tell you?
If you think you can grasp the
useless light... you'll just get hurt.
I...
Partner! We'll always be together.
Eternally in the darkness.
Always suffering.
Now we will train by putting up tents.
Complete it in one minute.
Begin!
You're not going fast enough.
Move faster!
Ten seconds.
Hey! Why are you wasting time?!
Camp sure is strict.
Hurry!
Don't waste time!
This is...
It's like she has the wrong idea.
Over there! Stop wasting time gossiping.
Hey, Renge!
This isn't training.
Camp is more exciting and fun.
Are you going to make a
waste of Juka's first camp?
I see...
When I was in training, it was always like this.
'Kobayashi Keiko'
Juka, Looks like someone
took your number one spot.
Guess I'll get Tendou to teach me again.
More importantly, today's camp! Camp! Yay!
'Kobayashi Keiko'
A reward for the girl who
took the number one spot.
Congratulations for being top in the school.
At this rate, being number one in
the nation wouldn't be unlikely.
No problem.
That makes me very proud to be the director.
So that's how it is.
I hope today's camp goes well.
And... I hope I become much better at badminton.
Juka! It's time to go.
Yeah. I'm coming now.
Hurry, Juka!
Wait, wait!
Let's go!
Tendou! I'm going.
Yeah. I'll go afterwards.
Kagami and Renge will go with you.
Okay! Let's go, Kagami!
Tendou, off I go!
Yeah.
Bye bye. Here I go!
What of the choir members?
No record after they graduated.
And to add to the mystery, all the parents say their
children haven't returned since middle school.
I see.
I figured something out looking at
the old blueprints of this place.
The choir club should have it's own room.
But that space has disappeared.
Truly a vanished choir club.
What do you mean?
Just as Waraube Valley hides
the history of the village.
The truth lies in the rumors.
Where are you aiming?
This is the choir room!
The same as seven years ago.
That was the beginning of everything, wasn't it?
Director.
Seven years ago, you had the
Worms mimic this whole choir.
And won the nationals.
The school's reputation improved,
but you feared the truth.
So you sealed away the choir room.
But the effects of history are not forgotten.
I just wanted to restore the honor of the school.
You joined with the Worms to hurt the students!
So that's how the cursed
mirror rumors started, right?
The students wished for it themselves.
What's wrong with making it come true?
My grandmother once said...
"The wishes of children are the future of reality."
"Adults that laugh at such
dreams are no longer human."
You are someone who has no right to be an educator.
The next... student. Tendou Juka's wish
has already been conveyed to the Worm.
What?!
Take care of the rest.
Okay.
You're under arrest.
Protect Juka.
I'll be right there.
Got it. Leave it to me.
Burn, burn!
The flame burns.
Look, look!
The fog.
It can't be... the ghosts of the
disappeared choir club?
It's not possible.
Everyone, calm down!
Be quiet!
Sing in a loud voice!
If you sing loudly, you won't
hear the ghost's singing.
Burn! Burn!
The flame burns!
This is how the flame burns up!
It burns even to heaven.
Flame, shine your light into the darkness!
Burn burn!
With the light. All from the flame!
That's it!
The ghosts are running.
Three. Go!
Burn burn! The flame burns.
This is how the flame burns up!
It burns even to heaven.
Sir.
Shine! Shine! Move in a swirl.
Make sure the door doesn't
open once I get outside.
What about you, sir?
I'm going ghost-hunting. Take care of everyone.
Okay.
Sir.
You're fighting me.
Henshin!
HENSHIN
Broken brother.
Brother, you should join us.
Then we can do our best tomorrow.
I'm jealous, Partner.
Bro.
I want to be cheered up too.
Henshin!
Transform...
HENSHIN
CHANGE PUNCH HOPPER
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
My friend, Kagamin!
I am the man who stands on the top of camping!
STANDBY
Henshin!
HENSHIN
RIDER JUMP
RIDER PUNCH
RIDER KICK
Partner. You really are the best.
No, you are, Bro.
Hyper Cast Off.
HYPER CAST OFF
What is this?
My grandmother once said...
"A bond is a deep connection
that can never be broken."
"Even if apart, heart and
heart are still connected."
KABUTO POWER
THEBEE POWER
DRAKE POWER
SASWORD POWER
ALL ZECTER COMBINED
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
HYPER CLOCK UP
Hiyori!
HYPER CLOCK OVER
Tendou!
What happened?
Nothing.
But there is something!
I cannot forgive you for using my
Sasword Zecter without permission!
Quit it.
Tendou!
Master!
Burn burn! The flame burns.
Hiyori. Soon I will save you.
I will definitely protect my two little sisters.
Tendou.
Camp sure is fun.
I see.
I'm glad you like it.
Shine the light into the darkness.
Tendou, come join us too.
Wait...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I can't remember...
I don't remember what I've been doing.
The current Reina isn't a Worm!
You have lost your Worm heart.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.