Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
I...
I transformed!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Clock Up!
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
Heaven sure is whimsical.
Big Brother, what are we
having for dinner tonight?
It'll be a surprise for when you return home.
Here.
You're going to be late.
Oh no! I'm off!
Have a safe trip.
I lost.
Perfectly lost.
But don't misunderstand me.
I did not lose to you.
I lost to myself.
While trying to beat you...
...I strayed from my path.
It's only natural that TheBee
Zecter would forsake me.
But TheBee has chosen its new partner.
I'm sure Kagami can do it...
Please eat this.
Delicious.
But the flavor is quite different.
It's the clash of individual side
flavors that you mentioned before.
This isn't bad.
A farewell gift!
But you...
...should make the mabou
tofu that only you can make.
"I'm here."
"And... I will always be by your side."
Hey!
Please! Don't kill!
Don't kill!
Don't kill...
Now you are a formal member of ZECT.
Really?
And, transforming into TheBee makes
you the captain of Shadow.
Captain?
But I was just an apprentice
before... now I'm the captain?!
I can also finally leave the hospital.
Get used to the fact that you're in charge.
Captain Kagami.
Captain Kagami?
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
Hiyori.
What's today's recipe?
I'd better calm down...
...or he'll be mad at me.
What's wrong?
TheBee's mark?!
You used the restaurant without
permission this morning, didn't you?
The cleaning was poorly done.
Pass that along to Kagami.
So Kagami is absent again?
You should fire him already.
Stop it.
That's Kagami's father.
Looks like my son is being a burden.
He's a big burden!
And yet he gives us pleasure.
Well, well, I'm happy that he
made such good friends.
Please take care of my son.
Of course.
Thank you for the meal.
Hey, it's me. I'm having a mackerel miso party at Salle, you should come.
I'm already here. Where's the party?
It's happening later.
Oh. Tell Hiyori for me...
I'll buy the goods.
Man... that guy...
A new TheBee user has appeared.
A bee is one that stings.
A bee that does not sting...
...is worthless!
Oh yeah, Kagami said he's having a party.
No thanks.
Why?
Why not?
Is it related to this picture?
It isn't.
That belt...
Is that really Kagami's?
You...
You saw the belt?
It fell from your bag.
But...
Kagami said it was his.
What if it was?
I...
...would never forgive Kagami.
Now I'll work with Tendou to defeat the Worms.
If I do that everything will go great!
I'm sure of it.
Yes?
The first orders for the new TheBee.
Eliminate Kabuto.
But Kabuto...
That's all.
Hello?!
Kabuto has defeated so many Worms already!
If he worked with TheBee, many more
Worms would be defeated!
So what?
Orders from headquarters are absolute.
You don't have a choice.
On that day we were under the rubble...
...even our hearts were frozen.
But in that darkness, you should
have seen a single flower.
I didn't see any flowers...
It's the flower called hope!
If not...
...we wouldn't have survived.
Your pictures have an
immeasurable gentleness to them.
Even a frozen heart...
...can warm just a bit.
Just like your pictures.
It's warm.
Anyway, Kagami sure is late.
He really should be fired.
Yo.
Tendou!
How long do you plan to keep me waiting?
"Eliminate Kabuto."
...is what they said, right?
You knew I became TheBee, didn't you?
That's what the party was for, right?
I...
I never wanted to tell you this...
I think of you as a friend.
If you think of me the same way...
Than please never appear before me again.
What about the mackerel miso party?
This is no time for that!
What a boring guy.
What?!
Just have a party, if you're going to.
Whether you're TheBee or not doesn't matter to me.
I can't!
As long as I'm TheBee...
...I must eliminate Kabuto!
Do it then.
However...
I'm not going to lose.
That's all, right?
Friends?
Using the word I hate the most.
Come!
TheBee Zecter!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Stop firing, I'll defeat him.
Captain!
Kageyama!
Take care of everyone!
Got it!
Everyone distant yourselves from the Worms!
Distant yourselves then focus your fire!
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Now!
Harmonize!
At this rate...
...we'll be wiped out.
This is..?!
Kagami?!
No. It's not me!
It can't be!
CLOCK UP
Kabuto...
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
You did it!
Captain Kagami.
Kabuto!
What's wrong, Kagami?!
Did you forget your orders?!
Still undecided?
What a disappointing fellow.
CLOCK UP
Are you going to fight or not?!
Which is it?!
I...
I don't want to fight a friend!
You are...
...no friend of mine!
My grandmother once said...
"Friendship is only for those
who have naive hearts."
Naive?!
If you're naive then you're naive.
There is no point to this unless
you're serious about fighting!
Serious?!
I won't go easy on you.
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
CLOCK OVER
Did Kagami win?
You're an interesting fellow after all.
You...
Don't waste the mackerel.
Blue greenish fish can add
the greatest flavor to cooking.
Why don't you finish him off?!
If TheBee fails...
...then Shadow will eliminate Kabuto!
These are orders from headquarters!
What are you doing, Kagami?!
You blocked our shots!
I...
And you're just going to giving up TheBee?!
I have something more...
...important to me.
Fall back.
We have lost another candidate for TheBee.
It's written...
In the twelfth chapter...
In the 24th verse.
Yes, sir.
If the first goes to nothing...
If one land dies, there are more...
If it dies...
There are plenty of other bodies.
In other words...
Even if we lose TheBee...
...there are plenty of other bodies.
...even in secret.
A new wind...
...has begun to blow, it seems.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Tendou Souji has no sense of friendship.
You'll fall in love with me.
I have a principle to participate
in all dating parties.
Kagami, you are forgetting something important.
Trilhando o caminho do Céu. Governando a todos nós.