SASWORD POWER
HYPER SLASH
As you can see...
...we have completed our Anti-Mimic Bomb
that overcomes the Worms' mimic abilities.
But right now we only have
the three experimental shots.
And it's efficiency lasts
only for a short period.
When complete, it will be the last weapon
that will end the war with the Worms.
The developers are testing it in battle.
We are going to use the Anti-Mimic
Bomb on the Worms in Area C3.
And what of our friends?
To be safe, they have been evacuated.
The path I must walk...
...that is...
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Alright.
I know we had to evacuate the
citizens to clean up the Worms, but...
Why couldn't we take these people?
Don't know. These are H.Q.'s orders.
Kagami!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
You guys are Natives?!
Natives?!
For now, protect them!
Save me!
He is the top's son, right? Why doesn't he help us?
The top's son?
ZECT members.
This time you've created a
lousy Anti-Mimic Bomb, it seems?
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Hold on!
Misaki! Are you okay?
Tadokoro!
Just what do you know?
I am...
What does it mean that I am the top of ZECT's son?
And...
Who are the Natives?
Let's go.
Today's cuisine is gold shining roots.
Gold Shining Roots
Gold Flakes Roots
It's the first I've tasted this.
Next time I'd like to have silver shining roots.
Renge! Hurry with the treatment!
Okay.
This is bad! This is bad.
Calm down!
It doesn't look like a deep wound.
Renge. Take care of the rest.
Hey! What are you doing?!
That's your lover, the most important
person in the world! Where are you going?!
That was... just an act.
I'm sorry.
An... act?!
Then... the two of you aren't a couple...
I see! All of it was an ordeal
to test my love with Misakinu!
This is the noblesse oblige of love and friendship!
Wait!
Stop!
I'm the commissioner's son!
There's something I want to ask him.
Do you have an appointment?
He's trying to break in!
Seize him!
Let go!
What are you doing?!
A reckless fellow as always.
Father.
To you, I may merely be your father.
But... here I am the commissioner.
Know the difference!
And the commissioner is the top of ZECT?!
Wait!
Let go! Father!
Hey! Father!
Sis...
Misakinu!
That's it! I have Misakinu.
The two of us should stand on the top of love.
Looks like I have to be blunt.
I...
Now...
Breakfast.
But... how did you get this in here?
Wait! Before my precious
Misakinu eats, I will test it.
Hey!
This is... rotten.
It's natto.
Nat...
Nattu?
Then, what's this?
Tofu.
Tufu?
How strange.
Terrible!
I'm amazed you can eat this.
Understand? We live in different worlds.
Don't think about me anymore.
Father...
Father.
Why did you keep silent?
That you were ZECT's top.
ZECT and the Natives...
How are they related?
The end is close.
ZECT belongs to the Natives. Even me.
We are merely the Natives' servants.
What?
You became Gatack thanks to the Natives.
Thirty-five years ago we made
the first contact with the Natives.
As soon as the project began...
...your destiny was set.
Then...
Father...
Why was I born?
My soul is...
...with the Natives.
And, the one to carry that notion on...
...is you.
Stop it.
Stop it!
I thought as much.
A stone that existed before the Shibuya
meteorite from seven years ago.
It means another meteorite fell
before the Shibuya meteorite.
Probably thirty-five years ago.
Thirty-five years ago... a meteorite...
The Natives were born from that meteorite.
The humans that made contact with them...
...made a deal with the Natives.
Deal?
The Natives would create the Masked Rider System.
And humanity would protect
the Natives from the Worm.
And the organization to carry
that through would be ZECT.
Wait...
So even the Riders belong to the Natives?
Yes.
The one who entrusted the
belt to me... was a Native.
But a Native is still a Worm!
So what?
You knew ZECT was a suspicious organization.
But the goal to defeat the Worm doesn't change.
Don't be upset by it now.
But I...
...cannot accept it.
Tadokoro.
Hurt... Abandoned on a mountain of trash.
Perfect for someone with
a broken heart, like me.
I'll just rust away here.
I envy you.
Really.
Me too. I wish I was called
a "Young Master" just once.
Don't make it sound so informal.
Smile.
Who are you guys?
How rude.
We're the greatest darkness.
Let's fall to hell.
Perfect.
I am the man who stands
at the top of recklessness.
We'll use the Anti-Mimic Bomb to
sweep away the Worm in Area C3.
You're going to join in.
Me?
But I...
I heard you learned the relationship
between ZECT and the Natives.
I understand your feelings. But right now...
Tadokoro, you knew, didn't you?
All of it from the beginning.
No longer do I...
...want to hear ZECT's orders.
I see.
I understand.
What are you going to do?
I am...
...going to fight to save humanity.
Even if it means doing it by myself.
RIDER KICK
RIDER PUNCH
Danger!!
This sucks.
Sucking is the best, Tsurugi.
You should be my little brother too.
Bro.
Let me ask one thing.
Who put the red shoes in the Rider System?
My precious lost friend.
So it was my father.
Kusakabe Souichi?
And you carried on his will?
He was truly...
The man that walks the path of heaven.
If you desire to walk that path too...
Then I will trust you.
Perhaps, I am a man that you cannot
help having a grudge against.
But...
At least my son...
It's okay.
I have no grudge against Kagami.
When the Worms lose their mimic,
move in and eliminate them.
Kagami. Are you ready?
Yes.
But why did you accept?
It's not for the organization.
It's for someone that I trust.
I appreciate it.
Tadokoro!
The Worms have them surrounded.
They were waiting for us! Kagami
and the others are in danger!
Kagami! Kagami, respond!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cancel the operation!
Tadokoro!
Tadokoro... is a Native?!
Tadokoro.
Kagami!
Kagami! Hey! Kagami!
What are you doing?! Pull yourself together!
I won't trust anyone anymore...
ZECT members!
We saw through your
operation from the beginning!
My grandmother once said...
"People walk on the path of people..."
"And that which opens
the path is the path of heaven."
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Tadokoro!
Kagami!
Are you okay?!
Let's go.
Let go of me!
Kagami!
Misaki! Take care of Kagami.
Come on. Stand up. Let's go. Kagami!
Come on!
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
Hyper Clock Up!
HYPER CLOCK UP
Goodbye.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
We are to exchange the hostage
Natives for the Anti-Mimic Bomb.
He's following the Native's orders
and giving them the Anti-Mimic Bomb.
Your father's feelings... you should catch them.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.