Headquarters' personal elite team, Shadow.
And that's the new rider, TheBee.
Long time no see.
Tadokoro.
You're the most elite in Shadow.
I thought you'd be the most suitable for TheBee.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
We fight the Worms for peace, on humanity's behalf.
We want you to work with us.
Is that the "Perfect Harmony" that you speak of?
I told you before.
I walk the path of heaven.
So, it is you.
Kabuto's true identity.
More importantly, one got away.
Defeating him is the priority.
That trick won't work.
If you defy the organization...
...we have but one choice.
What are you trying to do?
Defeating Kabuto...
...is my mission.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Why don't you fight back?
I have no reason to fight.
Headquarters views you as an enemy!
So, you're just following their orders?
Those not part of the organization
have no right to be a Rider!
Kageyama!
Kabuto!
Hang on!
I'm sorry...
I'm dragging the team down.
Transport him to a hospital! Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Tendou!
I told you to stay out of it!
What are you doing?
Furthermore, you hurt one of my comrades!
Tell him this.
If you meddle with me, you will pay for it.
Meddle with you?!
That's not all.
Because TheBee attacked me, a Worm got away.
TheBee defeated the Worm.
Don't give me that bullshit!
Give my best to your comrade.
Anyway, he should heal
from that wound after a week.
Hey!
Weren't you a bit naive?
Focusing on your subordinate...
...and letting Kabuto escape?
I'm terribly sorry!
But to me, protecting the
lives of my subordinates...
...is to protect the life of the team.
That's just like you.
Well, there's no need to worry.
You'll definitely succeed next time.
I know.
Mishima.
Please try to avoid using that name.
A doctor dies after being
splashed by an unknown poison.
If he was wearing white clothes...
...than it must be the Worm's doing.
Good morning, Big Brother!
Good morning.
Looks delicious!
Oh yeah. You have to thank
Hiyori for making pancakes for me.
I gave her a tulip for that.
A one-of-a-kind one...
That's not good enough.
I've got it. You should cook something for her here.
Big Bro's usual tofu full course!
That's true.
We haven't had that lately.
All right!
A doctor dies after being
splashed by an unknown poison.
Looks like headquarters' information
restriction control didn't make it in time.
So, this is also the Worm?
Looks like the case isn't over yet.
Good morning.
What's wrong? You weren't called to meet here.
I need a favor.
What is it?
Umm...
Please let me work under Yaguruma for a while.
Kagami...
There's a lot that I want to learn.
Please!
Do you have the consent of your superior?
Yes. Misaki was mad, but...
Tadokoro said he'd talk to headquarters.
What do you want to learn from me?
To defeat the Worms, I must become much stronger!
Humans cannot become stronger by themselves.
Do not forget that.
Okay!
So, it's okay?
Remember this.
We, Shadow, don't take things lightly.
Okay!
Thank you very much.
Hiyori.
What are you drawing?
Can you help me for a bit?
Why me?
Why not?
Yaguruma!
Well, look who has too much free time, Kageyama.
Better rest when in the hospital.
Thank you!
I'm sorry...
Because of my blunder...
...the operation wasn't completed.
I can defeat him at any time.
He's afraid of us, so he's probably in hiding.
When that happens, I'll find him!
That's my Kageyama.
Oh right.
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
Come in.
You! You're from Tadokoro's.
He's working with us for a bit.
That naive kid?
I'm not a kid.
I'm Kagami Arata.
Nice to meet you.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I can't do that.
That's not like you. Don't be proud.
Then...
What you made before, Yaguruma.
I'd like to eat mabou tofu.
Umm...
The "Perfect Harmony" that Yaguruma talks of...?
What does that mean?
We Shadow...
...do not allow grandstanding.
We comrades help each other out.
Act in a way to consider the whole team.
If you do that...
...the power of one will become two or three...
...even more than ten times greater.
That is the team's ultimate connection.
That is our Perfect Harmony.
I see!
That's what I like!
That battle from the other day...
Kabuto said there was another Worm didn't he?
Yes.
Probably a lie to get out of fighting me.
That was your mistake.
Kabuto was right.
Another Worm has appeared.
What's wrong?
No.
Nothing.
Anyway, I'm going shopping.
Let me do that.
No. There's an especially good tofu I'm after...
I want to use that for Kageyama.
A photo!
All right!
Okay you two.
Okay.
You look so pretty!
Thank you.
Not one left?
Sorry! All of it was bought up.
That "man walking the path of heaven" person.
That guy!
Where are you going?
I'm going to get it back!
What a petty man.
Payback for losing to me last time?
No. He seemed kind of happy.
He said he was going to have a tofu party.
Didn't get invited?
How lonely for you.
Tofu party?
Yeah... Be sure to come.
I.... don't need to.
Don't be shy.
This is a measly wish from
my beloved little sister.
Tendou!
Why'd you buy all the tofu?
You want tofu in mass?
Yaguruma does!
What?
You thought I'd share?
That arrogant man wouldn't give me tofu.
Yaguruma, unlike you, is an amazing man.
The tofu for example, is so he can
feed his hospitalized subordinate.
Chummy as always, eh?
What?!
Yes?
It's the Worm. Yaguruma is coming.
Understood.
Hey, wait!
I'll say it once more.
With Yaguruma here, you're no longer needed.
If you hurt my comrades once again...
...I'll never forgive you.
You okay with that?
I can't do anything with him...
Hiyori.
Please keep the tofu at the restaurant.
Have we evacuated the people inside yet?
No. We can't do that.
There's a chance the Worm is
impersonating a person among them.
There's one more wedding scheduled.
We'll have them do it.
However... to avoid danger...
Shadow will stand guard during the ceremony,
to ensure everyone's safety.
The analysis of the poison is completed.
It's the same poison from the Worm that
carried out the other serial murders.
If so, then that Worm will definitely
target people in white clothes.
Kagami.
Yes.
I'll check every nook and cranny.
Hello!
A photo for the wedding.
It's safe.
Pardon me!
Excuse me!
It's okay here.
All clear.
How did it go?
Everyone wearing white has been checked.
Will the Furuya family and Shirihara family
please make their way inside...
It's beginning.
Preparations for the ceremony are
complete and will begin shorthly...
Yaguruma, how is it inside?
My subordinates checked.
Shadow's security is perfect.
There isn't a crack for the Worm to enter.
Then the Worm is already outside the church?
Misaki.
Let's begin searching area B4.
Okay.
Kagami.
We should go search too.
Okay.
The lord said unto thee...
"In the blue sky of heaven there was the light...
Day and night separated.
To give a sign...
For time...
For the sun...
For the stars."
The lord said unto thee...
"Thou... will be in the blue sky of heaven...
Thou will shine the light upon the land."
My grandmother said unto thee...
"Thou... will walk the path of heaven...
...and rule over everything."
Tendou...
How did you get in here?
How is this perfect security?
Another uninvited guest is inside.
What?
The choir here...
What you call "Perfect Harmony",
doesn't it seem off here?
What's going on? What?
Everyone, please exit the building!
Come!
Hurry!
Everyone, please hurry this way.
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
So, come by at seven.
Are you really sure about that?
It's already decided.
You're the guest of honor.
Someone...
...is there.
Oh, it's you?
Good timing.
Here.
I left it for you.
Give it to your hospitalized subordinate.
Must we do this?
There is no need for two Riders.
I will defeat Kabuto.
No matter how brightly the stars shine...
...they're no comparison to the sun.
I am the sun.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Tendou and Yaguruma?
Seemed...
...really bad.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Tendou!
Yaguruma!
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
I've destroyed the belt.
He will never appear again.
We still might need Kabuto's power....
I'm going to protect everyone!
Transform.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.