I will defeat all you damn Worms.
Every last one!
The chosen one...
....is me.
You're...?!
Now I will shape the future using these hands.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Good job, Kagami.
You're not Kagami, are you?
Target, lost.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Big Bro, good morning!
Good morning.
Let's eat!
Today's breakfast is wonderful, like yesterday's!
For nothing to appear after all this time...
Then that means their organization
has that kind of power.
What are you talking about?
I've been thinking about
getting into the stock market.
Tendou, I think that would suit you.
Really?
Then maybe I should buy up Juka's school...
I might try being the principal then.
That's great!
So you were not the one who transformed?
Right.
Who did?
Well...
I only saw the guy once before.
He's... how do I put this...?
Anyway, he's a strange guy.
A strange guy?
Those that are not a member of
ZECT are not qualified to be Riders.
Find him.
Misaki.
Yes, sir.
The qualified candidate from
headquarters has been found.
Then I will bring the belt to the meeting point.
No... there's somewhere I'd like you to go first.
It'll be okay.
"I'm by your side."
I'm by your side.
What will we do when we
find the guy who transformed?
Don't tell me we'll let him join up.
If he's useful, then that's a possibility.
That sucks.
But hold on...
If we do that, I can put him below me.
Then I'll no longer be on the bottom!
That's great!
The problem is if he decides to not join ZECT.
Well, what happens then?
In that situation, we'd need to eliminate him.
Are we allowed to do that?!
In this day and age?
Here in Japan?!
That's what's required for the mission.
Better if you realize that now than later.
Awesome.
I don't know who this guy from
headquarters is... but surely it's a waste on him.
Go already. It's time for your part time job, right?
This is the place?
One basilik salmon, please.
Here.
And that's not all, because in fact...
What is it?!
How rude!
Smoke.
How very rude! No need to
ridicule us! Why can't we smoke?!
Right?
Forget it.
What do you mean "Forget it"?!
What a chicken.
Wh-What are you doing there?
What's the meaning of this?
What?
Hey what's your problem?
Putting it out is common sense.
It's not good for the child.
Bastard!
Go! Let's get outta here!
Savor your shame,
now get lost.
Savor your shame, now get lost.
Mackerel miso.
Like I said, mackerel miso.
We don't have that.
You cannot deceive my nose.
It's probably what the cook is making.
Hiyori.
Why don't we give him some?
Red miso and white miso...
...and a new blend of miso, right?
This will be the second time I say this about
another's cooking, since my grandmother cooked for me...
Delicious.
It's my first time cooking.
So, I made mackerel miso.
Such a waste.
You make better mackerel miso than me.
You should be more confident.
You're... a weird guy, aren't you?
Your name is Hiyori, right?
It's no good addressing your
customer in such a informal way.
Then... how should I address you?
My grandmother once said...
"He who walks the path of heaven..."
Good morning!
I'm starved.
Aren't you on the last shift, Kagami?
Oh, i just wanted to try Hiyori's mackerel miso.
Yo.
Tendou...
Good timing. I came here to see you.
Huh...?
I want to talk to you about the organization ZECT...
Can we talk outside?
I see.
So you keep ZECT a secret from the restaurant.
More important, why do you have a Rider belt?!
Tell me about ZECT!
Then I will tell.
I can't give you the details.
But believe us! We risk our
lives to fight the Worms.
We protect peace.
That's not precise.
It's not that you can't tell me...
...it's that you don't know anything.
Sorry, but I don't trust those
who are not well informed.
That aside, please be our comrade!
Please!
Like this!
Very well.
Really?
However!
You will be below me.
What?!
It is only natural...
I am the strongest, aren't I?
I'm doing this for your sake!
Can't you tell?!
Your desperation tells me one thing.
If I resist, they'll get ride of me..
If I mess up, I'll be killed.
And that's how ZECT works isn't it?
That guy...
Yes.
Go to the meeting point that Misaki is at.
Something happen?
The candidate has been killed.
I understand, I'll be right there.
The Worm came straight for him.
They knew he was the one who
was qualified for wearing the belt.
That's why the enemy is
such a terrifying opponent.
Tendou's in danger...
No matter how strong,
the unarmed are no match for the Worm.
If one transforms, can they
match the Worm's Clock Up?
Of course.
Kagami...
Wait! What are you doing?!
Wait for me, Tendou!
This time I will fight!
I know what you're thinking.
In this location, the Zecter
can't reach me to transform.
That's why you think you can win.
But...
You are underestimating my power.
If I say "come".
Then he...
...will come.
This time I will become a Rider.
Then I will defeat you bastards!
Come! Kabuto Zecter!
Because...
...I am the chosen one!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Why?!
Why doesn't it come to me?!
They used Clock Up!
Tendou!
Hang on!
Who can you save if you get killed?
Looks like the hero type doesn't suit you.
Shut up!
Listen!
The Masked Rider System has
the ability to combat Clock Up.
You have to find that!
I already know how.
What?!
Sorry, but I've had a long
relationship with the belt.
I just wanted to see how far I could go in this form.
Don't tell me...
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
In the Clock Up Rider form, one is capable
of speeds greater than any human.
CLOCK OVER
That was... Kabuto.
Wait, that's my bike!
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
CLOCK OVER
ONE TWO THREE
Rider...
...Kick
RIDER KICK
I see.
So at last, Kabuto is...
However...
We cannot allow someone
outside of ZECT to be a Rider.
Are you...
...fond of owls?
Yes...
Even if its prey are
covered in absolute darkness.
Even if its breath is stilled as it hides...
It gracefully brings it down.
It's a beautiful sight.
I will definitely...
...search and find him.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
You're not fit to be a member of ZECT.
What are you?
What are you?!
Your organization's true power...
ZECT's power, you will show it to me.
What are they after?
What's their criteria for picking victims?
We haven't a clue.
My grandmother once said...
"Make the world revolve around you."
"It's more fun to think that way."
Who are you?!
"It was more than a meteorite
that fell from space" right?
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.