Transform!
TRANSFORM
CHANGE PUNCH HOPPER
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
Tachikawa.
That guy...
...how is he related to Hiyori?
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
I broke a nail!
It's because you grow them too long.
Focus on what you're doing.
That was great!
Broke another one.
Let me have that.
Hey. What are you doing?
Special training. To prepare
Renge for working at Salle.
Ms. Renge, I'm glad you passed.
Okay. I'm off!
Have a...
Have a good time!
You're awake?
Where is this?
Don't worry. This place is...
Hey. Why are you able to transform into Drake?
Are you being chased by the Worms because of that?
Say something!
Kagamin!
How is your friend?
A friend's friend is everybody's friend.
That's why you and I are friends.
Thanks for your help.
Hey!
Wait!
Let me go!
Do you know who he really is?
Kagamin!
Get away from him!
Stop, Tsurugi!
So you are a Worm!
Stop it!
I can't do that even for my best friend!
TRANSFORM
CAST OFF
CLOCK UP
Yumeko, I'm sorry.
Don't you think it's strange?
That Tachikawa Worm.
He's being chased by other Worms.
And he can transform into Drake and Sasword.
And the thing I understand least is why
ZECT is giving out orders to protect him.
He came to tell me to stop collecting the Zecters.
Who is he?
I've seen that type of Worm before.
Eighteen years ago...
The ones that killed and mimicked my parents...
...were that type.
Then those Worms were here before the
meteorite from seven years ago. Eighteen years...
Could it be they have been
here even longer than that?
They call themselves "Natives".
Could it be...
...a different species than the Worm we know?
Natives...
A different species...
I'm sure he's related to Hiyori somehow.
We've got to find him before
the Worms eliminate him.
Have all of ZECT's teams search every location!
Understood.
But do not attack, no matter what!
If found, contact me.
Okay.
Do not tell H.Q.
I didn't hear anything about this.
Someone like you is not allowed
to give orders without my okay.
Why do I need confirmation from someone like you?
Yes.
The organization will not benefit
from you two being prideful.
Refrain from doing it anymore.
Yes, sir.
I'm glad you're the one that called for me.
There's something I want to ask.
You!
Whom do you think you're addressing?
It's fine. You can go.
Excuse me.
What is it?
What are the Natives?
Don't know...
Are they related to Hiyori somehow?
Hiyori... ah... your only little sister, right?
Is she doing well?
Don't play dumb!
Let me tell you this.
I can destroy ZECT if I want to right now!
Do you know the story of the red shoes?
Red shoes...?
There was a girl...
...she put on red shoes.
She went to a dance party. The shoes started
to dance on their own, and wouldn't stop.
What are you saying?!
It's also in Kabuto and Gatack.
Red shoes that have a will besides your own...
they will keep dancing till all Worm are defeated.
Till all Worm...
...are defeated?
Those shoes will probably
start acting on their own.
No one knows... when that will be.
I will... Hiyori... That's not possible!
Of course he's not going to show up here.
Where did you fall?
Hang in there!
Go on.
Isn't it dangerous?! Appearing in that place,
even though the Worms are after you?
Humans are so frail.
Surely they are an ephemeral life form.
But that is the reason they are lovely.
Are you Worms not humanity's enemy?
We are... allies of humanity.
So there are two species of Worm.
You Natives are the enemies
of the Worms we know.
Right?
We do not like conflict!
We don't want to be caught in the battle
between humans and Worm.
We just want to secretly live among humanity.
Is Hiyori...
...one of you?
I must...
Tell you where Hiyori's location is.
You know?
Transform!
TRANSFORM
I went through all the trouble coming
here to get the Sasword Zecter back...
Tendou, just where is that guy wasting time?
I'm still preparing.
Don't worry. I am the man that
stands at the top of waiting.
That's right!
Why don't I have you try my cooking?
Okay.
Alright!
I am the man that stands at the top of tasting.
It's two burned potatoes.
Two burned potatoes...
Two burned ones...
Two Burned Potatoes
Two potatoes...
Steamed Potatoes
Boiled potatoes, right?
It's the first time I've tasted something like this!
I want to try three burned potatoes!
All right!
The god of fighting, Gatack's chosen one.
Kagami Arata.
Why do you know that?
The one that controls the light. God of the sun.
Kabuto's chosen one.
Kusakabe Souji.
What?
Tendou! What is it?!
Tendou!
What's going on?
Tendou! Pull yourself together!
What is it?!
Tendou!
Tendou...
Stop it! Stop! Are you trying to kill him?!
Your grand plan will probably
be completed by our sons.
RIDER KICK
Tendou! Come to your senses!
Run.
Do not worry.
Kusakabe.
Tendou...
What is it...
Tendou?
Who's there?
No matter what... we're not
walking on a path with sunlight.
The sun is polluted!
Kageyama...
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Transform.
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
CHANGE PUNCH HOPPER
Let's go, partner.
I'll follow you anywhere, Bro.
What do we have here?
RIDER JUMP
RIDER PUNCH
RIDER KICK
Bro...
Tendou...
Tendou.
Tendou!
Are you okay?!
I...!
What... have I been doing?
You don't remember?
Hey! If I hadn't interfered you
would have attacked Tachikawa!
Those words...
...were true.
Kabuto and Gatack have a will besides
our own to destroy all Worms.
You can say...
...a berserk mechanism switch is set in them.
A will besides our own?
What's that?
Talk later! First... Tachikawa...
I must hear where Hiyori's location is from him!
Tachikawa!
Transform!
Hang on!
Hey!
A complete solar eclipse...
...search for it.
An eclipse...
Hiyori is...
...there.
Hey! Hey!
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
Hyper Clock Up.
HYPER CLOCK UP
MAXIMUM RIDER POWER
ONE TWO THREE
Hyper Kick!
RIDER KICK
HYPER CLOCK OVER
Tendou!
You know everything, don't you?
About the Hopper.
The door of Hell has opened.
Yes...
Darkness itself is coming.
I'm hungry.
When I went out of control before...
...you did a good job stopping me.
I'm grateful.
Stop it. That's not like you.
I'm going to give back all
the Zecters I've collected.
The only one who can
stop a berserk Rider...
...is a Rider.
Promise me...
If I ever go berserk and try to kill Hiyori...
...you will kill me.
However...
If the situation is reversed, I will kill you.
Okay?
A berserk switch?
Is there really such a thing in Gatack too?
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Members from our baseball team have vanished.
The devil's door opened?
First a cursed mirror,
then a missing choir club. Interesting.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.