Tendou!
Tendou.
I'm not saving you.
I told you before.
You're forgetting something important!
So, what is that supposed to mean?!
Daisuke!
Him again?
No choice...
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Gon.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Who... are you?
I can't believe you are also a chosen one.
It's not like I wished for this.
I'd like to know your name.
Tendou Souji.
The man who walks the path of heaven,
and will rule over everything.
You really are quite peculiar.
I'd say the same for you.
Hey, where are you going?
To follow the Worm. One got away.
What about you, Daisuke?
Aren't you going to chase after that monster?
Not my problem.
Hey, what's going on?
What are you talking about?
You said it just now! I'm forgetting
something important or whatever?
You should figure that out yourself.
So, all our dates in the party were Worms.
Just what are you into?
It's not my fault!
Have you seen a woman in grey pants?
Oh. Over there.
Tendou!
This is...
...the woman we just saw!
It's mimicked again.
Today is medley soup! It looks delicious!
Yeah. It's wheat medley soup.
I picked up umeboshi, takowan,
chirimen and much more.
Please add whatever you like before eating it.
Amazing, good!
Oh yeah, Bro.
I wonder if I can learn to cook too.
What do you think?
Juka, you should be able to cook well.
You are my little sister after all.
Alright! Then I'll let Mr. Kagami try it.
Please don't mention that guy right now.
Why?
He's your friend, right?
Juka.
Juka, you don't know yet.
What a dangerous word "friend" is.
This man is...
...Drake's chosen one.
Yes.
Kazama Daisuke.
Occupation: Make up artist.
Gon.
Puff #2.
No history of his address or any
company that has employed him.
Three months ago, he was seen
with an amnesiac girl.
He seems rather interesting.
Make Up.
Perfect.
Mr. Kazama, when you do my make
up, I always feel ten times prettier.
Thank you.
You really saved me.
Because I have an important date right now.
I'm jealous of your date.
Descending on this world, you are a beautiful...
Ummm... beautiful...
...goddess.
Yes, yes. That, that.
Drake belongs to ZECT.
If it isn't....
Then perhaps...
Have you ever heard of
the "grave of the elephants"?
That is... naught but a myth.
But...
I think I need it.
Yes...
One who is being destroyed...
...needs a grave.
ZECT?
Yeah.
It's a secret organization that fights the Worms.
The item you use to transform into
Drake was originally developed by ZECT.
But the Drake Zecter has chosen you.
Would you please join us?
Join ZECT.
Not interested.
This Drake or whatever it is...
I didn't wish for that power.
Rather, it's an inconvenience for me.
I was just thrown into a
situation I know nothing about.
Inconvenience?
But as a chosen one, you have a duty to fight.
A duty to save people. Right?
I'm saying that's an inconvenience to me.
I'm a wind that blows from flower to flower.
No one can catch the wind.
Hang on!
Please...
Please join ZECT.
You sure are stubborn.
If you don't... something bad will happen.
It's no use...
Threats don't work on me.
Kazama style ascension technique...
Ultimate Make Up.
What?
That guy...!
How can this be?!
But... this is kind of nice.
What do you want to say?
I want to know about ZECT's upcoming plans.
More people like Kabuto might appear.
People that are Riders,
yet not affiliated with ZECT.
Are you planning to eliminate them all?!
That's ridiculous!
Are you not well?
No.
It's nothing to worry about.
This is my dietary cure.
I don't have a sense of taste.
This is my supplement.
By the way, where is Tadokoro?
My meeting today was supposed to be with him.
He isn't coming.
I thought you wouldn't meet with me...
...so I used Tadokoro.
I'm sorry.
Leave.
You don't know anything about ZECT.
Know your place.
How pretty.
I'm a failure, Misaki.
Nothing I do works.
I wasn't able to get Kazama Daisuke.
And Tendou's treating me coldly.
A croquette soba please.
Okay.
This is what he says to me.
"You're forgetting something important."
I don't know what he's talking about at all.
I think I kind of know.
What do you mean?
It means "Why are you a member of ZECT?"
Well, looks like we both have our troubles.
Let's do our best.
Thank you!
Tendou!
I didn't come to see you.
I know that already...
We can only offer shared tables right now.
I don't mind.
Then this way.
Well, well.
We meet again.
What a mysterious connection we have.
Yet having it doesn't please me at all.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
What would you like?
What do you recommend?
Tuna covered with spiced vegetables.
I'll take that.
The same.
Me too!
Then...
Here.
What is this?
A scratch ticket.
If you win you get 100 yen off.
Regardless, you are beautiful.
You are a bud that will
bloom into a special flower.
I look forward to that.
Stop it.
Someone like you doesn't
deserve to talk to Hiyori.
Why don't we finish this?
Let's see who's more popular with the ladies?
Although I did humiliate you
in the previous dating party.
What humiliation?
They were all monsters. It didn't count.
Then in one hour in Kazegaoka Park
Let's see who brings more girls?
Okay.
Until there's a winner to the match.
Why have a match?
I won.
I won too.
A miss, huh?
This...
...shows nothing about one's character.
To rejoice in this just shows
the size of your container.
Female...
Hello?
Girls...
There's this weird guy here.
He was staring.
It really grossed me out.
'Girls Pro Wrestling Lab'
Who the hell are ya?!
What a waste.
You girls do not yet know your own beauty?
What was that?!
Kazama style ascension technique.
Ultimate Make Up.
Flowers...
...have bloomed.
Hiyori, seconds.
A scratch ticket too.
Tendou! I'll help too!
What are you doing here?!
What bullshit, what are you doing?
Now, let's go, everyone.
Okay!
Mr. Kazama.
Yukari.
Good timing.
I need your help too.
I won.
Way to go!
Hiyori.
How much was it?
Where'd it go?
That guy really is a weirdo.
You're so cute!
Looks like I win.
Hey!
Isn't that Tendou Souji?
It's true!
It's really him!
This...
...is impossible!
They're all your friends?!
No.
The girls just know of me.
Just as there is no one who does
not know the light of the sun.
"He who walks the path of heaven
will rule over everything."
All girls are flowers.
And flowers know...
...that they blooms because of the sun.
But numbers don't matter.
What's that?!
Yukari is the most beautiful.
Looks like you're stuck to superficial faces.
It's not something to compare with women.
My grandmother once said...
"All girls are equally beautiful."
Besides, that woman... is not human.
What are you saying?
After doing your make up, you always
use the perfume Happiness at the end.
I don't smell this from her at all.
Even if mimicking...
...you cannot copy one's smell.
It can't be...
Hurry and go.
Gon!
Transform.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Tendou!
Kagami!
Don't use "friendship" as an
excuse to depend on me.
For what reason did you join ZECT?
I...
He means "Why did you become a member of ZECT?"
That's right.
I...
I joined to defeat all Worms.
Tendou...
I finally understand.
You and I...
...are not friends.
That's right.
We're not friends.
Come on over to my home.
I'll make you something delicious to eat.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE DRAGONFLY
Mr. Kazama.
Yukari.
Do my make up again.
Make me...
...more beautiful than anyone else.
Daisuke.
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
Ms. Yukari...
Worms use the image of a human...
to exploit the weakness in one's heart.
Don't be deceived.
What you said is right...
But...
I don't like it!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Starting today, a new member will join our team.
Shadow members are being eliminated one by one?!
I will protect your lives.
I will protect you!
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.