MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
Tsurugi!
Misaki!
Stop it, Tsurugi!
Misakinu... What was I...
It can't be...
You are...
It can't be you are... a Worm, right?
I'm a Worm?
That can't be!
What are you saying, you bastard?!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
I'm a...
I'm a Worm...
Damn it...
I...
Mika?!
I killed her...
And then... myself.
You knew, didn't you?
That Tsurugi was a Worm.
Well...
Why didn't you tell me?! Why?!
Why did you keep silent, Jiiya?
Don't play dumb. You knew I was
a Worm all along, didn't you?
T-that...
I must destroy all Worms! That includes me!
I see... Kamishiro Tsurgui is...
Why did you keep silent?
It couldn't be helped.
It's not like this hasn't been on my mind... But...
I just didn't know what to do.
There is no need to ponder about this.
If he's a Worm, then he must be defeated.
Wait a minute.
He's not a bad guy. You know that.
He's the same...
As Tadokoro and Hiyori.
Don't lump them together!
He even killed Tsurugi's older sister.
And he's surely attacked other humans.
Well...
That...
I will protect Misaki.
Tsurugi...
Delicious!
Your Christmas cake is the best.
Isn't that true?
Here.
Thank you.
Juka... I want you to always smile.
And Hiyori...
I promise you. I will change the world.
Make it into a world where you can smile.
I will definitely do it.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Transform!
Tsurugi...
Tsurgui!
Stop it, Tsurugi! Please stop!
Seems you've also become a full Worm.
From now on stay by my side and do my work.
Watch your mouth.
If you don't want to die, that is.
What are you trying to do?
Kamishiro Tsurugi.
No... Kamishiro Tsurugi died.
And I have been reborn as the strongest Worm.
Don't get cocky!
You guys will work for me.
I... will stand on the top of all that is Worm.
Young Master...
Young Master... please take care of him.
Please... grant Young Master's wish.
Tsurugi...
I believed.
You may be a Worm, but...
You can live as a human.
Even now I believe that.
Here.
Take it, Tsurugi.
It's a present from Misaki.
Misaki is also worried about you.
Tsurugi... you...!
Live as a human?
Fool.
I will defeat all humans.
Let every Worm know.
Very soon, the last battle will begin.
Kagami Arata is in my hands.
Tadokoro.
What is a Worm?
What is a human?
I don't know either.
But perhaps we are fighting
to find the answer to that.
A trade for Kagami's life.
Bring all the Zecters.
If the Rider System is destroyed,
we Worm will have nothing to fear.
There is a person who has
watched you since you were a child.
He took your requests.
He granted your wishes.
I only have one wish.
Since the battle of Area Z, the Worms
have continued their random attacks.
It's like they can't stop moving.
Tadokoro, There's a change
in the Worms' movement.
They're all headed for the same place.
Tendou, stop! Stay away!
Tendou...
It's the end of the Riders.
As promised. Set him free.
Tendou...
It's over.
From today on our Worm era begins.
Stop!
This building is surrounded by ZECT.
So what?
You have no hope.
Get them.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Transform!
STANDBY
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Shall we try seeking it one more time?
The light...
Yeah.
Let's go, Bro.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
CHANGE PUNCH HOPPER
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Bro!
RIDER JUMP
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Rider Punch!
RIDER PUNCH
RIDER KICK
That's...
Could it be... Tsurugi...
Tendou! Stop!
No!
Misakinu, please forgive me.
Just once I wish we could have gone on a date.
I made a plan. First, we'd drink tea.
Then we'd go to an amusement park.
And then, we'd have the ultimate Christmas.
Hyper Cast Off!
HYPER CAST OFF
CHANGE HYPER BEETLE
No! Stop it!
KABUTO POWER
THEBEE POWER
DRAKE POWER
SASWORD POWER
ALL ZECTER COMBINE
No, Tendou!
What's wrong, Tendou?!
Remember our promise!
Stop it!
MAXIMUM HYPER TYPHOON
Tsurugi!
Bro... you alive?
Dunno.
Why?
Why?!
I told you to stop...
Tsurugi was... still Tsurugi.
I know.
But...
I was able to keep Tsurugi's promise.
Promise?
He always said it...
"Defeat all Worm."
By his power, he was able to
make that dream come true.
Tsurugi...
Young Master!
Hey, Jiiya.
What is it?
Is it okay for me to dream?
Yes.
Don't worry about anything.
Jiiya will always be by your side.
Thank you, Jiiya.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
"The sun is wonderful.
It can even make the dirt shine."
With this, Kabuto is an enemy to
society, no... an enemy to peace.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.