Against the dark chefs that manipulated
the body and mind of powerful men...
Always sincere, they lived so people
could have a bit of happiness.
The chefs of light existed.
The man that stood at the top
of those chefs passed down a single knife.
It's name is the White Knife.
I have won.
I will... avenge you.
I swear it!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Kagami.
What did you want to talk about?
Well...
Actually... Ummm...
Misakinu!
Misakinu! Today I formally
ask you out on a date.
Now... let's go back to my mansion.
You...
I am thinking only of you!
Misakinu!
Misaki, please run.
Thanks.
Hey! What do you want with Misaki?
I will protect Misakinu!
I swear to protect her... with these hands.
Once before....
I wasn't able to protect my sister.
But! Right now I'm stronger than all others!
You. As well as Tendou will not get in my way.
The scorpion Worm... With these
hands I will definitely defeat him!
He doesn't realize that he's a Worm?
It's a special miso sauce shabu. Please try it.
Let's eat!
Really...
Really?
What's wrong, Tendou?
N-nothing.
Could it be? You're in a slump?
Big trouble! Big trouble!
H-hey! How many times must I say it?!
What is it? You're being noisy!
Someone's here without a reservation!
What?
You...!
I heard the rumors.
You are the one that inherited
Kyokai Seki's technique.
Show it to me.
I challenge you.
Eat mine first.
I'll leave the truth to you.
Are you stupid?
Letting the enemy be the judge.
This is... This is out of this world!
The flavor and fragrance are
completely different from my sashimi!
Judgement by knife is faster than light.
That is because, it's a dark technique
where the light cannot reach.
You did not realize this match was such that you
could deal judgement on yourself, did you?
For punishment...
Look.
I lost!
I am taking this sign.
Big trouble, Boss! An intruder!
Be quiet.
What?
The legendary Oe Domai technique...
Show it to me.
I challenge you!
I'm taking this curtain.
Heaven...
You!
This soba is pretty good.
The consistency is miraculous.
You have a discerning tongue.
You are?
Tadokoro.
Our Chief.
This shop is my little brother's shop.
Exactly!
This soba shop has been
passed down in our family.
My brother is actually better
at cooking than me. But!
I inherited it.
Don't talk so much.
Well. Take your time.
Show me the technique you
inherited from Shinisei Sogoya.
You...
I challenge you.
Here to lay waste to my soba shop?!
B-Bro!
Don't panic!
Tadokoro's flavor that's held for
three hundred years cannot lose.
Good.
Now... eat mine.
This is...!
Sooooo good!
It's amazing!
The flavor of the cutting.
The deepness.
This technique isn't human.
It's heaven!
No... no way!
This curtain... is mine.
Wait.
What are you doing this for?
I tear up the pride of all the chefs.
And send them to the depths of Hell.
Then I will be the unchallenged chef of the world.
My cooking can control emotions.
I'll use it to rule the world.
I knew you stunk.
I cannot let you be.
Challenge me again.
Okay.
I will finish you off.... so that
you can never stand again!
What? You challenged that man?
Please.
Please... train me from the beginning.
I will endure anything.
Anything?
Then...
You wouldn't mind going to Hell?
Right.
Then...
Here.
What's this?
I thought this might happen, so I prepared it.
There is a chef's training ground
that's unknown to the world.
This is a letter of introduction to that place.
Go.
Okay.
Mr. Kagami.
Today's cooking is wonderful.
It makes me feel really good.
I am honored that you are pleased.
Enjoy yourselves.
I came to train my cooking.
Please train me.
The man who wrote that letter of
introduction is my twin little brother.
But I live in these mountains,
so I don't teach people to cook.
Please!
Teach me the true meaning of cooking.
Look!
Those are the graves of people who risked
their lives, but were not able to master cooking.
Are you saying you would not
mind meeting the same fate?
I am prepared.
Then... try cooking this dust cloth!
Amen.
I'm so happy.
Cloth tempura.
But what's the meaning of this?
How am I supposed to eat this?!
This is the best!
This is heaven.
Cloth steak.
It's in sauce, so you can at
least squeeze it and drink that.
I don't like it!
It really is amazing cooking.
Please introduce the chef.
Definitely.
Understood.
I am also honored by your compliments.
I cut the cloth into bits and wrapped it in udon.
You should be able to eat it now...
Now you people are captives of my cooking.
And... eventually the hearts of
everyone will be my slaves.
Just what should I do?
What is the old man trying to have me do?
What's this?
That's... my response.
You do not cook cloth.
Everything in this world has a true nature.
Being able to see that is important.
What can you do seeing
the true nature of things?!
Knowing nature...
...is to know oneself.
You have grasped the true meaning of cooking.
You have become a chef of light.
This White Knife is proof of that.
Now in the Dark Kitchen is a cooking contest
between Ikesu Isshiro and Tendou Soujirou.
The theme is miso soup.
The loser will be stripped of
their value and honor as a cook.
Okay!
Where's the opponent?
So he ran away with his tail between his legs?
It can't be help. He has no chance
of winning no matter how he struggles.
I am your opponent!
Mika.
I will avenge you.
I swear it.
That guy...
Start!
The Tadokoro Unblemished Knife,
sealed away for many years...
I can't believe I will hold it again.
It's rusted!
I compliment you for not running away.
Is that...?
The legendary White Knife.
Just what should I do?
If you don't mind...
Please use this.
I would be honored to use it.
The Black Knife and White Knife don't matter.
What's important...
Fool.
White radish?
Is such a common miso
soup supposed to beat me?
I'll open your eyes with my
transcendental miso soup.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Heaven.
It has egg whites combined with the miso bowl.
Truly artistic.
Is it so bad that there is no comment?
No...
It's so good there is no right expression for it.
The flavor of this miso soup...
...is above heaven.
All I can say is just one thing.
Compared to this flavor...
...yours...
...is pig food!
Pig... food?!
That's impossible!
This is... what is this white radish?
During the cooking I went outside...
I exposed the finely sliced
radish to the gentle breeze.
With a coating of its gentle breath,
the radish developed a consistency.
Using the gentle breeze as seasoning?!
Exiting the forest...
This gentle breeze crossed the
river and blows into the miso soup!
You rely too much on your technique.
So you do not have the world's flavor.
My grandmother once said...
"One that is self absorbed,
will eventually fall to darkness."
In this match, victory goes to me.
It's true...
Well done.
Let me reward you.
I see.
So that's how it is.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Stop!
Stop it!
Tendou!
Stop it, Tendou!
Stop it!
Kagami... what are you trying to do?
Are you... serious?
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
To know the truth, is only for
he who walks heaven's path.
When dealing with a Worm... I show them no mercy.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.