All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Good morning!
What is this?!
The manager is very angry.
He said this cost him a lot.
He said he'll take it out of your paycheck, Kagami.
Why..?
Aren't these supplies for the restaurant?
Cash on delivery?
Kagami Arata.
It's addressed to me?!
Hello!
This is the restaurant Salle, right?
I was told to come here to receive the matsuwa.
Matsuwa?
They're so shiny!
My grandmother once said...
"If you're going to eat it anyway... then first, eat the best one first!"
She said.
The way you speak...
Don't tell me you're Tendou's...
Little sister!
This way! This way!
Can he cook?
Of course.
And he's as good as a pro.
Please say that I'm better than a pro.
There it is again!
I'm sure you must get tired
of Big Brother's arrogant manner.
I'm sorry!
Hey.
Big Brother said recently he
found what he wanted to do.
Something he wanted to do?
Do you know anything about it?
Well...
That's...
Anyway...
You two live in this big house?
Tokyo Dome is right there.
Yup.
But... I'm not lonely at all.
I'm with Big Brother after all.
"Big Brother" eh?
Those words bring up memories.
What?
You have a litter sister too?
No.
A little brother.
Delicious...
This is the first time I've ever
eaten such delicious mackerel miso.
This is awesome!
No good...
It's nothing compared to Hiyori's.
It's lacking something.
Hang on...
I have work!
Kagami, that idiot.
He left me alone...
Hey! It's overflowing!
Mr. Kagami!
Come again!
Because Mr. Kagami, you're the
first friend Big Brother has ever made.
Not really.
It's not like we're friends.
Big Bro, quiet you.
Make me a promise, okay?
A promise, eh?
What are you doing?!
I don't need it.
They said I'd never be a pitcher.
You won't know that unless you try!
Don't be ridiculous!
If you can't be a pitcher, then
there are still other positions.
Don't give up!
Make me a promise.
Try practicing again.
Alright.
Big Brother.
Ryou!
Where are you?!
Big Brother?
Ryou...
Kagami's still not here?
Yo!
This is a present from Kagami.
It's matsuwa mackerel.
Man...
To force me to bring it... what a cold guy.
Where's Kagami?
He hasn't returned yet?
It's his job.
He should get fried.
I think so too.
By the way...
Please make mackerel miso for me again.
I want to know the secret of its deliciousness.
I don't have any secrets.
All you have to do is let me watch as you make it.
No way.
Okay, do it after we finish this.
Don't decide that by yourself.
By the way...
Do you know anything
about Kagami's little brother?
Did something happen?
No...
Nothing.
It seems he disappeared...
...two years ago.
Hey Bro...
Why aren't you saying anything?
You...
Why did you suddenly disappear?
I was worried.
Sorry.
I'm not as strong as you, Bro.
I just got fed up with everything.
You didn't even write me one letter.
I was sure the Worm got you.
Worm?
What's that?
Hey, look Bro.
We used to love playing like that.
Yeah...
We'd play till it was dark,
and we couldn't see anymore.
Look here...
This is still my greatest treasure.
Ever since I was little...
...Bro, you were always my hero.
The time I spent hitting balls
at Koushi Park's mound, Bro...
...do you know how happy it made me and Father?
Ryou...
You...
Sorry.
I always have work. I have to go.
Can we meet again... tomorrow?
At that playground?
I'll be there.
Definitely.
Bye.
By the way, I...
...was attacked by something weird recently.
Weird?
And then... something even more weird showed up.
And defeated the weird thing.
Was that really weird?
What could that have been?
Sorry, Hiyori for being late!
You're way too late!
Yo.
What?!
Tendou is here too?!
Good timing!
Let's have a party tomorrow!
A Hiyori mackerel miso party!
Hold on...
I'm making it?
Please! It's for a celebration!
You seem pretty happy.
My little brother is back.
My little brother was gone for so long...
No doubt about it.
That's my little brother.
Hey, which is better, red or white?
You!
Kagami's little brother has returned.
Doesn't that seem a little too convenient?
Go investigate using your powers at ZECT.
Who are you?!
Wait!
Kagami Ryou.
Disappeared 2 years ago.
Your little brother, right?
Right.
I checked with headquarters,
it's highly likely he's a Worm mimic.
It'll just be us for this case.
You'll be on standby.
Why are you taking me out?!
Let me do this too!
If the time comes, can you kill a Worm
that has the same face as your little brother?
I can!
No.
Just give it up this time.
Misaki...
Why did you investigate my little brother?
I was told to.
By the man who stole the Rider Bike.
That bastard...
Yo!
Looks like your off your gleeful high.
Now let's go back and have a mackerel miso party.
You bastard!
Why did you talk about my little brother?!
Did you think I'd forgive you for letting
me know my little brother is a Worm?!
That's correct.
You were not facing reality.
Shut up!
I'll fight you any time you want...
But right now, you will tell me
where your little brother is.
I will...
...defeat him.
If he's a Worm...
...then he...
...killed Ryou.
I'll finish him.
That's why I joined ZECT.
Listen to me.
Don't get in my way.
Very well.
That was some punch.
Bro!
You came.
Of course I did.
Because I didn't keep my
promise from two years ago.
I waited here that day.
After you disappeared, I felt like
something was missing inside me.
Something important.
That was when I quit baseball.
I'm sorry.
But I won't run away anymore.
I also plan to tell Father everything.
Are you really Ryou?
You're Ryou, right?
What are you saying?!
I was followed?
Bro...
What's this?
Who are these people?
Stop!
Stop it!
Fire!
Bro...
You killed my little brother didn't you?!
Oh come on.
How many times must I say it?
I'm Ryou.
Why do you know things only
my little brother would know?!
When I mimic a human...
...I also receive their memories.
That's why, I'm Ryou.
Stay away!
I'll fire.
At me?
Can you do that, Bro?
If I'm gone, the memories of
Ryou inside me will be gone too.
My friends say they want to mimic you. Bro.
But don't be afraid.
Bro, after you die, you'll continue
to live on eternally as a Worm.
So...
Join me.
Let's play baseball together.
My grandmother once said...
"When people love others they become weaker...
But... it is nothing to be ashamed of.
Because that is not true weakness."
Right?
Only those who know weakness...
...will become truly stronger.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Why aren't you fighting back?
Don't tell me you're...
What'll you do?
You decide.
You won't let me disappear, right?
You sacrificed everything for me,
I'm the only thing you're proud of.
Please stop it...
Kabuto!
Please!
Cast Off...
CAST OFF
CHANGE BEETLE
CLOCK UP
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick...
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
Bro...
Tendou!
Someday, I will...
I will surpass you!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Misaki, what's the meaning of this?
I'll be waiting for you under
Tokyo Tower at four o'clock.
Father...
The plan to capture Kabuto
is already in progress.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.