ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Hiyori.
Let's go home.
I heard from Mishima.
Come on.
What are you doing?!
You lowly monster!
What is with that attitude, you lowly human?
Watch your tone.
Understand?
Your reply?
Okay.
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
In the end, I wasn't able to figure anything out.
Just what is the Masked Rider Project?
Why is my name in a file
from thirty-five years ago?
Maybe...
What?
The name in that file!
Maybe that wasn't Kagami Arata.
Maybe it's Kaga Bishin?
In other words... someone else.
On a list from thirty-five years ago,
is the name of your unborn son.
Why is that?
The reason for that...
...is probably known best by you, right?
Indeed...
There is too much I don't know.
Or else...
Maybe the name is Ka Gabishin!
Enough.
Nothing will come about
from your shallow thinking.
'Arriving on a gentle breeze.
He is the genius makeup artist.'
This man...
Kazama...
Daisuke.
Gon.
Daisuke!
The number you have called...
...is currently not in use.
Please check the phone number and call again.
I have to go do something.
So I'm going out for a bit
Yuriko
Seems like your plan failed.
In the end, the power of your
people cannot beat the Riders.
I could say the same for you.
Even though you created the Rider System...
...it's very different from how you imagined it.
At the moment, it's in our
best interests to work together.
What's so funny?
I never imagined I would be joining with humans.
I'm the same way.
How can I work with a Worm?
But who cares about that?
As long as we eliminate that
which must be eliminated.
I do not make poor actions.
Okay?
I do not either.
Mishima.
Is this really okay?
Joining with the Worm?!
First of all, can we really trust her?!
You must know how I work by now.
I will use everyone that I can use.
Is this really okay?
Trusting humans?
I will use everyone that I can use.
That's all there is to it.
'Kazama Daisuke - Make Up Artist'
Daisuke?
This is Kazama Daisuke Make Up Therapy.
Umm...
Excuse me.
Daisuke... can you put Daisuke on?
Kazama is busy with work right now...
I will accept your appointment.
I want to talk to him right away! Please!
You're a fan, right?
Thank you for your support...
Daisuke...
Make Up.
Great work, Daisuke.
It's perfect.
Thank you very much.
But...
You are awfully quiet.
You used to compliment me so much.
Your beauty has not changed...
You are truly a single...
Single...
Ummm...
How boring.
Maybe next time...
I'll call for this boy?
This boy has such a good reputation.
You might be in trouble if
you're not careful, Daisuke.
Good work.
A fan just called. I dealt with her though.
What's my next job?
That's it for today.
There's been a lot of cancellations lately.
Perhaps it's due to the increase in rivals?
Umm... it's hard for me to say, but...
What is it?
I want this to be my last day.
I thought I'd try taking care
of a promising new guy.
I understand.
Please do what you want.
He said it was okay.
I can start in the morning.
Today's cooking is still the best.
Great work, Jiiya.
What's wrong, Jiiya?
You look pale.
Jiiya?
Jiiya!
How long are you going to stay here?
Till you cook me one of your recipes.
Gon!
You...
Where's Daisuke?
Didn't you recover your memory and go home?
Do you know where Daisuke is?
Come to think of it, I haven't seen him recently.
Not that I'm complaining.
I see.
Hey.
Can you let me work part time at this restaurant?
Please.
Part time?
What do you mean?
What happened?
It's terrible!
Jiiya is...
What is it?
Mr. Kazama Daisuke, correct?
And you would be?
Challenge me!
Ultimate
Supreme
Make up.
You're quite talented.
You're not bad yourself.
Looks like it's a draw.
Next time...
...I will definitely win.
You are too cheeky.
That's the man!
That man is the culprit!
Please eat.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for doing this for someone like me.
So...
How is he?
Without a doubt, he's overworked.
It's because you're always hard on him.
N-no!
You always overestimate me.
You are humanity's treasure.
Hurry and get better.
I can always come and cook.
I don't need your help!
I will tend to Jiiya.
Can you do that?
Of course.
I am the man that stands at the top of nursing.
Hey. Then let me stay. I'll definitely help.
You...
Okay.
I won't be responsible for what happens.
You should go home.
I'm sure your mother is worried.
No! I'm not going back till I see Daisuke.
I have a flower for that.
What do you mean?
Don't worry.
I will take responsibility for her.
I am the man that stands at the top of baby sitting.
Just... what did I do?
You!
Stop!
Meat bill!
Fish bill!
My salary?
Interest.
Gasoline bill.
Loan?
The money from your company?
Charges.
Fish bill!
My salary?
Gasoline bill!
Interest!
Meat bill!
My salary?
What... is this?
They're bills.
This house is really nice, but...
...financially, aren't you bankrupt?
Impossible!
I am a descendent from the
famous British Discabil family.
I should have plenty of money in the bank.
I'm sorry.
I'll definitely repay you in a month.
Just wait a bit longer...
It can't be...
No...
Help.
Hey... I wonder if the part time job pay is okay?
Tendou, this sweet fish rice is très bien!
Juka's mouth also goes mmm.
The best part is how natural it is.
The good flavors are completely
different from western cooking.
This...
It can't be.
Tempura soba. It's 540 yen.
Good work.
W-wait a minute!
Where's my change?
I took it as your donation.
After all, with these hands I must rebuild
the finances of the famous Discabil family.
What are you talking about?
This isn't enough of a donation!
Give me more!
I will take it!
Kazama Daisuke!
You're coming with us for suspicion of murder!
Move!
Raid!
You want to eat this?!
Are those noodles normal?!
You...
What are you doing?
Yo.
Murderer.
You're wrong!
What are you doing?
Reporting to the police, of course.
It's my duty as a citizen.
I told you that's not the case!
It's a misunderstanding.
I've fallen into some sort of trap!
Well...
That is possible.
You're a pathetic man, but not a murderer.
At any rate, you can't stay here.
We'll talk at my house.
You're really helping me?
I owe you.
But we're only talking till Juka returns.
I can't let my little sister meet
with a wanted criminal after all.
And I'm not doing this for you.
It's for Gon.
Gon...
She's wanted to see you.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
I'm home!
I forgot, my club is on summer break.
My blunder!
Who are you?
Where's Tendou?
He left on some urgent business.
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Nice to meet you.
I'm your big brother's friend...
Could it be...
This?
I had no idea you were Tendou's friend!
I also didn't know that he had
a beautiful little sister like you.
Hey.
Can you tell me how to do make up?
Clock Up!
CLOCK UP
Clock Up.
ONE
TWO
THREE
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Rider Kick.
Kazama style ascension technique.
Ultimate Make up.
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Unfortuantely... ZECT has confirmed his death.
The living Kazama Daisuke is a Worm.
From now on I will always live on as you.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.