Rider Kick.
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
Hiyori!
That's...!
Where is Hiyori?!
Who the hell are you?
Just what happened?
Who knows!
Wait!
What are you drawing?
Doesn't matter.
You...
Where did you go?
Hiyori...
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
Then... Hiyori has been missing since that day?
Yeah, it's been a week.
So you've been depressed all that time, haven't you?
But, she'll definitely be saved, right?
Yeah...
That's not like you.
What happened to the old Kagami,
always rushing in blindly?
Of course I really want to save her, but...
I don't know what to do...
Mr. Kagami!
Juka...
What's with this car?!
He said it's my personal limousine.
Well... I don't know the details, but...
Yes?
...at any rate, Big Bro likes this car.
Lucky, lucky!
"Lucky"?
So bye bye!
Yes. I understand.
Kagami. Time for work.
Okay.
Another team is here?
Shadow's here too.
Stop gossiping.
All teams and Shadow plunge in from the front.
Let's go.
Okay.
Where have I heard that voice before?
The Worm is in the deepest room.
Eliminate it within three minutes.
Why are trainees included?
Kageyama, you can complain after you're finished.
Move!
Ca-Captain!
Hurry up and get me down!
Don't let your guard down!
Move forward while watching out for traps!
Okay.
Misaki!
Are you okay?
Yes.
One, two!
Five seconds.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
That's the stuff.
You...
What are you doing?!
You should probably watch your mouth, Mister.
A girl?!
Tendou, as Kabuto, has become a member of ZECT.
Furthermore, H.Q. acknowledged his abilities,
and quickly gave this area to the Commander.
Isn't that amazing?
Mister, you didn't know?
How could I have known?
And this was a survival race to decide
who will be my second-in-command.
Trainee Takatori Renge.
Apprentice Kagami Arata.
So who should I make my second-in-command?
Here here! Here!
I'm willing to let you have it because
of our past friendly relations.
Tendou! Why are you here...?
You...
Who are you again?
Stop playing games!
You...!
Don't move. It's also around your neck.
Very good.
Alright.
I've decided on you.
I did it!
M-my neck! My neck!
My prize for the winner.
It's good.
No... that's okay.
So I, Takatori Renge, will work hard as
Mr. Tendou's second-in-command.
Pleased to be working with you all.
Okay, Mr. Tendou, if you will?
My grandmother once said...
"A cuisine's flavor is decided
by preparation and performance."
It's the same with battle.
Understand.
Yes! From here on, I will follow Mr. Tendou...
And one more thing.
From now on you will eat here.
I want to make this shop
as successful as possible.
Understand.
Yes!
1,000 yen please.
What are you trying to do?
Did you join ZECT to make it
easier for you to find Hiyori?
How naive.
To save Hiyori, ZECT must be destroyed.
Destroyed?
How?
Eliminate all Riders beside myself.
What?!
Renge. You eat too. This lunch is very good.
Don't worry.
What is that?
From the Warring Period, the best
provision to carry, dried boiled-rice.
Dried Boiled Rice
All the trainees eat this.
Is it good?
I've forgotten that feeling.
I haven't eaten in seven years.
Why was Kabuto let into the organization?!
That is where he belonged in the first place.
There is no reason to refuse him.
But we know he's up to something anyway.
If you know that, then why?!
We are already handling it.
I... haven't heard anything.
Mishima... Please don't abandon me. I'll help you.
Okay?
Just a bit more...
Alright! Perfect!
Then I'm taking it.
Young Master!
What are you doing with Sasword Zecter?
He wanted to buy it, so I gave it to him.
It's for the rebuliding of the
Discabil family, I have no regrets.
But... the Worms...
Don't worry.
Even if I can't be Sasword...
I have the Discabil hereditary famous sword...
Discalibur.
Oh right. I guess you
weren't told yet, Mr. Kagami.
Tendou and I aren't real siblings.
Some years before I was born,
my grandmother took him in.
Tendou, who is family.
I see...
That's why that time...
You are my little sister... my only little sister.
I'm so happy having a brother like that.
He's always by my side.
And he's kind. And he's cool!
I love my brother!
It must be him!
Come in.
Juka, this—!
Tendou bought Sasword Zecter?!
Right now, if he fights a Worm, Young Master
will surely turn into the Scorpion Worm.
Please... get it back.
Tendou, that guy...
Leave it to me.
You... Why did you take
Sasword Zecter from Tsurugi?
He needs that!
I told you.
I will eliminate all Riders except myself.
To do that...
I need all Zecters in my hand.
What?
Because of our past friendly relations...
...I will give you special treatment.
Will you be good and hand over Gatack Zecter?
Or will I have to take it by force in battle?
Which way? Pick.
You...
Are you serious?
Mr. Tendou, excuse us.
What did you want from me?
Hand over TheBee Zecter. Right now.
What?!
I'll never give this up!
Then I'll take it using force.
Transform.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
TheBee Zecter is as important as my life!
Why would I give it to someone like you?!
Stop it...
Stop it!
Transform!
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
Cast Off!
CAST OFF
Why must the Riders be eliminated?
To protect Hiyori!
Protect Hiyori?
Riders fight to protect humanity.
Both ZECT and the Riders...
exist to defeat the Worms.
Even if I find Hiyori...
...as long as they exist,
Hiyori cannot live as Hiyori should!
Really?
I am the only Rider needed.
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
Rider Kick!
That... What should I do?
How unsightly.
I can help you.
What kind of person would take help from you!
Please...
A Worm?
I will defeat all Worm.
I'll show you the shine of
the famous sword, Discalibur.
What?!
I see... just what I'd expect
from the famous sword.
It's so bright you cannot see it.
Why?!
Young Master!
This is the real one. Please use it!
Gon.
Did Daisuke just give it up without a fight?
No. I brought it without permission.
Because, if the man walking the path of
heaven says so, then it has to be right.
Here.
Gon, you should get going.
Bye.
Good timing.
There's something I want to ask you.
Jiiya. What's the meaning of this?
I'm terribly sorry.
I had sold the real one!
Then... you bought this back?
How much was it?
Well...
The money from the Sasword Zecter wasn't enough,
so I gave up my paycheck once again.
Money.
Money is a fleeting thing, is it not?
Talk!
What happened at Area X?!
Did Hiyori disappear because of that?!
It has nothing to do with humans. Give up on it.
Rider Sting!
RIDER STING
Move.
I will finish him.
Yeah. Get it over with.
That's...
It can't be...
Yaguruma.
You!
What happened to your Perfect Harmony?
Now...
I no longer have Perfect Harmony.
Either way, a loser like me...
Transform.
TRANSFORM
CHANGE KICK HOPPER
Now, who was it I heard laughing at me?
Was it you?
Rider Jump.
RIDER JUMP
Rider Kick!
RIDER KICK
He's the enemy of ZECT! Get him!
Kageyama.
Won't you go to hell with me?
RIDER JUMP
RIDER KICK
You... Give that back!
I will take all Zecters.
Will you give me yours too?
Tendou...
Tendou is trying to gather all the Zecters.
I see. Keep a closer eye on him.
When the time is ripe, I will give the order.
Yes, sir.
You're so lucky...
Either way, a loser like me...
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
Only by crawling on the ground...
will you be able to see the light.
Kabuto... I just destroyed your future.
The future is already in my hands.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.