Rider Kick.
RIDER KICK
CLOCK OVER
You.
You...
You killed my parents!
All your wishes may come true...
If you're the chosen one!
The world's running amok, there's no more time to bring it back...
To its former self!
Your heart's also moving fast!
The clock's running!
Go beyond tomorrow!
Whenever I fight next to you, I'm reborn!
With a visible speed that transcends motion!
Who can we lean on for strength, but ourselves?
Don't let the light-speed vision slide...
...if you can surpass it!
You...
I-it can't be!
You're the traitor!
Oh no! I'm gonna be late!
You get out of school in
the afternoon today, right?
Yeah.
Then I'll prepare a delicious lunch for you.
All right!
I'm off!
Have a safe trip.
Can I help you with something?
There's something I want to ask you.
I can't believe it.
Kagami is the traitor?
People can surprise you.
Then we should see what he has to say about this.
Kagami has already tainted himself.
Please don't do anything unnecessary.
Leave the rest to me.
If that's okay with you.
Hey! Over here!
Why him?
How strange...
It was a woman who requested your services....
Yesterday... I saw a weird guy.
He... wore the same belt...
...as the one from seven years ago.
I think...
I think he killed my parents....
Childhood memories aren't always right.
I didn't want to remember it either.
But... that time...
When I touched that belt....
The memories revived..... in my mind.
The terrible memories I suppressed for so long....
Then why not forget them?
They're bad memories.
One hundred negatives can never make one positive.
Is that belt yours?
No.
It was in your bag, right?
It's not my taste.
Then whose is it?!
Who is that weirdo?
I'm done.
Try it.
Don't try to trick me!
It's good.
Try a bite.
Don't ever show up in front of me again.
I refuse to do your make up.
I usually have a principle
against doing men's make up.
That's not it. I want you to
cooperate with my organization.
I already gave my refusal before.
Come on, Daisuke. This is business.
This sound good to you?
You want to be paid money?
It's not too expensive, right?
They call me the famous make up artist after all.
This is just ridiculous!
If you're leaving....
Don't forget this.
That's why I didn't want to do this.
I'm asking too.
Your power is needed.
I'm a whimsical wind that
moves from flower to flower.
My ears perk when they hear the
murmurs of a beautiful flower.
There he goes again.
This guy...! His attitude is
completely different from before!
My phone's battery is dead.
Can I borrow your cell?
Here.
Why is that guy a Rider?
You...
The usual.
I told you not to come didn't I?
I decide where I go.
Hiyori.
Is something wrong?
Welcome.
Hey, lately Hiyori has been down.
Did something happen?
Don't worry.
There's no such thing as a
winter that doesn't end in spring.
That's it. Use that to cheer up Hiyori, okay?
Today's recipe is rolled cabbage?
This is bad.
This is for everything I owe.
What do you mean?
I will never come again.
Don't worry, Hiyori.
Why are they all Shadow members?
Seems there's a traitor.
Traitor?
Misaki.
Maybe if we check this
cell phone, we'll get a lead?
Is something wrong?
'Kagami Arata'
Why is Kagami's name...
I'll check the data in this
cell phone in more detail.
You watch over Kagami.
Okay.
Temporarily
Closed
Temporarily Closed
Soba would have been good for a day like this.
What? It's closed?
Poor guy.
Do you know any good soba shops around here?
Who are you?!
Why are you following Kagami?
You... are Kabuto aren't you?
And you're TheBee?
I'd like to see your face!
Too bad.
More importantly... tell me
why you're following him.
I'll tell you if you want.
Kagami is a traitor.
It's Hiyori! I'm so happy!
Did you come to play? Come in!
No, No. I didn't...
Give this to Tendou.
What is it?
You'll find out when you give it to him.
Hey. Won't you eat with me?
No.
Please! Please!
Please go ahead.
Finely chopped burdock.
Potato flowers.
White spinach.
Fried egg.
Boiled rice and miso soup.
This... was all made by him?
Of course! Let's eat!
My grandmother once said...
"Sickness comes from food."
"You can't spell "great" without "eat"."
Right? Isn't it delicious?
Yes.
It's very delicious.
Misaki....
You are under arrest.
What do you mean?
You used the cell phone of an eliminated
Shadow member to your advantage.
That's how you were able to
convey the members' data.
That's ridiculous!
Are you the traitor?
No! Because just now,
I lent my cell phone to Kageyama....
When did he...?
Let's have a long talk.
No... It wasn't me.
Wait!
Don't let him get away!
Roger!
Temporarily Closed
Has heaven abandoned me?
Tendou!
Yo.
Got a minute?
Let me go.
Do you know a good restaurant around here?
This is no time for that! Listen!
I don't want to listen.
Right now, my biggest priority is eating.
But I...
I don't know what happened, but...
...can't you solve your own
problems once in a while?
First, I will eat.
Kagami.
Excuse me.
It was an accident, my legs are just so darn long.
You!
Why are you so panicked? Did something happen?
Did you see Kagami?
Someone being chased by a flower.
How I envy being chased by a flower.
He ran that way.
I thought you weren't coming anymore.
The usual....
Delicious.
Tendou... couldn't have done that.
I'm sure.... he couldn't have.
Come for me?
It's so hard being popular.
What am I doing?
Aren't you guys.... Shadow?!
Kagami! Stop resisting!
Kageyama! Why is Shadow here?!
Hey, hey. Call me Captain Kageyama.
I heard from him.
He pretended to split up
Shadow to expose the traitor.
I'm not the traitor!
If you had properly investigated,
you would see that.
We will investigate.
Hand the gun over.
Okay.
Kagami! Hang on!
Hang on!
I'm sorry. I thought he was going to shoot you,
Captain, so my finger slipped.
It's okay.
Now we know who the real traitor is.
So it's you.
You're joking...
Kagami was just a lure.
The real traitor would try to shut Kagami up.
I was waiting for this.
You sacrificed Kagami for that?!
Why not? He was just an apprentice.
The second Perfect Harmony...
This is for a new perfect connection.
How is this perfect?
My grandmother once said...
"A truly famous store does
not put out advertisements."
Kabuto!
Only one person was able
to see me as I was in Clock Up.
You're a Worm.
Then Kagami is...
Kagami!
Hang on.
You!
You weren't going to protect me?
You...
...should be glad just to live on in me.
What?
Each team, split up and eradicate the Worms!
Transform.
TRANSFORM
Cast Off.
CAST OFF
CHANGE WASP
Rider Sting.
RIDER STING
Clock Up.
CLOCK UP
Pay close attention. This happens in the
very instant that the bullets are flying.
ONE TWO THREE
Rider Kick.
RIDER SHOOTING
Looks like a capricious wind is blowing.
You...!
Kamen Rider Kabuto!
It's too dangerous! Facing a Worm alone.
You have no right to lead people.
I want to prove myself.
I want to show that I can do it if I try.
Walking the Path of Heaven. Ruling Over Us All.